<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Conversational Designer - IVR - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2f7a4dc4846f4f62</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO is looking for a passionate and talented Sr. Conversational Designer. This role will work on a variety of conversational platforms, designing experiences that serve customer needs across the enterprise and connect to different communication channels. The individual will work closely with product managers, engineers and other experienced designers from initial concept and strategy through the execution. Your bac</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Conversational Designer - IVR - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=65c768a2d73a67bc</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO is looking for a passionate and talented Sr. Conversational Designer. This role will work on a variety of conversational platforms, designing experiences that serve customer needs across the enterprise and connect to different communication channels. The individual will work closely with product managers, engineers and other experienced designers from initial concept and strategy through the execution. Your bac</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Conversational Designer - IVR - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dd0b872152ad8c23</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO is looking for a passionate and talented Sr. Conversational Designer. This role will work on a variety of conversational platforms, designing experiences that serve customer needs across the enterprise and connect to different communication channels. The individual will work closely with product managers, engineers and other experienced designers from initial concept and strategy through the execution. Your bac</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Generative AI Research Engineer, Multimodal, Agent Modeling - SIML - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0114d362816ac659</link>
        <description>Are you passionate about Generative AI? Are you interested in working on groundbreaking generative modeling technologies to enrich billions of people? We are driving multiple initiatives focused on advancing generative models, and we are seeking technical leaders experienced in training, adapting and deploying large\-scale generative models. This role emphasizes multimodal understanding and generation, and the development of agentic systems that push the boundaries of what AI can achieve responsibly.  

  

We are the Intelligence System Experience (ISE) team within Apple’s software organization. The team operates at the intersection of multimodal machine learning and system experiences. It oversees a range of experiences such as System Experience (Springboard, Settings), Image Generation, Genmoji, Writing tools, Keyboards, Pencil \&amp; Paper, Generative Shortcuts \- all powered by production scale ML workflows. Our multidisciplinary ML teams focus on a broad spectrum of areas, including </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Machine Learning Engineer, Data and ML Innovation - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=eaea88e5d2eb6ed5</link>
        <description>Are you excited to tackle some of the most ambitious technical challenges in Apple Intelligence? Be involved in collaborating closely with our machine learning researchers, engineers, and data scientists? Together, you will orchestrate groundbreaking research initiatives and develop transformative products designed to build a significant impact for billions of users worldwide!  

  

As part of Apple's AI and Machine Learning org, we encourage and create groundbreaking technology for large\-scale ML systems, computer vision, natural language processing, and multi\-modal understanding and generation. The Data and Machine Learning Innovation (DMLI) team is looking for Machine Learning Engineer to explore new methods, challenge existing metrics or protocols, and develop new insightful practices that will change how we understand data and overcome real\-world ML challenges.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a Machine Learning (ML) Engineer, you will be entrusted with the critical role of in</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Machine Learning Engineer, Data and ML Innovation - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dc80afa79bcf27b7</link>
        <description>Are you excited to tackle some of the most ambitious technical challenges in Apple Intelligence? Be involved in collaborating closely with our machine learning researchers, engineers, and data scientists? Together, you will orchestrate groundbreaking research initiatives and develop transformative products designed to build a significant impact for billions of users worldwide!  

  

As part of Apple's AI and Machine Learning org, we encourage and create groundbreaking technology for large\-scale ML systems, computer vision, natural language processing, and multi\-modal understanding and generation. The Data and Machine Learning Innovation (DMLI) team is looking for Machine Learning Engineer to explore new methods, challenge existing metrics or protocols, and develop new insightful practices that will change how we understand data and overcome real\-world ML challenges.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a Machine Learning (ML) Engineer, you will be entrusted with the critical role of in</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Manager, Siri Communications Experiences - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=126282e637cf61f1</link>
        <description>The Siri Communications App Experiences team at Apple is seeking a hands\-on Engineering Manager to lead the development of Siri’s customer facing experiences across Apple platforms. This is a high impact leadership role at the center of conversational and transactional experiences used by millions of people every day. You will define a compelling product vision, build a thoughtful roadmap, and guide a talented engineering team to bring that vision to life. At Apple, innovation is woven into everything we do, from groundbreaking products to the way we collaborate and operate. If you’re excited about shaping the future of intelligent communication experiences (e.g. Messages, Phone, Payment, Mail app experiences) through Siri, this is an opportunity to build something meaningful at global scale.  

  

**Description**  

  

We’re looking for a technical leader who pairs strong engineering depth with a passion for crafting exceptional user experiences.  

  

As the Engineering Manager f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Answers, Knowledge and Information (AKI) - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e6ed5336430ed79e</link>
        <description>The Answers, Knowledge and Information Team is building the next\-generation of machine learning solutions for Knowledge Q\&amp;A at Apple and help power features including Siri and Spotlight. The features we build are redefining how hundreds of millions of people use their computers and mobile devices to search and find what they are looking for. As part of our team, you will be leveraging and improving upon the latest advancements in machine learning and software engineering to understand user queries and intents, retrieve and rank documents and generate helpful answers and work on horizontal areas such as internationalization and safety.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a member of our fast\-paced group, you’ll have the unique and rewarding opportunity to shape upcoming products from Apple. Our team includes a diversity of backgrounds from applied machine learning engineers with a focus on ML and LLM to experienced distributed systems engineers. As such, we are looking for candidates wi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Manager, Siri Communications Experiences - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b0d36d43be36aaa</link>
        <description>The Siri Communications App Experiences team at Apple is seeking a hands\-on Engineering Manager to lead the development of Siri’s customer facing experiences across Apple platforms. This is a high impact leadership role at the center of conversational and transactional experiences used by millions of people every day. You will define a compelling product vision, build a thoughtful roadmap, and guide a talented engineering team to bring that vision to life. At Apple, innovation is woven into everything we do, from groundbreaking products to the way we collaborate and operate. If you’re excited about shaping the future of intelligent communication experiences (e.g. Messages, Phone, Payment, Mail app experiences) through Siri, this is an opportunity to build something meaningful at global scale.  

  

**Description**  

  

We’re looking for a technical leader who pairs strong engineering depth with a passion for crafting exceptional user experiences.  

  

As the Engineering Manager f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Lead AI Engineer - Capital One</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=88d02788d30ee295</link>
        <description>Sr. Lead AI Engineer**Overview:**


At Capital One, we are creating responsible and reliable AI systems, changing banking for good. For years, Capital One has been an industry leader in using machine learning to create real\-time, personalized customer experiences. Our investments in technology infrastructure and world\-class talent — along with our deep experience in machine learning — position us to be at the forefront of enterprises leveraging AI. From informing customers about unusual charges to answering their questions in real time, our applications of AI \&amp; ML are bringing humanity and simplicity to banking. We are committed to continuing to build world\-class applied science and engineering teams to deliver our industry leading capabilities with breakthrough product experiences and scalable, high\-performance AI infrastructure. At Capital One, you will help bring the transformative power of emerging AI capabilities to reimagine how we serve our customers and businesses who have</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead AI Engineer - Capital One</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5e071657edaece49</link>
        <description>Lead AI Engineer**Overview:**


At Capital One, we are creating responsible and reliable AI systems, changing banking for good. For years, Capital One has been an industry leader in using machine learning to create real\-time, personalized customer experiences. Our investments in technology infrastructure and world\-class talent — along with our deep experience in machine learning — position us to be at the forefront of enterprises leveraging AI. From informing customers about unusual charges to answering their questions in real time, our applications of AI \&amp; ML are bringing humanity and simplicity to banking. We are committed to continuing to build world\-class applied science and engineering teams to deliver our industry leading capabilities with breakthrough product experiences and scalable, high\-performance AI infrastructure. At Capital One, you will help bring the transformative power of emerging AI capabilities to reimagine how we serve our customers and businesses who have com</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Scope Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=35f2715891200f11</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| SAN FRANCISCO, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


PRODUCT


4626


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Waymo's Product Management Team is a mission\-driven team responsible for writing and enacting first\-of\-their\-kind playbooks to bring fu</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Analyst - Strava</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b036e535ada0a751</link>
        <description>**Location**
------------


Strava SF

**Employment Type**
-------------------


Full time

**Location Type**
-----------------


Hybrid

**Department**
--------------


DepartmentTechnologyData and Insights

**Compensation**
----------------

* $176K – $187K • Offers Equity


This range reflects base compensation only and does not include equity or benefits. Your recruiter can share more details about the full compensation package during the hiring process.


At Strava, we know our employees are the most important ingredient to our success, and our compensation and total rewards programs reflect that. We take a market\-based approach to pay, and pay may vary depending on the department and your location. Salary ranges are categorized into one of three zones based on a cost of labor index for that geographic area. We will determine the candidate’s starting pay based on job\-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location, and market conditions. We may modify these ranges in t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Scope Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e61f2258f4732d6d</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Waymo's Product Management Team is a mission\-driven team responsible for writing and enacting first\-of\-their\-kind playbooks to bring fully autonomous driving technology to market. Our team develops simple solutions for complex problems by orchestrating cross\-functional efforts to safely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Scope Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=42bcec796a8d44e3</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Waymo's Product Management Team is a mission\-driven team responsible for writing and enacting first\-of\-their\-kind playbooks to bring fully autonomous driving technology to market. Our team develops simple solutions for complex problems by orchestrating cross\-functional efforts to safely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship, Audio &amp; Sensor Software Engineer, Vehicle Engineering (Summer 2026) - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8d6be84292cf2a58</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Consider before submitting an application:

  

This position is expected to start May 2026 and continue through summer term (ending approximately August 2026 or later, if available). We ask for a minimum of 12 weeks, full\-time (40 hours/week) and on\-site, for most internships. Our internship program is for students who are actively enrolled in an academic program. Recent graduates seeking employment after graduation and not returning to school should apply for full\-time positions, not internships.


International Students: If your work authorization is through CPT, please consult your school on your ability to work 40 hours per week before applying. You must be able to work 40 hours per week on\-site. Many students will be limited to part\-time during the academic year.


The Internship Recruiting Team is driven by the passion to recognize and develop emerging talent. Our year\-round program places the best students in positions where they will grow technically, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Process Development Engineer, Metrology - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1d5062b85d2f9868</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Tesla is looking for a highly motivated process development engineer to create, develop and scale up manufacturing processes for our cutting\-edge Tesla battery cell manufacturing line. This role will invent, develop, scale up and optimize battery manufacturing processes within a cross\-functional engineering team responsible for the development lifecycle and launch into manufacturing. In this role, you will work closely with many organizations both internal and external to Tesla taking new battery designs from initial concept through into full production.


The battery cell is a critical component in Tesla vehicles and storage systems. This role will have the opportunity to make meaningful contributions to our products. The work environment is demanding, fast\-paced and incredibly exciting. The ideal candidate should be ready to push their limits, as they join in highly motivated and capable team to make unbelieve things into reality.

 **What You'll Do*** Drive dev</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Competitive Intelligence) - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=522b2a91c85811e4</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Competitive Intelligence Team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

The Competitive Intelligence team works to understand the strategy and performance of Uber and other companies with similar products through a combination of external and internal data. Uber operates in a diverse array of markets and product categories filled with rapidly evolving competing options; assessing the success or failure of a product or strategy depends on understanding this context. Doing this, and doing it well, is an interesting and challenging problem. The team uses its data analysis, statistical modeling, economics, and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Competitive Intelligence) - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=78f0ac2a20b8c548</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Competitive Intelligence Team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

The Competitive Intelligence team works to understand the strategy and performance of Uber and other companies with similar products through a combination of external and internal data. Uber operates in a diverse array of markets and product categories filled with rapidly evolving competing options; assessing the success or failure of a product or strategy depends on understanding this context. Doing this, and doing it well, is an interesting and challenging problem. The team uses its data analysis, statistical modeling, economics, and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; GenAI Data Scientist-Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6ab4e8d25e18fa12</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in data and analytics focus on leveraging data to drive insights and make informed business decisions. They utilise advanced analytics techniques to help clients optimise their operations and achieve their strategic goals. In data analysis at PwC, you will focus on utilising advanced analytical techniques to extract insights from large datasets and drive data\-driven decision\-making. You will leverage skills in data manipulation, visualisation, and statistical modelling to support clients in solving complex business problems.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situations, you are growing your personal brand, deepening technical expertise and awareness of your strengths. You are expected to anticipate the needs of your teams and clients, and to deliver quality. Embracing increased ambiguity, you are comfortable when the path forward isn’t clear, yo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; GenAI Data Scientist-Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a20fa6b3324a7771</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in data and analytics focus on leveraging data to drive insights and make informed business decisions. They utilise advanced analytics techniques to help clients optimise their operations and achieve their strategic goals. In data analysis at PwC, you will focus on utilising advanced analytical techniques to extract insights from large datasets and drive data\-driven decision\-making. You will leverage skills in data manipulation, visualisation, and statistical modelling to support clients in solving complex business problems.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situations, you are growing your personal brand, deepening technical expertise and awareness of your strengths. You are expected to anticipate the needs of your teams and clients, and to deliver quality. Embracing increased ambiguity, you are comfortable when the path forward isn’t clear, yo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applications Engineer (ML/Auto Defect Classification) - PDF Solutions, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c81b35d3235a3b42</link>
        <description>Overview:

**Role Summary**  

We are seeking a **Senior Applications Engineer** to join our team, focusing on the development of cutting\-edge machine learning and artificial intelligence solutions for the semiconductor industry. The ideal candidate will have extensive experience in creating robust and scalable software, with a strong background in data analysis, machine learning, and containerization technologies.
Responsibilities:
* **Design and Implement ML/AI Algorithms:** Help develop and implement advanced machine learning and AI\-based algorithms for the automatic classification of defects in semiconductor inspection tools.
* **Data Analysis:** Analyze large volumes of defect data to identify critical patterns, trends, and anomalies, using this analysis to inform model development.
* **Training and Model Development:** Train, validate, and deploy defect classification models, ensuring they meet strict performance and accuracy requirements.
* **System Optimization:** Continuousl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Scientist (Senior Consultant) - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4628289a62607241</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Scientist (Senior Consultant) - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=58cea49ce108a9bb</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Operations Engineer (DevOps/MLOps) - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ab59de9298cecf92</link>
        <description>We are seeking an experienced Staff Software Development Engineer with deep expertise in cloud infrastructure and a passion for building scalable, production‑grade ML systems. As part of the Applied Research and Technology Services organization, you will play a meaningful role crafting the operational backbone for high‑performance, reliable, and globally scaled machine learning services. In this role, you’ll work closely with multi\-functional collaborators. These include Adobe Research, Adobe AI Platforms, and product engineering teams. Together, you will architect solutions that speed up innovation and improve service resilience. You will also provide technical leadership and define, document, and enforce guidelines adopted across teams. You will own technical direction for core service infrastructure and MLOps, influence architectural decisions across multiple teams, and raise the operational maturity of the organization through standards, reusable platforms, and mentorship. You wil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer - Test Automation - KLA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=463a562e09f02043</link>
        <description>Company Overview
KLA is a global leader in diversified electronics for the semiconductor manufacturing ecosystem. Virtually every electronic device in the world is produced using our technologies. No laptop, smartphone, wearable device, voice\-controlled gadget, flexible screen, VR device or smart car would have made it into your hands without us. KLA invents systems and solutions for the manufacturing of wafers and reticles, integrated circuits, packaging, printed circuit boards and flat panel displays. The innovative ideas and devices that are advancing humanity all begin with inspiration, research and development. KLA focuses more than average on innovation and we invest 15% of sales back into R\&amp;D. Our expert teams of physicists, engineers, data scientists and problem\-solvers work together with the world’s leading technology providers to accelerate the delivery of tomorrow’s electronic devices. Life here is exciting and our teams thrive on tackling really hard problems. There is n</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager III, AI/ML, Cloud AI Systems - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cdb47d7888796038</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in program management.
* Experience managing machine learning or artificial intelligence programs.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of experience managing cross\-functional and cross\-team projects.
* Experience with quantitative analysis, cost\-effectiveness assessment techniques, and data quality metrics for AI products.
* Experience with machine learning algorithms and tools (e.g. TensorFlow), artificial intelligence, or deep learning.
* Experience in large\-scale high performance serving systems.
* Experience in communicating technical concepts to non\-technical audiences.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, yo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=362115024eda6496</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in product management or related technical role.
* 3 years of expe</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a5c9d6b28c62945</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager I, Machine Learning, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=16bd58a0803ea8bf</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Kirkland, WA, USA; New York, NY, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a relevant field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in program management.
* 8</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7e12063abf52b3ad</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Data &amp; Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=85dcda190e4e1590</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4617


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Waymo Mapping team's goal is to build a high resolution map of the world to support safe autonomous driving. We work on creating the map using a combination of automa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer II, Search - PlayStation</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6a9117e61d6c35de</link>
        <description>Position Type:
Location(s):
United States, San Mateo, CA
Date Posted:
Job ID:
R\-123175
  
**Why PlayStation?**


PlayStation isn’t just the Best Place to Play — it’s also the Best Place to Work. Today, we’re recognized as a global leader in entertainment producing The PlayStation family of products and services including PlayStation®5, PlayStation®4, PlayStation®VR, PlayStation®Plus, acclaimed PlayStation software titles from PlayStation Studios, and more.


PlayStation also strives to create an inclusive environment that empowers employees and embraces diversity. We welcome and encourage everyone who has a passion and curiosity for innovation, technology, and play to explore our open positions and join our growing global team.


The PlayStation brand falls under Sony Interactive Entertainment, a wholly\-owned subsidiary of Sony Group Corporation.

**Mid\-Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Search**

**San Mateo, CA**


Do you want to join a Machine Learning team committed to personaliz</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5e76f9580b7747d0</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Senior Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies.  



As a Senior Data Scientist, you will partner closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refine innovative growth strategies. Your expertise—especially in causal inference and advanced analytics—will be instrumental in surfacing critical insights and translating them into actionable hypotheses that fuel sustained customer and revenue growth. **Responsibilities**


* Drive Business Strategy through Data \- Translate business problems into analytical frameworks. Connect data across multiple functions to drive actionable recommendations and </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate, Digital Finance Transformation - Data Scientist - Private Equity Performance Improvement (OPEN TO ALL US LOCATIONS) - Alvarez &amp; Marsal</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=92087e0417204ffa</link>
        <description>Location: San Francisco, CA, United States  

Date Posted: Feb 28, 2026

  

**Description**


**Digital Finance Transformation \- Data Scientist: Associate – Private Equity Performance Improvement**

**About Alvarez \&amp; Marsal**


Alvarez \&amp; Marsal (A\&amp;M) is a global consulting firm with over 10,000 entrepreneurial, action and results\-oriented professionals in over 40 countries. We take a hands\-on approach to solving our clients' problems and assisting them in reaching their potential. Our culture celebrates independent thinkers and doers who positively impact our clients and shape our industry. The collaborative environment and engaging work—guided by A\&amp;M's core values of Integrity, Quality, Objectivity, Fun, Personal Reward, and Inclusive Diversity—are why our people love working at A\&amp;M.

**The Team**


A\&amp;M’s Private Equity Performance Improvement Services (PEPI) practice works with private equity held portfolio companies and provides our clients with solutions to preserve and g</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Director, Translational Data Science – Hematology R&amp;D - AstraZeneca</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4f7c5393a788aea4</link>
        <description>**Job Title:** Associate Director, Translational Data Science – Hematology R\&amp;D  

**Location:** South San Francisco, California, United States

  

At AstraZeneca, we put patients first and strive to meet their unmet needs worldwide. Working here means being entrepreneurial, thinking big and working together to make the impossible a reality. If you are swift to action, confident to lead, willing to collaborate, and curious about what science can do, then you’re our kind of person.


Recognizing the importance of individualized flexibility, our ways of working allow employees to balance personal and work commitments while ensuring we continue to create a strong culture of collaboration and teamwork by engaging face\-to\-face in our offices **3 days a week**. Our head office is purposely designed with collaboration in mind, providing space where teams can come together to strategize, brainstorm and connect on key projects.


Our dedication to sustainability is also central to our cultur</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Qcells</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=56d181c3f0e6aa90</link>
        <description>**Description**


### **POSITION DESCRIPTION:**

  

We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Grid \&amp; Energy Analytics team within G\&amp;ES. In this role, you will lead the implementation of enterprise\-grade microservices that support the real\-time optimization and simulation of diverse energy assets participating in U.S. wholesale electricity markets including CAISO, ERCOT, NYISO, ISO\-NE, and PJM.  

  

This position will be preferably based out of our Santa Clara, San Francisco, Houston, or Seattle, or Atlanta offices.### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

* Work closely with Technical Lead to improve microservices including optimization, simulation, and market emulation.
* Drive microservice benchmarking, develop operations metrics, and continuously improve system performance using data\-driven insights.
* Own significant software components, including documentation and testing suites, training junior engineers where appropriate.
* Contribute to the next\-generation mercha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Qcells</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cfe6cc1991668234</link>
        <description>**Description**


### **POSITION DESCRIPTION:**

  

We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Grid \&amp; Energy Analytics team within G\&amp;ES. In this role, you will lead the implementation of enterprise\-grade microservices that support the real\-time optimization and simulation of diverse energy assets participating in U.S. wholesale electricity markets including CAISO, ERCOT, NYISO, ISO\-NE, and PJM.  

  

This position will be preferably based out of our Santa Clara, San Francisco, Houston, or Seattle, or Atlanta offices.### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

* Work closely with Technical Lead to improve microservices including optimization, simulation, and market emulation.
* Drive microservice benchmarking, develop operations metrics, and continuously improve system performance using data\-driven insights.
* Own significant software components, including documentation and testing suites, training junior engineers where appropriate.
* Contribute to the next\-generation mercha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8211a592f6d505ca</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's sof</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=253f2c1dc16a7e33</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML Recommendations, Rankings, Predictions, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b46b5caf995b062</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience building and deploying recommendation systems models (retrieval, prediction, ranking, personalization, search quality, embedding) in production; and experience building architecture.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation tec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, AI/ML GenAI, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0190ac1e33679a35</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience leading ML design and optimizing ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products.
* 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 2 years of experience with state of the art GenAI techniques (e.g., LLMs, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) or with GenAI\-related concepts (language modeling, computer vision).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technical direction.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex, matrixed organization involving cross\-functional,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbdd6e3a81271bb3</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California **Job ID** 19494
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Senior Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies.
As a Senior Data Scientist, you will partner closely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Business - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c6625ad62ed33d83</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

The Business Data Science team uses data and analytics to optimize business performance, drive growth, and foster meaningful partnerships, with the goal of ensuring the sustained and impactful expansion of OpenAI's initiatives to maximize the benefits of AGI for all of humanity. We partner with Sales (GTM), Marketing, Partnerships, Support, Finance, Product, and Growth.
  
  

About the Role
  
  

As a member of our Business Data Science team, you will help build a data\-driven culture around insight generation, decision making, and strategy at OpenAI. This role is focused on driving customer success within our business products (ChatGPT Team, ChatGPT Enterprise, and API). You will work on projects such as identifying opportunities for interventions within a customer lifecycle to drive activation \&amp; onboarding, identifying target audiences for new feature launches, and measuring the efficacy of emails, events, and other interventions to drive ongoing engagement w</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA)Staff, Data Scientist - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f8712b5cef69991</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**About the Role** We’re looking for a Staff Data Scientist to design and build advanced forecasting models to ensure accurate financial planning and analysis (FP\&amp;A) that power critical business decisions. You’ll build and deploy state\-of\-the\-art time series models (classical \+ ML \+ deep learning), drive explainability and trust (XAI), and explore next\-generation approaches such as graph neural networks for spatiotemporal and relational forecasting problems. You’ll partner closely with engineering, product, and stakeholders to deliver measurable impact at scale. **What You’ll Do**
* **Design and deploy** statistically and ML models to address high\-impact financial forecasting needs, ensuring alignment with Walmart’s business objectives.
* **Perform statistical analysis** across large data sets and within defined segments to empower data driven decisions.
* **Own E2E forecasting lifecyc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 01:14:52 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
