<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Experimental Physicist - KBR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cb1ff63bda19eaa3</link>
        <description>**BELONG. CONNECT. GROW. with KBR.**


Around here, we define the future. We are a company of innovators, thinkers, creators, explorers, volunteers, and dreamers. But we all share one goal: to improve the world responsibly and safely.

**Job Description:**

  

We are seeking an Experimental Physicist with specialized expertise in acoustic testing of cryogenic propellant transfer lines to:

* Conduct acoustic testing of unwanted bubbles in cryogenic liquids propellent lines.
* Analyze and interpret data to understand the acoustic behavior and characteristics of the bubbles.
* Collaborate with a team of physicists and engineers on testing and data analysis.
* Utilize LabView, SolidWorks, and MATLAB for data acquisition, analysis, and reporting.
* Contribute to the development of protocols and standards for acoustic detection or "bubble alarm".
  

This person will lead independent research through numerical and theoretical analysis, exploring quantum error\-correction, quantum algorithm</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Training Framework Engineer, GenAI - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d94304e45f5389a1</link>
        <description>The Opportunity
  
Adobe Applied Science \&amp; Machine Learning ( ASML ) is seeking a Staff Machine Learning Training Framework Engineer to play a critical role in building and scaling the core training systems behind Adobe’s generative AI foundation models.
  
In this role, you will serve as a senior technical owner for key components of our training framework , translating research needs into reliable, scalable, and high‑performance training infrastructure. Rather than focusing on a single model, your work will enable multiple multimodal and video foundation models by strengthening the shared systems used to train them.
  
You will operate at the intersection of applied research and large‑scale systems execution, ensuring that training workflows are robust, reproducible, and performant across large GPU clusters. This role is ideal for a senior engineer who thrives on deep technical ownership, complex execution, and close collaboration with research teams. Job Responsibilities
  
**Train</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Oncology - BillionToOne</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7fc6d494ae291855</link>
        <description>**Ready to redefine what's possible in molecular diagnostics?**
---------------------------------------------------------------



Join a team of brilliant, passionate innovators who wake up every day determined to transform healthcare. At BillionToOne, we've built something extraordinary—a culture where transparency fuels trust, collaboration drives breakthroughs, and every voice matters in our mission to make life\-changing diagnostics accessible to all. We don't just aim for incremental improvements; we strive to build products that are 10x better than anything that exists today. Our people are our greatest asset:talented scientists, engineers, sales professionals, and visionaries united by an unwavering commitment to changing the standard of care in prenatal and cancer diagnostics. This is where cutting\-edge science meets human compassion—every innovation you contribute helps remove fear of unknown from some of life's most critical medical moments. **If you're driven by purpose, e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Engineer - Technical Lead - Arine</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bd21973a52e2b6d3</link>
        <description>Based in San Francisco, Arine is a rapidly growing healthcare technology and clinical services company with a mission to ensure individuals receive the safest and most effective treatments for their unique and evolving healthcare needs.



Frequently, medications cause more harm than good. Incorrect drugs and doses costs the US healthcare system over $528 billion in waste, avoidable harm, and hospitalizations each year. Arine is redefining what excellent healthcare looks like by solving these issues through our software platform (SaaS). We combine cutting edge data science, machine learning, AI, and deep clinical expertise to introduce a patient\-centric view to medication management, and develop and deliver personalized care plans on a massive scale for patients and their care teams.



Arine is committed to improving the lives and health of complex patients that have an outsized impact on healthcare costs and have traditionally been difficult to identify and address. These patients f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, ML Inference Performance - SambaNova Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=17d03a5e781bc408</link>
        <description>The era of pervasive AI has arrived. In this era, organizations will use generative AI to unlock hidden value in their data, accelerate processes, reduce costs, drive efficiency and innovation to fundamentally transform their businesses and operations at scale.



SambaNova Suite™ is the first full\-stack, generative AI platform, from chip to model, optimized for enterprise and government organizations. Powered by the intelligent SN40L chip, the SambaNova Suite is a fully integrated platform, delivered on\-premises or in the cloud, combined with state\-of\-the\-art open\-source models that can be easily and securely fine\-tuned using customer data for greater accuracy. Once adapted with customer data, customers retain model ownership in perpetuity, so they can turn generative AI into one of their most valuable assets.

### **About The Role**



The **Principal Compiler Engineer \- ML Systems** position will be responsible for working with the different layers of the compiler stack and </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA) Senior, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c0cb34f3703796f3</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

  

The Senior Software Engineer will lead the design, development, and delivery of scalable software solutions aligned with business objectives. This role involves analyzing requirements, creating detailed designs, and producing maintainable code while ensuring quality and security standards. The position requires collaboration with cross\-functional teams to address technical challenges, implement continuous integration and deployment practices, and support ongoing application performance and maintenance.  

  

**About the Team:**  

  

BuyBox is a critical service within Walmart's e\-commerce platform, responsible for selecting the best offer for an item. The BuyBox team is responsible for developing, maintaining, and optimizing the complex ecosystem of micro services, which selects the best offer for Walmart customers using machine learning and business rules. They ensure integration wit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist III - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a5248758e37ec23c</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------


Our Company If you’re thinking ‘scale’, think bigger and don’t stop there. At Walmart Labs, we don’t just innovate, we enable transformations across stores and different channels for the Walmart experience. We innovate to deliver a simple and seamless experience for our customers. Our tech talent solves the biggest and most complex problems. They drive digital transformation where data science and analytics are enabling us to better serve our customers and create a digital relationship with them. As our customers evolve and adapt, we are taking it a few notches further here. We’re changing what customers can expect from the experience of shopping, from the physical stores, to mobile social and even online; we’re not just ready for the future of shopping, we’re creating it. Our Team Market Intelligence (MINT) team at Walmart Global Tech delivers on the promise of EDLP (Every Day Low Prices) to</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Software Engineer Intern (Delivery Marketplace), United States - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=be700be9655d5573</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates in the machine learning and optimization domain to intern with our Delivery Marketplace team during summer 2026 (12 weeks). You will be embedded in an engineering team and work closely with other specialists, data scientists, and product managers. As a PhD intern, you will work on an exciting yet bold problem independently, under the supervision of an experienced engineer on that team.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

At Uber, we work on many ambitious engineering products covering many lines of business as well as the underlying platform technologies that power those businesses. We foster growth and increase profitability of Uber by pushing the frontiers of machine learning, constrained optimization, statistics, data science and economics and developing highly reliable and scalable platforms to accelerate Uber's impact on the transportation industry.
  

  

As a PhD software engineer intern, you will have a lot of opportunities to work with product m</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Experimental Physicist - KBR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e0154ab80ddd5538</link>
        <description>**Title:**


Experimental Physicist**BELONG. CONNECT. GROW. with KBR.**


Around here, we define the future. We are a company of innovators, thinkers, creators, explorers, volunteers, and dreamers. But we all share one goal: to improve the world responsibly and safely.

**Job Description:**

  

We are seeking an Experimental Physicist with specialized expertise in acoustic testing of cryogenic propellant transfer lines to:

* Conduct acoustic testing of unwanted bubbles in cryogenic liquids propellent lines.
* Analyze and interpret data to understand the acoustic behavior and characteristics of the bubbles.
* Collaborate with a team of physicists and engineers on testing and data analysis.
* Utilize LabView, SolidWorks, and MATLAB for data acquisition, analysis, and reporting.
* Contribute to the development of protocols and standards for acoustic detection or "bubble alarm".
  

This person will lead independent research through numerical and theoretical analysis, exploring quantum e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Off-Search, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81a42167b27b57bf</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights.
  

  

We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover mo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Principal AI/ML Scientist - Abbott</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e3c986d7589d1600</link>
        <description>Abbott is a global healthcare leader that helps people live more fully at all stages of life. Our portfolio of life\-changing technologies spans the spectrum of healthcare, with leading businesses and products in diagnostics, medical devices, nutritionals and branded generic medicines. Our 115,000 colleagues serve people in more than 160 countries.


Our medical devices help more than 10,000 people have healthier hearts, improve quality of life for thousands of people living with chronic pain and movement disorders, and liberate more than 500,000 people with diabetes from routine ﬁngersticks.

**Working at Abbott**


At Abbott, you can do work that matters, grow, and learn, care for yourself and family, be your true self and live a full life. You’ll also have access to:

* Career development with an international company where you can grow the career you dream of.
* Employees can qualify for free medical coverage in our Health Investment Plan (HIP) PPO medical plan in the next calendar</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA) Senior, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df5419f309e5132</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

  

As a Senior Software Engineer, you will lead the delivery of scalable software solutions by managing feature implementation, testing, and ongoing support within collaborative teams. This role requires expertise in multiple programming languages and a strong focus on software lifecycle execution, including automation and continuous integration. You will integrate AI and machine learning components to enhance system capabilities while ensuring alignment with platform objectives. By applying sound technical judgment and fostering innovation, you will contribute to high\-quality, reliable software that meets business goals and supports continuous improvement across the organization. **\*\*\*\*\*Immigration Sponsorship support will NOT be available for this**  

**position\*\*\*\*\***
  

**About the team:**
  

The Walmart Business (B2B) group focuses on delivering innovative solutions that em</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer - Palo Alto Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8f020aa6341a736b</link>
        <description>Santa Clara, California, United States Product Engineering Ref ID: JR\-015122  

**Our Mission**


At Palo Alto Networks®, we’re united by a shared mission—to protect our digital way of life. We thrive at the intersection of innovation and impact, solving real\-world problems with cutting\-edge technology and bold thinking. Here, everyone has a voice, and every idea counts. If you’re ready to do the most meaningful work of your career alongside people who are just as passionate as you are, you’re in the right place.

**Who We Are**


In order to be the cybersecurity partner of choice, we must trailblaze the path and shape the future of our industry. This is something our employees work at each day and is defined by our values: Disruption, Collaboration, Execution, Integrity, and Inclusion. We weave AI into the fabric of everything we do and use it to augment the impact every individual can have. If you are passionate about solving real\-world problems and ideating beside the best and t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer with AI/ML Focus - Tata Consultancy Services (TCS)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d0fc0f491c9f4bb</link>
        <description>JOB DESCRIPTION:
Core Responsibilities
1\. Data Architecture \&amp; Pipeline Design
* Identify good data set and data candidates for building AI based recommendation engine
* Design denormalized data structures optimized for LLM consumption
* Aggregate data from multiple CRM modules/tables into one for LLM consumption
* Implement data quality monitoring and validation frameworks

2\. CRM Data Expertise
* Analyze complex CRM schemas (Accounts, Opportunities, Notes, Order History, Account Actuals)
* Understand business relationships between entities and their impact on recommendations
* Map data lineage from source systems to AI\-ready datasets

 3\. AI/ML Data Preparation
* Data preprocessing and normalization for LLM consumption
* Create training datasets for recommendation model improvement
* Implement data versioning for model reproducibility

4\. Performance Optimization
* Query optimization for large\-scale data aggregation
* Caching strategies for frequently accessed recommendation da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Sutter Health</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9e4eb366f4273b09</link>
        <description>We are so glad you are interested in joining Sutter Health!

**Organization:**


SHSO\-Sutter Health System Office\-Bay**Position Overview:**


\*\*\*\*Please Note: While this position is listed as hybrid, regular in\-office attendance is required. Candidates should be prepared to commute to the San Francisco office on a consistent basis to support team collaboration and business needs.\*\*\*\*
  

  

Responsible for leading the design, build, and maintain Sutter Health’s artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) infrastructure, including end to end pipelines for ML and large language models (LLM) that support analytics, data science, and enterprise AI use cases. This includes how AI models and associated data are ingested, processed, trained, deployed, monitored, governed, and secured across cloud and on premises environments. Ensures that AI systems meet high standards of performance, reliability, and compliance, enabling the organization to safely and effectively integ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Observability - CRUSOE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7439ce0a1c20dfd8</link>
        <description>Crusoe's mission is to accelerate the abundance of energy and intelligence. We’re crafting the engine that powers a world where people can create ambitiously with AI — without sacrificing scale, speed, or sustainability.


Be a part of the AI revolution with sustainable technology at Crusoe. Here, you'll drive meaningful innovation, make a tangible impact, and join a team that’s setting the pace for responsible, transformative cloud infrastructure.

**About This Role:**


We’re seeking a Senior Software Engineer to play a key role on our Observability team within the Cloud Infrastructure organization. This team owns the real\-time observability platforms that underpin visibility, reliability, and operational insight across our cloud and data center infrastructure.

**What You’ll Be Working On:**

* Maintain and manage core observability tools, including platforms for metrics, events, logs and tracing.
* Develop and operate data pipelines to move telemetry data from various sources to b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Head of AI - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc47fcacc4c7ee4a</link>
        <description>**About Highlight AI**


We're a small, senior team building the intelligent OS for the agentic age. Highlight is a proactive AI that captures your team's context, surfaces what matters, and handles the busywork so you can focus on decisions and building. We ship fast, obsess over craft, and care deeply about user experience and trust. Backed by General Catalyst, Valor, SV Angel, and Conviction, we’re looking for like\-minded people to help define how the next generation of knowledge workers get things done.

**The Role**


We're hiring a **Head of AI Engineering** to lead and scale our ML and AI efforts as we build the engine that powers Highlight. You'll own the architecture, quality, and roadmap for how we ingest, model, and surface context, starting from data pipelines and evals to the context graph that makes our system truly useful. This is a hands\-on leadership role: you'll write code, set technical direction, mentor engineers, and collaborate closely with Backend and Product t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer - Unity Technologies</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f6aac306145591a6</link>
        <description>**The opportunity**  

At Unity, we're building a world\-class advertising platform that operates at a massive global scale. The Ads team powers the systems that connect advertisers with creators and players, driving performance, reliability, and growth across our ecosystem.



As a Data Engineer on the Feature Platform team, you'll play a critical role in building the data foundations that power machine learning, experimentation, and optimization across our ads ecosystem. You'll operate at the core of our ML infrastructure, transforming raw, high\-volume event data into reliable, production\-grade feature datasets used for bidding, attribution, and ranking systems.



You will work at the intersection of business logic, large\-scale distributed processing, and platform engineering — translating complex and evolving product requirements into scalable, well\-modeled, and reproducible data systems. This role goes beyond analytics enablement; it focuses on building durable, high\-quality </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer - Unity Technologies</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6cd0d0f24117572d</link>
        <description>**The opportunity**  

At Unity, we're building a world\-class advertising platform that operates at a massive global scale. The Ads team powers the systems that connect advertisers with creators and players, driving performance, reliability, and growth across our ecosystem.



As a Data Engineer on the Feature Platform team, you'll play a critical role in building the data foundations that power machine learning, experimentation, and optimization across our ads ecosystem. You'll operate at the core of our ML infrastructure, transforming raw, high\-volume event data into reliable, production\-grade feature datasets used for bidding, attribution, and ranking systems.



You will work at the intersection of business logic, large\-scale distributed processing, and platform engineering — translating complex and evolving product requirements into scalable, well\-modeled, and reproducible data systems. This role goes beyond analytics enablement; it focuses on building durable, high\-quality </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Product Development Engineer - Ampere Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=966199665d7530b9</link>
        <description>**Description**  



  

Invent the future with us.  

  

Ampere is a semiconductor design company for a new era, leading the future of computing with an innovative approach to CPU design focused on high\-performance, energy efficient AI compute.
  

  

As a pioneer in the new frontier of energy efficient high\-performance computing, Ampere is part of the Softbank Group of companies driving sustainable computing for AI, Cloud, and edge applications.  

  

Join us at Ampere and work alongside a passionate and growing team \- we’d love to have you apply!  

  

**About the role:**  

  

The Principal Product Development Engineer will be instrumental in leveraging system to tester data to define SKU binning and developing performance binning models for our products. This role requires a detail\-oriented engineer who can quickly identify root causes and implement corrective actions to enhance product performance and quality. The ideal candidate will have a strong background in data ana</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer, Machine Learning, Google Customer Solutions - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c1941d6bcff541c0</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, a related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience working on data and creating reports, and with database query (e.g., SQL) and visualization tools (e.g., Tableau, dashboards).
* Experience with one or more general purpose programming languages (e.g., Python, C/C\+\+, Java).
* Experience with Artificial Intelligence or Machine Learning Pipelines.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience with TensorFlow, TFX, TorchX, JAX, PyTorch, YDF, Vertex AI or other ML modeling and pipeline technologies.
* Experience with Big Data or scaled/sharded system design.
* Experience with Apache Beam, or Python and SQL.
* Proficiency in machine learning, data analysis, or data science, working knowledge of ML tas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer, Machine Learning, Google Customer Solutions - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6740e0aa5c417dbb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, a related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience working on data and creating reports, and with database query (e.g., SQL) and visualization tools (e.g., Tableau, dashboards).
* Experience with one or more general purpose programming languages (e.g., Python, C/C\+\+, Java).
* Experience with Artificial Intelligence or Machine Learning Pipelines.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience with TensorFlow, TFX, TorchX, JAX, PyTorch, YDF, Vertex AI or other ML modeling and pipeline technologies.
* Experience with Big Data or scaled/sharded system design.
* Experience with Apache Beam, or Python and SQL.
* Proficiency in machine learning, data analysis, or data science, working knowledge of ML tas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Manager, Borglet Machine Learning - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=30daa84520906bb7</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 3 years of experience with developing large\-scale infrastructure, distributed systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage or hardware architecture.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role.
* 2 years of experience in a people management or team leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* Experience with system software, distributed systems, and complex multi\-component software systems.
* Experience in developing and releasing system software products.
* Familiarity with the Linux kernel interface, and containers.
* Understanding of key concepts of performance analysis and tuning with excellent C/C\+\+ programming skills.
* Excellent data analysis and SQL skills.

**About the job**
-----------------


Like Google's own a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Business Data Scientist, Ads Marketing Analytics - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2a7d67ccbdbf6b6</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a relevant PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Statistics or related quantitative discipline.
* 4 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analys</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Business Data Scientist, Ads Marketing Analytics - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3ce24daeaeff408d</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a relevant PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Statistics or related quantitative discipline.
* 4 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analys</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Manager, Ads Personalization, User Modeling Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=54c037913817d125</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 3 years of experience in AI/ML related engineering, developing, deploying, managing, and maintaining machine learning infrastructure.
* 2 years of experience in a people management or team leadership role.
* Experience working in the digital advertising industry.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience building end\-to\-end solutions either in an infrastructure or product\-based team.
* Experience building and testing highly\-scalable distributed systems or low\-latency/streaming batch systems.
* Experience collaborating with cross\-functional teams in a global organization and managing stakeholders.
* Ability to take full ownership and execute highly\-visible projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


Like Google's own ambitions, the work of a Software Engineer goes beyond just Sea</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Group Product Manager, AI Personalization, Data Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2f5482de3e4b77a6</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience as a Product Manager in the data or AI/ML domain.
* 5 years of experience in people management, with technical leadership.
* 5 years of experience taking technical products from conception to launch (e.g., ideation to execution, end\-to\-end, 0 to 1, etc).
* Experience developing and scaling data management infrastructure products at a global level.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or a business related field.
* Experience in building back\-end systems, with the knowledge of the infrastructure to power Generative AI (Gen AI) and agentic experiences.
* Experience supporting the Machine Learning development lifecycle, particularly regarding Retrieval\-Augmented Generation (RAG) or personalization models.
* Knowledge of data management best practices where privacy and consent are paramount.
* Ability to conduct market research and parti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, YouTube Shorts, Viewer Feed Quality - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7acfcca82f4cff33</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or equivalent practical experience.
* 15 years of experience in engineering.
* Experience with cross\-functional technical innovation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 7 years of experience in a technical leadership role responsible for multiple technical areas and setting technical direction.
* Ability to manage multiple complex assignments simultaneously and to work with geographically dispersed, cross\-functional teams.
* Deep expertise in large\-scale recommendation systems (Retrieval/Ranking), Generative AI for content understanding, and machine learning Infrastructure.

**About the job**
-----------------


The Viewer Growth team within the Shorts Discovery organization aims at bringing step\-changes in the viewer Shorts recommendations through improved understanding of users’ interests, preferences \&amp; behavior patterns, and leveraging advanced AI/ML technology.
  

  

In this Princip</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Developer Technology Intern, High-Performance Databases - Summer 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ef37ae83835c672f</link>
        <description>Our work at NVIDIA is dedicated towards a computing model focused on visual and AI computing. For two decades, NVIDIA has pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics, with our invention of the GPU. The GPU has also shown to be spectacularly effective at solving some of the most complex problems in computer science. Today, NVIDIA’s GPU simulates human intelligence, running deep learning algorithms and acting as the brain of computers, robots and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. We are looking to grow our company and teams with the smartest people in the world and there has never been a more exciting time to join our team!
NVIDIA is hiring passionate, extraordinary interns to work in its Developer Technology (DevTech) team. Artificial intelligence, the dream of computer scientists for over half a century, is no longer science fiction. And in the next few years, it will transform every industry. As high\-performance accelerators conti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Developer Technology Intern, AI - Summer 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a5c709a8675e35c</link>
        <description>Our work at NVIDIA is dedicated towards a computing model focused on visual and AI computing. For two decades, NVIDIA has pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics, with our invention of the GPU. The GPU has also shown to be spectacularly effective at solving some of the most complex problems in computer science. Today, NVIDIA’s GPU simulates human intelligence, running deep learning algorithms and acting as the brain of computers, robots and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. We are looking to grow our company and teams with the smartest people in the world and there has never been a more exciting time to join our team!
Developer Technology team at NVIDIA plays a pivotal role in extracting maximum performance from our computing platform which enables researchers to develop and productize these state\-of\-the\-art technologies. Do you share our passion for Artificial Intelligence? Come join a team full of outstanding engineers to w</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Fullstack Engineer - Cargomatic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5ce602fc17eef5ff</link>
        <description>Join a rapidly growing company disrupting the trucking industry! Cargomatic is the \#1 technology platform and digital marketplace powering world\-class local trucking. Take a look around you. Literally everything humans build, grow, or sell has spent time on a truck. Local trucking is the lifeblood of every regional economy, yet this $82 billion industry still relies heavily on phone calls and fax machines. Cargomatic is transforming the way goods move through every local node in the supply chain by connecting shippers and commercial truck drivers with powerful mobile and web\-based technology. We are solving complex, real\-world problems every day and bringing transparency and efficiency to the shipping process.


**Senior Full Stack Engineer – React / Node / Go / AWS / MongoDB**



Cargomatic is seeking a Senior Full Stack Engineer who is passionate about building highly scalable, event\-driven systems for a real\-time logistics marketplace. This role will play a critical part in de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer - Cathexis</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ac3cc50fb4458aec</link>
        <description>Team CATHEXIS elevates the government contracting experience through rapid response, deep skill, and thoughtful problem\-solving and communication. Our core capabilities are our top\-tier program and project management, data analytics, and audit services, the backbone of which is our integrated approach to operational excellence.


You worked hard to get to where you are. You strive to make every day better than the day before. So do we. Team CATHEXIS operates with an all\-in mindset. We are working together to create a company that supports our shared values and individual goals. Our values are centered around Respect, Engagement, Customer Service, Integrity, Teamwork, and Excellence in everything we do for our employees, clients, partners, and communities. We believe success is best when we listen and lead with empathy; model high standards of ethics to provide a rewarding candidate experience; work hard, have fun, and appreciate the strengths we all bring to the team; and empower ou</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ML Platform Engineer - Afresh</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ebfe5376f2d39b14</link>
        <description>Afresh is the leading AI company in fresh food—partnering with grocers like Albertsons, Wakefern, Meijer, and Stater Bros to order billions of dollars of fresh food in over 12,000 grocery departments nationwide.



Following record\-breaking 70% growth in 2025, we've expanded our platform to cover all fresh departments, launched our full store suite, and debuted DC Fresh Buying.



We're on a mission to eliminate food waste and make fresh food accessible to all. In 2025 alone our software helped save 200M lbs of food waste. If you're looking for a role where your work directly translates into massive scale and social good, and you want to be part of the team that defines the future of fresh, there is no better time to join us.


The **ML Platform Engineering team** at Afresh is responsible for building and maintaining the foundational infrastructure and tooling that powers all of our machine learning and applied science solutions. We provide the shared components and services that enab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Shield - Box</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=88492e295288a867</link>
        <description>**WHAT IS BOX?**



Box (NYSE:BOX) is the leader in Intelligent Content Management. Our platform enables organizations to fuel collaboration, manage the entire content lifecycle, secure critical content, and transform business workflows with enterprise AI. We help companies thrive in the new AI\-first era of business. Founded in 2005, Box simplifies work for leading global organizations, including JLL, Morgan Stanley, and Nationwide. Box is headquartered in Redwood City, CA, with offices across the United States, Europe, and Asia.



By joining Box, you will have the unique opportunity to continue driving our platform forward. Content powers how we work. It's the billions of files and information flowing across teams, departments, and key business processes every single day: contracts, invoices, employee records, financials, product specs, marketing assets, and more. Our mission is to bring intelligence to the world of content management and empower our customers to completely transfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Reinforcement Learning - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=013d92448b2ca44d</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
------------------



Come help us build the world's most reliable local e\-commerce platform for on\-demand last\-mile grocery and retail delivery! We're looking for an experienced senior machine learning engineer to help us develop the cutting\-edge reinforcement learning models that power DoorDash's growing grocery and retail business.


**About the Role**
------------------



We're looking for a passionate Applied Machine Learning expert to join our team. As a Reinforcement Learning expert, you'll be conceptualizing, designing, implementing, and validating algorithmic improvements to the reinforcement learning system at the heart of our fast\-growing grocery and retail delivery business. You will use our robust data and machine learning infrastructure to implement new ML solutions to make our product selection and inventory information more accurate and real time, as well as help Dasher efficiency. We're looking for someone with a command of production\-level ma</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director of Engineering – Machine Learning &amp; AI Products - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8ca7bad71ea2527e</link>
        <description>The Opportunity
  
We are looking for a Director of Engineering to guide the development of AI\-native, production\-ready machine learning products for external clients. This leader will be responsible for the entire lifecycle of sophisticated AI systems—from product conception and rollout to production, customer engagement, and continuous operational success.
  
This role requires a rare blend of hands‑on technical depth, product judgment, and senior‑level people leadership. You will lead a highly experienced ML engineering organization and work closely with Product, Development, and Go‑to‑Market partners to bring differentiated AI solutions to market.
  
Key Responsibilities
  
Technical \&amp; Product Leadership
  
Own the end‑to‑end delivery of AI/ML solutions deployed in production, moving beyond proofs‑of‑concept to scalable, reliable, customer‑facing systems.
  
Lead deep technical discussions on system build, model integration, performance, reliability, and operational readiness.
 </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=60720148c44c7f1d</link>
        <description>Job Description
  
We are seeking a Senior ML Engineer to join our team of dedicated machine learning and software engineers. This role involves timely engineering, system development, ML model assessment, constructing data pipelines, composing prototypes, evaluation, operationalization.
  
  

Looking for individuals skilled in classical and deep learning, able to build and implement ML solutions for production environments. If you thrive on delivering innovative customer features, adopting new technologies, and contributing to high\-visibility projects, this role may be a good match. The atmosphere is dynamic, fast\-paced, creative, collaborative, and data\-centric.
  
What you’ll do
  
  

Contribute to the backend services supporting ML and Generative\-AI functionalities.
  
  

Build, develop, implement, and evaluate machine learning models using classical and deep learning approaches, as well as GenAI.
  
  

Collaborate with cross\-functional teams to integrate ML solutions into</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Server Engineer, Find My - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d1085ff214fe5435</link>
        <description>The Find My team is dedicated to building a seamless, private, and secure experience for users to locate their devices, personal items, and share location with friends and family. We're a group of highly motivated engineers, designers, and product managers who are passionate about creating a simple and reliable experience for hundreds of millions of users worldwide. We thrive in a fast paced environment where team members are often encouraged to wear multiple hats and contribute to various aspects of the product lifecycle. Innovation and creative problem\-solving are at the heart of our team, and we constantly explore new approaches to deliver groundbreaking solutions while collaborating with diverse disciplines across the company, including hardware, software, and privacy, to deliver an exceptional user experience.  

  

**Description**  

  

As an engineer on our team, you'll thrive in a fast\-paced, startup\-like environment, collaborating closely with a passionate team to achieve</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sensing ML Algorithm Engineer - HID - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d79d2420c3dd4e30</link>
        <description>Join the engineering team creating next\-generation touch interfaces for iPad, Pencil, iPhone, Watch and more. We are an eclectic group with backgrounds in signal processing, machine learning, computer science, estimation algorithms, human factors, and more, dedicated to inventing new ways of interacting with Apple products and shipping amazing products every year.  

  

We are looking for a signal processing and machine learning engineer with C/C\+\+ implementation skill. Your good communication skills, and ability to drive discussions with cross\-functional teams would come in very handy. Have you gained any experience with user interface design or graphics programming skills as well? That’s great! It will further help broaden your role and effectiveness in this position.  

  

To summarize, you will be working on innovative projects and will be responsible for productizing algorithmic solutions, and you will be part of the team shipping products to millions of users every year.  
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Siri NL Platform Software Engineer, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=aaf61e30970b2f68</link>
        <description>The Siri NL Platform team bridges ML research and user\-facing experiences, integrating large language models into Siri across all Apple devices. We partner with modeling teams, hardware teams, and leadership to shape what Siri can become.  

  

**Description**  

  

We're looking for a software engineer to work on Siri's on\-device runtime across iOS, macOS, tvOS, watchOS, and visionOS. You'll build performant client software under tight constraints, work across teams throughout Apple, and help guide technical decisions that reach millions of users.","responsibilities":"Design, develop, test, and maintain Siri's on\-device runtime platform across Apple's operating systems  

  

Integrate large language models into client experiences with a focus on performance and efficiency  

  

Collaborate with modeling teams to ensure successful LLM integration on\-device  

  

Partner with hardware teams to bring new Siri experiences to new product lines  

  

Work cross\-functionally with </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer - Automation &amp; Infrastructure - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2031115f8485ff9e</link>
        <description>Apple’s Video Engineering group build the systems that ensure every next\-generation product meets the highest bar for quality, reliability, and performance. Our team operates at the intersection of hardware, software, and machine learning\-creating the infrastructure that powers breakthrough technologies. We thrive on curiosity, precision, and bold problem\-solving, and we take pride in transforming complex engineering challenges into elegant, scalable solutions.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a Software Engineer \- Automation \&amp; Infrastructure, you will design, develop, and maintain scalable automation frameworks and robotic systems that enable high\-quality testing of computer vision (CV) algorithms and next\-generation products. You will work at the intersection of software, robotics, and test engineering to build reliable infrastructure that accelerates product development.  

  

In this role, your day\-to\-day work will blend coding, system integration, cross\-team collaborati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Siri NL Platform Software Engineer, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=581877860233e146</link>
        <description>The Siri NL Platform team bridges ML research and user\-facing experiences, integrating large language models into Siri across all Apple devices. We partner with modeling teams, hardware teams, and leadership to shape what Siri can become.  

  

**Description**  

  

We're looking for a software engineer to work on Siri's on\-device runtime across iOS, macOS, tvOS, watchOS, and visionOS. You'll build performant client software under tight constraints, work across teams throughout Apple, and help guide technical decisions that reach millions of users.","responsibilities":"Design, develop, test, and maintain Siri's on\-device runtime platform across Apple's operating systems  

  

Integrate large language models into client experiences with a focus on performance and efficiency  

  

Collaborate with modeling teams to ensure successful LLM integration on\-device  

  

Partner with hardware teams to bring new Siri experiences to new product lines  

  

Work cross\-functionally with </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>On-device ML Integration Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=058073840b8d0f73</link>
        <description>Imagine being at the forefront of an evolution where cutting\-edge AI meets the elegance of Apple silicon. The On\-Device Machine Learning team transforms groundbreaking research into practical applications, enabling billions of Apple devices to run powerful AI models locally, privately, and efficiently. We stand at the unique intersection of research, software engineering, hardware engineering, and product development, making Apple the leading destination for machine learning innovation.  

  

Our team builds the essential infrastructure that enables machine learning at scale on Apple devices. This involves onboarding cutting\-edge architectures to embedded systems, developing optimization toolkits for model compression and acceleration, building ML compilers and runtimes for efficient execution, and creating comprehensive benchmarking and debugging toolchains. This infrastructure forms the backbone of Apple’s machine learning workflows across Camera, Siri, Health, Vision, and other </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Apple Intelligence Model Platform - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4a700010b333b5e8</link>
        <description>The Proactive Intelligence Platform is at the heart of an intelligent system experience that understands you and anticipates your needs. We are building an on\-device personal and contextual intelligence platform that will benefit the millions of people who use Apple devices every day. Our team is comprised of Systems engineers and ML engineers focused on seamlessly integrating intelligence into all Apple products. Our team is responsible for developing exciting new features across all Apple platforms \- iOS, macOS, watchOS, tvOS, visionOS, and Private Cloud Compute. You should have a strong understanding of operating system fundamentals and experience working throughout the stack. As a member of the team, you would participate in all stages of software development, from new feature design and implementation, to maintenance and bug fixing of released code. You will develop and improve unit tests, performance tests, and diagnose and resolve customer reported issues. Your ideas will powe</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Systems Software Developer, Apple Vision Products - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=892defd3633de054</link>
        <description>The Vision Products Group is seeking an exceptional software engineer to design, develop, and integrate systems software across high\-performance, energy\-efficient systems that power our next\-generation intelligent vision products.  

  

In this highly collaborative role, you will be at the forefront of efforts to influence hardware design, utilize existing hardware, including machine learning accelerators, diverse software and operating systems powering different processor flavors. You will be part of a team responsible for designing, building, and maintaining systems software such as kernel drivers, runtime libraries, frameworks, software running on low\-power embedded cores, and daemons that power novel vision products with a focus on performance, power efficiency, security, privacy, and machine intelligence.  

  

We are looking for a motivated systems software engineer with a genuine passion for solving complex and challenging systems software problems that possesses strong an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Staff Machine Learning Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=29948ca580d32a2c</link>
        <description>Join a team at the forefront of ML infrastructure and generative AI, where data and model workflows come together to enable the next generation of intelligent experiences on Apple products and services. We focus on building robust systems that connect scalable data pipelines with advanced ML workflows to accelerate the development of real\-world AI applications.  

  

**Description**  

  

The ADP ML Data Platform team enables future Apple intelligent products by providing Apple engineers with cutting edge ML technologies, large scale compute and data systems specifically designed for machine learning.  

  

You will build the data foundation that powers ML training across Apple. Our team enables governed, scalable sharing of text and multimodal datasets, ensuring teams can safely discover, access, and use high\-quality data for training.  

  

We focus on turning raw data into usable training assets with streamlining data preparation, enabling rapid iteration, and supporting advan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=71572c5f6ccbf091</link>
        <description>The Siri team is creating groundbreaking technology for large scale systems, spoken language, machine learning, and LLMs to enable better conversational experience with Siri. The features we create are redefining how hundreds of millions of people use their computers and mobile devices to fulfill their requirements and find what they are looking for. As part of the Siri team, you will work with the talent dense team who crafted the intelligent assistant that helps users get things done \- just by asking.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a machine learning engineer at Siri, you will be responsible for doing development and research in the deep learning field and building the most advanced natural language and conversation understanding systems. You should be passionate about working with software and platform engineers to integrate the models on\-device and improve natural language understanding ability of Siri. Excellent interpersonal skills will be required to coordinate work across m</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Research Engineer, Siri Comprehension &amp; Planning, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7c8cc35aa64f7018</link>
        <description>The future of AI is on\-device. On the Siri team, we're solving the defining challenge: building and shipping powerful, LLMs that run with extreme efficiency across hundreds of millions of iPhones, Watches, and Macs. You will own the full ML stack, from data to deployment, bridging the gap between bleeding\-edge research and product\-critical models. This is where the hardest problems in applied ML are being solved.  

  

**Description**  

  

The frontier of AI isn't in the cloud anymore. It's in your pocket. The real challenge is building models that are not only powerful but also private, efficient, and intelligent enough to act as a true assistant on a user's device.  

  

At Apple's Siri team, this isn't a research paper\-it's our daily work. We are building the next generation of LLMs and deploying them at the largest customer scale in the world. We're looking for engineers who thrive on solving the puzzles that exist at the bleeding edge of hardware, software, and machine lea</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Backend/Data Engineer: Agentic Workflows, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5acacc4e6b5650a1</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there’s no telling what you could accomplish.  

  

Do you want to make Siri and Apple products more intelligent for our users? The Siri \&amp; Information Intelligence team is building groundbreaking technology to revolutionize how users interact with Apple devices.  

  

As part of this group, you will contribute to build the infrastructure to power the development of multi\-modal agentic workflows.  

  

**Description**  

  

We design, build and maintain infrastructure to support agentic workflows for Siri. Our team is in charge of data generation, introspection and evaluation frameworks that are key to efficiently developing foundation models and agentic workflows for Siri applications. In this team you will have the opportunity to work at the intersection of with cutting edge foundation models an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Backend/Data Engineer: Agentic Workflows, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9bd2215e3360dc3b</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there’s no telling what you could accomplish.  

  

Do you want to make Siri and Apple products more intelligent for our users? The Siri \&amp; Information Intelligence team is building groundbreaking technology to revolutionize how users interact with Apple devices.  

  

As part of this group, you will contribute to build the infrastructure to power the development of multi\-modal agentic workflows.  

  

**Description**  

  

We design, build and maintain infrastructure to support agentic workflows for Siri. Our team is in charge of data generation, introspection and evaluation frameworks that are key to efficiently developing foundation models and agentic workflows for Siri applications. In this team you will have the opportunity to work at the intersection of with cutting edge foundation models an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Manager, Ads Quality - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0b9ba3cd5ca07111</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
------------------



The mission of the Ads Quality team is to show the most relevant ads and promotions to our users across all our verticals, ad formats for both search (query context) and discovery experiences. This team owns the full lifecycle of the ads delivery funnel—from large\-scale retrieval to deep\-learning\-based ranking.



We're looking for an Engineering Manager with hands\-on experience in modern machine learning and recommendation systems to lead a team that develops advanced machine learning models to show the most engaging and relevant promoted content to the users.



Ads Quality is a critical part of the Ads Delivery funnel with deep personalization playing a central role.


**About the Role**
------------------


* Manage a growing team of ML and backend engineers
* Continue to build a team that can support end\-to\-end execution of ranking, retrieval, GenAI initiatives for deeply personalized promoted content.
* Support a culture of analytica</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Worldwide Specialist Solutions Architect - GenAI, Data &amp; AI GTM - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c156b1135c21c6e5</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you passionate about Generative AI (GenAI)? Do you want to help define the future of Go to Market (GTM) at AWS using generative AI? In this role, you will help some of our largest customers build and deploy GenAI enabled applications using Amazon Bedrock and SageMaker, fine tune and build Generative AI models, and help enterprise customers leverage these models to power end applications. You will engage with AWS product owners to influence product direction and help our customers tap into new markets by utilizing GenAI along with AWS Services.  

  

At Amazon, we’ve been investing deeply in artificial intelligence for over 20 years, and many of the capabilities customers experience in our products are driven by machine learning. Amazon.com’s recommendations engine is driven by machine learning (ML), as are the paths that optimize robotic picking routes in our fulfillment centers. Our supply chain, forecasting, and capacity planning are also inform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Worldwide Specialist Solutions Architect - GenAI, Data &amp; AI GTM - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=117e89c6be81fa83</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you passionate about Generative AI (GenAI)? Do you want to help define the future of Go to Market (GTM) at AWS using generative AI? In this role, you will help some of our largest customers build and deploy GenAI enabled applications using Amazon Bedrock and SageMaker, fine tune and build Generative AI models, and help enterprise customers leverage these models to power end applications. You will engage with AWS product owners to influence product direction and help our customers tap into new markets by utilizing GenAI along with AWS Services.  

  

At Amazon, we’ve been investing deeply in artificial intelligence for over 20 years, and many of the capabilities customers experience in our products are driven by machine learning. Amazon.com’s recommendations engine is driven by machine learning (ML), as are the paths that optimize robotic picking routes in our fulfillment centers. Our supply chain, forecasting, and capacity planning are also inform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Scientific Lead - Forward Deployed AI Engineer, Applied Intelligence for Discovery - Eli Lilly</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3febd775780f1670</link>
        <description>At Lilly, we unite caring with discovery to make life better for people around the world. We are a global healthcare leader headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana. Our employees around the world work to discover and bring life\-changing medicines to those who need them, improve the understanding and management of disease, and give back to our communities through philanthropy and volunteerism. We give our best effort to our work, and we put people first. We’re looking for people who are determined to make life better for people around the world.

**The Opportunity**


We are building something unprecedented — an AI foundation that will push the frontier on what is possible today across drug discovery research, from target identification and disease biology through translational science.


The Applied Intelligence for Discovery (AI4D) team is a newly formed group within Lilly Research Laboratories that operates at the intersection of scientific delivery and core platform development. AI4</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Scientific Lead, Applied Intelligence for Discovery - Eli Lilly</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5c16e06c2d5aa993</link>
        <description>At Lilly, we unite caring with discovery to make life better for people around the world. We are a global healthcare leader headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana. Our employees around the world work to discover and bring life\-changing medicines to those who need them, improve the understanding and management of disease, and give back to our communities through philanthropy and volunteerism. We give our best effort to our work, and we put people first. We’re looking for people who are determined to make life better for people around the world.


The Opportunity


We are building something unprecedented, an AI foundation that will fundamentally change how drug discovery research is conducted.


The Applied Intelligence for Discovery (AI4D) team is a newly formed group within Lilly Research Laboratories that operates at the intersection of scientific delivery and core platform development. AI4D’s mission is to connecting scientists to petabyte\-scale data through natural language interf</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist II - Avathon</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2b79f4ac6055475e</link>
        <description>**Who We Are \&amp; Why Join Us**


**Avathon** is revolutionizing industrial AI with a powerful platform that enables businesses to harness the full potential of their operational data. Our technology seamlessly integrates and contextualizes siloed datasets, providing a 360\-degree operational view that enhances decision\-making and efficiency. With advanced capabilities like digital twins, natural language processing, normal behavior modeling, and machine vision, we create real\-time virtual replicas of physical assets, enabling predictive maintenance, performance simulation, and operational optimization. Our AI\-driven models empower companies with scalable solutions for anomaly detection, performance forecasting, and asset lifetime extension—all tailored to the complexities of industrial environments.



**Cutting\-Edge AI Innovation** – Join a team at the forefront of AI, developing groundbreaking solutions that shape the future.  

**High\-Growth Environment** – Thrive in a fast\-sca</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist I - Avathon</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81f56a55e57fefe0</link>
        <description>**Who We Are \&amp; Why Join Us**


**Avathon** is revolutionizing industrial AI with a powerful platform that enables businesses to harness the full potential of their operational data. Our technology seamlessly integrates and contextualizes siloed datasets, providing a 360\-degree operational view that enhances decision\-making and efficiency. With advanced capabilities like digital twins, natural language processing, normal behavior modeling, and machine vision, we create real\-time virtual replicas of physical assets, enabling predictive maintenance, performance simulation, and operational optimization. Our AI\-driven models empower companies with scalable solutions for anomaly detection, performance forecasting, and asset lifetime extension—all tailored to the complexities of industrial environments.



**Cutting\-Edge AI Innovation** – Join a team at the forefront of AI, developing groundbreaking solutions that shape the future.  

**High\-Growth Environment** – Thrive in a fast\-sca</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Director, Head of Clinical Statistical Programming - Jazz Pharmaceuticals</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4da42b6503465781</link>
        <description>**If you are a current Jazz employee please apply via the Internal Career site.**



Jazz Pharmaceuticals is a global biopharma company whose purpose is to innovate to transform the lives of patients and their families. We are dedicated to developing life\-changing medicines for people with serious diseases — often with limited or no therapeutic options. We have a diverse portfolio of marketed medicines, including leading therapies for sleep disorders and epilepsy, and a growing portfolio of cancer treatments. Our patient\-focused and science\-driven approach powers pioneering research and development advancements across our robust pipeline of innovative therapeutics in oncology and neuroscience. Jazz is headquartered in Dublin, Ireland with research and development laboratories, manufacturing facilities and employees in multiple countries committed to serving patients worldwide. Please visit www.jazzpharmaceuticals.com for more information.


The Senior Director, Head of Clinical Stat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist - Payment - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=372a5aa10d953557</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
Overall Purpose  

  

This position is a senior technical role within Data Sciences. This role assumes analytic project ownership, starting from conceptualization and design. Oversees the process of development, implementation and enhancement of the analytically derived models</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Spatial Data Analyst - Temporary - Northeastern University</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c15a5b993c04c378</link>
        <description>**About the Opportunity**

**Job Summary**
===============

Conduct spatial analysis and statistical modeling to evaluate cannabis cultivation density patterns across tribal, private, and boundary lands. Develop refined sampling grids, analyze temporal trends, and produce visualizations and reports to support cannabis remediation research on tribal lands.


**Minimum Qualifications**
==========================

* ### **Knowledge of spatial statistics, GIS analysis, and statistical modeling using R.**
* ### **Ability to integrate and analyze complex environmental datasets; as normally acquired through a Master's degree in Geography, Environmental Science, Statistics, or related field**
* ### **2\-3 years of relevant experience.**

**Key Responsibilities**
========================

* Refine sampling grid methodology and develop statewide grids that improve land\-type resolution while maintaining privacy requirements. Conduct spatial distribution analysis of tribal and private lands and v</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Product Analytics - Gallup</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c4d58f6128c6ddc6</link>
        <description>**Shape product road maps and strategies with data\-driven analytics and insights.**



As a senior/principal data scientist focused on product analytics for our Technology team, you'll work with product managers, engineers and designers to define success, validate hypotheses, and measure user behavior and product performance.



We're looking for self\-driven, curious analytics partners who thrive in ambiguity, learn continually and help teams accelerate decision\-making.



At Gallup, our analytics reflect what the world is thinking, empower millions of people to thrive using their strengths, and help leaders create exceptional workplaces. If you want your work to influence products that bring that mission to life, we'd love to hear from you.


**What You'll Do**


* Partner with product teams early in discovery, road map discussions and launch planning to turn goals into measurable outcomes
* Define and govern success metrics by building trusted metric definitions, dashboards and da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Maps Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3aa1994b2bca8bde</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in C\+\+ and SQL.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* Experience with Deep Learning.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or a related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience with Python.
* Experience with ML model fine\-tuning, evaluation, and performance optimization for user\-facing systems.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of user</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Preparedness - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2a0d07656da4ae30</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

The Preparedness team is an important part of the
  
  

Safety Systems
  
  

org at OpenAI, and is guided by OpenAI’s
  
  

Preparedness Framework
  
  

.
  
  

Frontier AI models have the potential to benefit all of humanity, but also pose increasingly severe risks. To ensure that AI promotes positive change, the Preparedness team helps us prepare for the development of increasingly capable frontier AI models. This team is tasked with identifying, tracking, and preparing for catastrophic risks related to frontier AI models.
  
  

**The mission of the Preparedness team is to:**  

Closely monitor and predict the evolving capabilities of frontier AI systems, with an eye towards misuse risks whose impact could be catastrophic to our society
  
  

Ensure we have concrete procedures, infrastructure and partnerships to mitigate these risks and to safely handle the development of powerful AI systems
  
  

Preparedness tightly connects capability assessment, eval</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df0d976afd057a4</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California; San Diego, California; San Francisco, California **Job ID** 19894
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across discipline</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Developer, Machine Learning - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0f1e9cbbaa334324</link>
        <description>This posting is for a new vacancy.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Waterloo, ON, Canada**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in software development using one or more programming languages.
* Experience in one or more of the following: video compression, video processing, video encoding, or video decoding.
* 2 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools, building production quality Machine Learning (ML) systems and infrastructure.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience with image processing, computer vision, or machine learning applications.
* Experience in one or more of the following: video compression, video processing, signal/image pro</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Search Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f62798825ba5e785</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Cambridge, MA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 3 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 6 years of work experience with a PhD degree.
* Experience articulating business questions and using mathematical techniques to arrive at an answer using available data.
* Experience translating analysis results into business recommendati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineering NERD, AI.x - Charles Schwab</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3b5b02de118510ad</link>
        <description>**Your opportunity**
--------------------

  

At Schwab, you will build a rewarding career while making a difference in the lives of our millions of clients. Here, innovative thinking meets creative problem solving as we work together to challenge the status quo. We believe in the power of collaboration and value being together in the office, which is why this role is based on\-site in our San Francisco office. Joining Schwab means joining a company committed to transforming the financial industry and putting clients at the center of everything we do.  

Schwab’s AI Strategy \&amp; Transformation team, known as AI.x, is the central hub for Artificial Intelligence at Schwab. We are an integrated product, engineering, strategy and risk team, all based in San Francisco. We help set the enterprise vision for AI, invest in the most promising opportunities, and accelerate delivery across the company. We also build the core platform that powers AI at scale and explore next\-generation GenAI effo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Satff Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df7d07727627e4e</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refine innovative growth strategies. Your expertise—especially in causal inference and advanced analytics—will be instrumental in surfacing critical insights and translating them into actionable hypotheses that fuel sustained customer and revenue growth.

 **Responsibilities**


* Drive Business Strategy through Data \- Translate business problems into analytical frameworks. Connect data across multiple function</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>CCB Risk program Senior Associate - JPMorganChase</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3a3339cce49ccc7b</link>
        <description>**JOB DESCRIPTION**  

Come and join us in reshaping the future!


As a Risk program Senior Associate within the Chase consumer Bank, you'll be the analytical expert for identifying and retooling suitable machine learning algorithms that can enhance the fraud risk ranking of particular transactions and/or applications for new products. This includes a balance of feature engineering, feature selection, and developing and training machine learning algorithms using cutting edge technology to extract predictive models/patterns from data gathered for billions of transactions. Your expertise and insights will help us effectively utilize big data platforms, data assets, and analytical capabilities to control fraud loss and improve customer experience.

**Job Responsibilities:**

* Identify and retool machine learning (ML) algorithms to analyze datasets for fraud detection in the Chase Consumer Bank.
* Perform machine learning tasks such as feature engineering, feature selection, and developin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1eb0d19c64b72edd</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Staff Engineer is a lead member of the engineerin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3742eddcc5e71f7a</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Senior Staff Engineer is a lead member of the eng</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e924304b2daed071</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Senior Engineer is a leading member of the engine</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Engineer I - BillionToOne</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ab7e4e62ffd83084</link>
        <description>**Ready to redefine what's possible in molecular diagnostics?**
---------------------------------------------------------------



Join a team of brilliant, passionate innovators who wake up every day determined to transform healthcare. At BillionToOne, we've built something extraordinary—a culture where transparency fuels trust, collaboration drives breakthroughs, and every voice matters in our mission to make life\-changing diagnostics accessible to all. We don't just aim for incremental improvements; we strive to build products that are 10x better than anything that exists today. Our people are our greatest asset:talented scientists, engineers, sales professionals, and visionaries united by an unwavering commitment to changing the standard of care in prenatal and cancer diagnostics. This is where cutting\-edge science meets human compassion—every innovation you contribute helps remove fear of unknown from some of life's most critical medical moments. **If you're driven by purpose, e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior, Data Scientist (Personalization) - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=48789add1d9755e1</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------


***Immigration sponsorship is not available for this role. Applicants must******be authorized to******work for any employer in the United States without current or future visa sponsorship.***

Walmart Global Tech is looking to hire a seasoned Senior Data Scientist for their Personalization team in Sunnyvale, CA to support the Personalization and Recommendation development efforts with our eCommerce team.  

  

**About the Team:**
The Personalization team consists of platform, application engineers, scientists and product visionaries all working together to design, prototype and build technology\-driven products and experiences that will change the future landscape of ecommerce. We are focused on building end\-to\-end customer experience, from finding the product to delivering it to the customer. This will span many markets, business models and form factors; therefore, we are looking for data</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Computer Vision - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f873a17a79fe7304</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
==================



Come help us build the world's most reliable on\-demand, logistics engine for last\-mile grocery and retail delivery! We're looking for an experienced senior machine learning engineer to help us develop the cutting\-edge Computer Vision models that power DoorDash's growing grocery and retail business.


**About the Role**
==================



We're looking for a passionate Applied Machine Learning expert to join our team. As a Computer Vision expert, you'll be conceptualizing, designing, implementing, and validating algorithmic improvements to the computer vision system at the heart of our fast\-growing grocery and retail delivery business. You will use our robust data and machine learning infrastructure to implement new ML solutions to make our product knowledge graph and inventory information more accurate and real time, as well as help Dasher efficiency. We're looking for someone with a command of production\-level machine learning and exper</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Lead AI Engineer - Capital One</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=456d0f19df5de27e</link>
        <description>Senior Lead AI Engineer**Overview:**


At Capital One, we are creating responsible and reliable AI systems, changing banking for good. For years, Capital One has been an industry leader in using machine learning to create real\-time, personalized customer experiences. Our investments in technology infrastructure and world\-class talent — along with our deep experience in machine learning — position us to be at the forefront of enterprises leveraging AI. From informing customers about unusual charges to answering their questions in real time, our applications of AI \&amp; ML are bringing humanity and simplicity to banking. We are committed to continuing to build world\-class applied science and engineering teams to deliver our industry leading capabilities with breakthrough product experiences and scalable, high\-performance AI infrastructure. At Capital One, you will help bring the transformative power of emerging AI capabilities to reimagine how we serve our customers and businesses who h</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Experienced Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd02371cc6e6817c</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Driven by curiosity, you are a reliable, contributing member of a team. In our fast\-paced environment, you are expected to adapt to working with a variety o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Experienced Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=68db4a7fee83b003</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Driven by curiosity, you are a reliable, contributing member of a team. In our fast\-paced environment, you are expected to adapt to working with a variety o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Research Data Analyst, Deportation Data Project (5274C), Berkeley Law - 84426 - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a016b57b2f13ad65</link>
        <description>Senior Research Data Analyst, Deportation Data Project (5274C), Berkeley Law \- 84426 About Berkeley
  
  

At the University of California, Berkeley, we are dedicated to fostering a community where everyone feels welcome and can thrive. Our culture of openness, freedom and belonging make it a special place for students, faculty and staff.
  
  

As a world\-leading institution, Berkeley is known for its academic and research excellence, public mission, diverse student body, and commitment to equity and social justice. Since our founding in 1868, we have driven innovation, creating global intellectual, economic and social value.
  
  

We are looking for applicants who reflect California's diversity and want to be part of an inclusive, equity\-focused community that views education as a matter of social justice. Please consider whether your values align with our Guiding Values and Principles , Principles of Community , and Strategic Plan .
  
  

At UC Berkeley, we believe that learnin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Assistant/Associate/Full Project Scientist - Machine Learning &amp; Data Analytics Advanced Bioimaging Center Department of Molecular and Cell Biology - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dba0365e43fa8a4f</link>
        <description>**Position overview Position title:** Project Scientist
  
**Salary range:** The UC academic salary scales set the minimum pay determined by rank and step at appointment. See the following table for the current salary scale for this position: https://www.ucop.edu/academic\-personnel\-programs/\_files/2025\-26/represented\-july\-2025\-scales/t37\-b.pdf . A reasonable estimate for this position is $181,700 \- $229,700\.
  
  

**Percent time:** 100%
  
  

**Anticipated start:** Winter/Spring 2026
  
  

**Position duration:** Initial appointment is for one year with the possibility of renewal based on performance and funding availability.
  
  

Application Window
  
**Open date:** February 25, 2026
  
  

**Next review date:** Wednesday, Mar 11, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Apply by this date to ensure full consideration by the committee.
  
  

**Final date:** Friday, Mar 27, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Applications will continue to be accepted until this date, but those re</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Science Manager - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=40166b7351317d3e</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Science Manager - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=95d474789ef56e02</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Machine Learning Engineer - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2a588910b3c90edf</link>
        <description>Adobe Firefly’s Generative AI Services team is seeking Senior Machine Learning Engineers for our GenAI Services area. In this high\-impact role, you will work with a team of talented engineers in building scalable, high\-performance generative AI systems—powering features across Adobe products like Firefly, Photoshop, Illustrator, Express, Stock, and Premiere. You will design and develop efficient inference pipelines, optimize models for latency and through at inference, and build APIs and ecosystems that integrate both Adobe’s first\-party and third\-party generative models into Adobe suite of products that serve individual and enterprise customers. You will tackle Adobe’s most complex engineering challenges at the forefront of the the industry, set technical direction, and mentor other ML engineers. Job Responsibilities
  
  

Design and evelopment of core GenAI services and APIs that integrate a wide range of generative models into Adobe’s flagship products.
  
  

Design and build </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Data Scientist - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a47372d5ad18a5fe</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Lead Data Scientist who thinks in systems, understands B2C business problems deeply, and can build the models and analyses that power real growth outcomes for the world's largest consumer companies — all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "build models in isolation and hand off a notebook" role. You'll own the entire data science function — from problem framing through model development through business impact — and you'll do it for enterprise customers where the stakes are real and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist / ML Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbeb93fbc7e35bb4</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Data Scientist who understands B2C business problems deeply, builds models that work with real\-world data, and delivers analyses that drive real growth outcomes — all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "receive a ticket, train a model, hand off a notebook" role. You'll own problems end\-to\-end — from framing through modeling through impact — for enterprise customers where the stakes are real and the feedback loop is tight. If you understand why churn analysis matters differently f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead AI Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c681cf735c207c93</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Lead AI Engineer who can own the technical direction of Hilbert's AI stack, ship production\-grade systems hands\-on, and elevate a growing engineering team; all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "manage from a distance" role. You'll write code, make architecture calls, set the bar for quality and velocity, and build the engineering culture as we scale. You're the person the team looks to when the problem is ambiguous, the stakes are high, and the path forward hasn't been written y</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f3f89d6e8b828d2e</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for an AI Engineer who can build production\-grade AI systems end\-to\-end \- from prototype to pipeline to product \- with the ownership and urgency of a startup culture.


This is not a "fine\-tune a model and hand it off" role. You'll own core pieces of the AI stack that power Hilbert's demand intelligence platform, ship fast in conditions where the spec is evolving, and communicate what you're building (and why) with clarity to the rest of the team. If you write clean Python, think in systems, and want to buil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5187e2377e02df66</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle informatio</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0acc40891131c6bb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Irvine, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Satff Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=31dfff0141bbc219</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California **Job ID** 19495
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senio</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Principal AI/ML Engineer - Abbott</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9a8101317b40f77</link>
        <description>Abbott is a global healthcare leader that helps people live more fully at all stages of life. Our portfolio of life\-changing technologies spans the spectrum of healthcare, with leading businesses and products in diagnostics, medical devices, nutritionals and branded generic medicines. Our 115,000 colleagues serve people in more than 160 countries.


Our medical devices help more than 10,000 people have healthier hearts, improve quality of life for thousands of people living with chronic pain and movement disorders, and liberate more than 500,000 people with diabetes from routine ﬁngersticks.

**Working at Abbott**


At Abbott, you can do work that matters, grow, and learn, care for yourself and family, be your true self and live a full life. You’ll also have access to:

* Career development with an international company where you can grow the career you dream of.
* Employees can qualify for free medical coverage in our Health Investment Plan (HIP) PPO medical plan in the next calendar</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Developer Efficiency - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=926a2a0f154ea1f4</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------

Job Overview
------------


The Development Efficiency Data Science team within PDX is responsible for ensuring that Intuit’s Development Efficiency metric is analytically correct, interpretable, and trusted as it becomes a core input to FY26 execution, planning, and finance conversations.


We are seeking a Staff DS to lead Development Efficiency Data Science. This role owns the analytical strategy, measurement framework, and interpretation standards for Development Efficiency across the Product Development Lifecycle. The role is explicitly focused on measurement science and decision support, not on building developer platforms, enforcing tooling, or operating systems.


This leader will manage a team of senior data scientists and partner closely with Finance, PDX leadership, and senior stakeholders to translate complex analytical outputs into clear, defensible narratives that inform planning, prioritization, and investment decisions.

 **Responsibilities**
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 01:05:30 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
