<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sensing Software Engineer - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5ff51b4fc663ee33</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
The Tesla Sensing Software Team is looking for a sensing software engineer with expertise in state\-of\-the\-art computer vision algorithms. The person in this role will need to be familiar with and has prior experience of machine learning and deep learning algorithms, proficient with programming and software engineering fundamentals, and work with hardware engineers and firmware engineers to develop efficient, and tightly integrated features. The candidate is also expected to be able to learn and adapt quickly to the fast\-paced environment, get hands dirty in the lab or in the car for data collection and analysis, algorithm validation when needed to, and use it to root cause issues, and propose solutions.

 **What You'll Do*** Development of new computer vision algorithms for sensing applications
* Write python and C\+\+ code to develop algorithms, analyze data and generate visualizations
* Work with hardware engineers and firmware engineers to develop efficient, a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Performance Engineer - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d2687ed7b2b2a254</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
The Performance Optimization team takes research models and makes them run efficiently on Tesla's AI\-ASICs, powering Autopilot and Optimus. This role sits at the intersection of AI research, compiler development, kernel optimization, and hardware design. You'll collaborate with AI researchers on novel quantization techniques, precision improvements, and non\-standard architectures. You'll develop optimized kernels using our MLIR\-based compiler stack to achieve real\-time latency for self\-driving and humanoid robots. You'll work directly with hardware teams to shape our next\-generation AI and Dojo chips.

 **What You'll Do*** Implement, optimize, and profile highly performant kernels for inference and training on Tesla's AI and Dojo ASICs
* Optimize bottlenecks in the inference flow, make precision/performance tradeoff decisions, and develop novel techniques to improve hardware utilization and throughput
* Work on a variety of edge and datacenter workloads, from s</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Staff Engineer - Applied AI - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2c1bc264cbde977f</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Senior Staff Engineer, Applied AI**
=====================================

**About GEICO**
---------------


At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.


Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers' expectations while</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Staff Engineer - Applied AI - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e2003f5ef03cb532</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Senior Staff Engineer, Applied AI**
=====================================

**About GEICO**
---------------


At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.


Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers' expectations while</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Assistant/Associate/Full Researcher Machine Learning Models - Advanced Bioimaging Center Department of Molecular and Cell Biology - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81f049efde576f80</link>
        <description>**Position overview Position title:** Assistant/Associate/Full Researcher
  
**Salary range:** The UC academic salary scales set the minimum pay determined by rank and step at appointment. See the following table for the current salary scale for this position: https://www.ucop.edu/academic\-personnel\-programs/\_files/2025\-26/policy\-covered\-july\-2025\-scales/t13\-a.pdf . A reasonable estimate for this position is $199,700\- $357,200\.
  
  

**Percent time:** 100%
  
  

**Anticipated start:** Winter/Spring 2026
  
  

**Position duration:** Initial appointment is for one year with the possibility of renewal based on performance and funding availability.
  
  

Application Window
  
**Open date:** February 26, 2026
  
  

**Next review date:** Thursday, Mar 12, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Apply by this date to ensure full consideration by the committee.
  
  

**Final date:** Saturday, Mar 28, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Applications will continue to be accepted until t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Machine Learning Engineer - A10 Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=459c8aa3afb1e7dd</link>
        <description>Sr. AI Machine Learning Engineer
**Position Overview**
---------------------

We are looking for a talented and experienced Deep Learning Engineer specializing in Large Language Models (LLMs) to join our dynamic team. In this role, you will play a pivotal part in enhancing the reliability, safety, and performance of AI models and systems. You will work closely with AI researchers and product teams to drive cutting\-edge advancements in AI safety and responsible AI solutions.


**Responsibilities**

* Assist in designing and implementing end\-to\-end safety\-focused frameworks for LLMs
* Develop and apply risk mitigation techniques, including safe inference strategies to ensure reliable AI behavior
* Identify vulnerabilities in AI systems and contribute to adversarial testing, bias detection, and mitigation strategies
* Collaborate with cross\-functional teams to integrate safety mechanisms into AI workflows and pipelines
* Design and optimize LLM architectures to improve performance, s</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Off-Search, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5d2d1c808279c486</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights.
  

  

We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover mo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products Off-Search Sourcing - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=aed2e2670ee6a276</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover more about Sponsor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Sensor Validation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=573132bc8b2144e0</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Software Engineering builds the brains of Waymo's fully autonomous driving technology. Our software allows the Waymo Driver to perceive the world around it, make the right decision for every situation, and deliver people safely to their destinations. We think deeply and solve complex technica</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineering Tech Lead / Architect - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92f4c535a1af9c1</link>
        <description>**Mission**
-----------

At Faros AI, we are reshaping the way engineering organizations operate, with an engineering intelligence platform that provides visibility and context across the organization's software delivery systems. This deep operational context supports engineering leaders today, and is increasingly essential as AI agents begin to operate within real software delivery environments. Faros AI is laying the foundation for how humans and AI will build software together in the years ahead.

**About the Role**
------------------


Join our AI team to build Lighthouse AI \- the intelligence engine that helps engineering leaders understand organizational bottlenecks and improve performance in an age where AI is redefining the engineering craft. You'll work on natural language interfaces, causal analysis models, and ML\-driven insights that impact how thousands of engineers work at companies like Autodesk, Discord, and Vimeo.

**Responsibilities**
--------------------

* Collabor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Autonomous Material Processing Postdoctoral Fellow - Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ef7bde20fa64aedb</link>
        <description>Berkeley Lab’s Energy Geosciences division is hiring an Autonomous Material Processing Postdoctoral Fellow to help transform how critical materials are produced.  

In this role, you’ll bring together machine learning, real\-time monitoring, and thermochemical insight to build smarter, self\-improving materials processing systems. Your work will help strengthen a sustainable domestic lithium supply while significantly cutting waste, water use, and carbon emissions.  

You’ll work side by side with talented scientists and engineers from national laboratories, universities, and industry, all collaborating to rethink how critical materials are produced — making the process cleaner, smarter, and more efficient.  

This is an opportunity to help reshape how critical materials are produced — moving toward smarter, data\-driven processes that are autonomous, scientifically grounded, and continuously improving. If you’re ambitious, creative, and excited about building the foundation for AI\-po</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer (Prisma Access) - Palo Alto Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e08ef26de035de5</link>
        <description>Santa Clara, California, United States Product Engineering Ref ID: JR\-013557  

**Our Mission**


At Palo Alto Networks®, we’re united by a shared mission—to protect our digital way of life. We thrive at the intersection of innovation and impact, solving real\-world problems with cutting\-edge technology and bold thinking. Here, everyone has a voice, and every idea counts. If you’re ready to do the most meaningful work of your career alongside people who are just as passionate as you are, you’re in the right place.

**Who We Are**


In order to be the cybersecurity partner of choice, we must trailblaze the path and shape the future of our industry. This is something our employees work at each day and is defined by our values: Disruption, Collaboration, Execution, Integrity, and Inclusion. We weave AI into the fabric of everything we do and use it to augment the impact every individual can have. If you are passionate about solving real\-world problems and ideating beside the best and t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Analyst, Trust and Safety, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4e9bc141554057be</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in data analysis, including identifying trends, generating summary statistics, and drawing insights from quantitative and qualitative data.
* 5 years of experience managing projects and defining project scope, goals, and deliverables.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with one or more of the following languages: SQL, R, Python, or C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with machine learning systems.
* Experience in prompt engineering and applying large language models for data labeling.
* Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
* Excellent problem\-solving and critical thinking skills with attention to detail in an ever\-chan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Analyst, Trust and Safety, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c96b1184d842fbe8</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in data analysis, including identifying trends, generating summary statistics, and drawing insights from quantitative and qualitative data.
* 5 years of experience managing projects and defining project scope, goals, and deliverables.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with one or more of the following languages: SQL, R, Python, or C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with machine learning systems.
* Experience in prompt engineering and applying large language models for data labeling.
* Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
* Excellent problem\-solving and critical thinking skills with attention to detail in an ever\-chan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Google Security Operations - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0d72f787b560d7b6</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in C\+\+ or Go, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* Experience building and architecting large\-scale distributed systems.
* Experience performing quantitative and qualitative data analysis to drive product or business decisions.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience developing and deploying applications that leverage Google Cloud Spanner for data persistence in a production environment.
* Experience with cloud security architecture, including designing and implementing secure cloud solutions.
* Experience designing, building, and operating large\-scale distributed systems for large enterprise customers.
* Experience developing and deploying machine learning models for anomaly detection </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager III, Network Infrastructure, Cloud AI Systems - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0962de20e6df6768</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in program management.
* Experience leading network infrastructure projects as an engineer or technical program manager making technical contributions to programs.

Experience managing software integration programs or direct integration engineering.  
* 

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of experience managing cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.
* Experience in emerging cloud technologies or related technical fields.
* Experience in full\-stack development.
* Ability to synthesize material for audiences via executive communications, presentations, dashboards, and documentation.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's projects, like our users, span the globe and require managers to keep the big picture in focus while being able to dive into the unique engineering challenges we face daily. As a Technical Program Manager at G</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Scientist, PhD - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=173cf44ae91267c7</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

The Research team at OpenAI advances the frontier of artificial intelligence by developing new models, algorithms, and learning paradigms that push toward safe and beneficial AGI. Our researchers work across a wide range of domains including multimodal learning, reasoning, robotics, alignment, and large\-scale foundation models, collaborating closely with engineering and product teams to translate research breakthroughs into real\-world impact.
  
  

About the Role
  
  

As a Research Scientist at OpenAI, you will develop novel machine learning methods and contribute to advancing the research agenda of the team you join. You will work on discovering simple, scalable, and generalizable ideas that improve model capabilities and help shape a unified long\-term research vision across the organization.
  
  

We’re looking for people who are excited to pursue ambitious research problems, operate independently, and collaborate deeply with interdisciplinary teams to br</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Sensor Validation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=12e5fb1de98c135b</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| KIRKLAND, WASHINGTON, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4316


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Software Engineering builds the brains of Waymo's fully autonomous driving technology. Our software allows the Waymo Driver to perc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer - AI/ML - Stanford Health Care</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f74043deeb5aad2d</link>
        <description>1\.0 FTE Full time Day \- 08 Hour R2654167 Hybrid 108480039 TDS Data Science Innovation Technology \&amp; Digital Solutions PALO ALTO, 1830 Embarcadero, California
If you're ready to be part of our legacy of hope and innovation, we encourage you to take the first step and explore our current job openings. Your best is waiting to be discovered.

  


Day \- 08 Hour (United States of America)**This is a Stanford Health Care job.**


The Data Engineer will be part of a team building Stanford Health Care's (SHC) solutions incorporating Artificial Intelligence including providing health care solutions in the areas of patient care, medical research and administrative services. This group is designed to bring Artificial Intelligence (AI) and other emerging machine learning (ML) based innovations in data science into healthcare and will partner closely with individuals across clinical specialties and operations areas to deploy algorithms that can lead to better patient outcomes.
  

  

Reporting </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Robotics Software Engineer - Grasping - Intrinsic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=72b3052a5c2d639f</link>
        <description>Intrinsic is Alphabet's bet aiming to reimagine the potential of industrial robotics. Our team believes that advances in AI, perception and simulation will redefine what's possible for industrial robotics in the near future – with software and data at the core.



Our mission is to make industrial robotics intelligent, accessible, and usable for millions more businesses, entrepreneurs, and developers. We are a dynamic team of engineers, roboticists, designers, and technologists who are passionate about unlocking the creative and economic potential of industrial robotics.

**Role**
--------



As a Robotics Software Engineer, you will develop innovative algorithms and strategies to facilitate robust grasping and manipulation in complex, real\-world manufacturing environments. You will be responsible for abstracting the inherent complexity of robotic manipulation into intuitive, seamless workflows. By building a software layer that possesses a deep understanding of manufacturing tasks, y</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Robotics Software Engineer - Grasping - Intrinsic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=199c97342bbbb643</link>
        <description>Intrinsic is Alphabet's bet aiming to reimagine the potential of industrial robotics. Our team believes that advances in AI, perception and simulation will redefine what's possible for industrial robotics in the near future – with software and data at the core.



Our mission is to make industrial robotics intelligent, accessible, and usable for millions more businesses, entrepreneurs, and developers. We are a dynamic team of engineers, roboticists, designers, and technologists who are passionate about unlocking the creative and economic potential of industrial robotics.

**Role**
--------



As a Staff Robotics Software Engineer and Researcher, you will take full technical ownership of developing and deploying robotics grasping and manipulation algorithms, leading the end\-to\-end lifecycle from foundational research to global deployment. You will help define the architecture and long\-term strategy that enables robots to interact with the physical world, researching and scoping innov</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Operations Lead - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94cd416369c12455</link>
        <description>### **Company Description**


**Join us and make YOUR mark on the World!**


Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory (LLNL) has turned bold ideas into world\-changing impact advancing science and technology to strengthen U.S. security and promote global stability.


Our mission spans four critical national security areas nuclear deterrence, threat preparedness, energy security, and multi\-domain defense empowering teams to take on the toughest challenges of today and tomorrow. With a culture built on innovation and operational excellence, LLNL is a place where your expertise can make a real impact.


### **Job Description**


We are seeking a highly qualified **AI Operations Lead** to lead an interdisciplinary team of systems analysts, computational engineering analysts, and machine learning and artificial intelligence experts. The AI Operations Lead will translate Laboratory operational, policy, and administrative challenges into scalable, data\-driven AI workflows and interface with D</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Research Intern (PhD), AI Research, Science - Biohub</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7226642d767cd83a</link>
        <description>Biohub is leading the new era of AI\-powered biology to cure or prevent disease through its 501c3 medical research organization, with the support of the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative.

**The Team**
------------



Biohub is building the first large\-scale initiative combining frontier artificial intelligence and frontier biology to cure or prevent all disease. In 2025, Biohub welcomed the EvolutionaryScale team \- recognized for creating large\-scale frontier AI systems for the life sciences \- to accelerate the mission. Led by co\-founder Alex Rives, who now serves as Head of Science at Biohub, the integrated organization is scaling up the compute and research infrastructure needed to build next\-generation models of biology\-powered by the largest cluster dedicated to open science. Backed by the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative (CZI), Biohub operates as a nonprofit organization uniting leading scientists, engineers, and technologists across hubs based in the San Francisco Bay Area, New York, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Training Framework Engineer, GenAI - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d94304e45f5389a1</link>
        <description>The Opportunity
  
Adobe Applied Science \&amp; Machine Learning ( ASML ) is seeking a Staff Machine Learning Training Framework Engineer to play a critical role in building and scaling the core training systems behind Adobe’s generative AI foundation models.
  
In this role, you will serve as a senior technical owner for key components of our training framework , translating research needs into reliable, scalable, and high‑performance training infrastructure. Rather than focusing on a single model, your work will enable multiple multimodal and video foundation models by strengthening the shared systems used to train them.
  
You will operate at the intersection of applied research and large‑scale systems execution, ensuring that training workflows are robust, reproducible, and performant across large GPU clusters. This role is ideal for a senior engineer who thrives on deep technical ownership, complex execution, and close collaboration with research teams. Job Responsibilities
  
**Train</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Oncology - BillionToOne</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7fc6d494ae291855</link>
        <description>**Ready to redefine what's possible in molecular diagnostics?**
---------------------------------------------------------------



Join a team of brilliant, passionate innovators who wake up every day determined to transform healthcare. At BillionToOne, we've built something extraordinary—a culture where transparency fuels trust, collaboration drives breakthroughs, and every voice matters in our mission to make life\-changing diagnostics accessible to all. We don't just aim for incremental improvements; we strive to build products that are 10x better than anything that exists today. Our people are our greatest asset:talented scientists, engineers, sales professionals, and visionaries united by an unwavering commitment to changing the standard of care in prenatal and cancer diagnostics. This is where cutting\-edge science meets human compassion—every innovation you contribute helps remove fear of unknown from some of life's most critical medical moments. **If you're driven by purpose, e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Engineer - Technical Lead - Arine</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bd21973a52e2b6d3</link>
        <description>Based in San Francisco, Arine is a rapidly growing healthcare technology and clinical services company with a mission to ensure individuals receive the safest and most effective treatments for their unique and evolving healthcare needs.



Frequently, medications cause more harm than good. Incorrect drugs and doses costs the US healthcare system over $528 billion in waste, avoidable harm, and hospitalizations each year. Arine is redefining what excellent healthcare looks like by solving these issues through our software platform (SaaS). We combine cutting edge data science, machine learning, AI, and deep clinical expertise to introduce a patient\-centric view to medication management, and develop and deliver personalized care plans on a massive scale for patients and their care teams.



Arine is committed to improving the lives and health of complex patients that have an outsized impact on healthcare costs and have traditionally been difficult to identify and address. These patients f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, ML Inference Performance - SambaNova Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=17d03a5e781bc408</link>
        <description>The era of pervasive AI has arrived. In this era, organizations will use generative AI to unlock hidden value in their data, accelerate processes, reduce costs, drive efficiency and innovation to fundamentally transform their businesses and operations at scale.



SambaNova Suite™ is the first full\-stack, generative AI platform, from chip to model, optimized for enterprise and government organizations. Powered by the intelligent SN40L chip, the SambaNova Suite is a fully integrated platform, delivered on\-premises or in the cloud, combined with state\-of\-the\-art open\-source models that can be easily and securely fine\-tuned using customer data for greater accuracy. Once adapted with customer data, customers retain model ownership in perpetuity, so they can turn generative AI into one of their most valuable assets.

### **About The Role**



The **Principal Compiler Engineer \- ML Systems** position will be responsible for working with the different layers of the compiler stack and </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist III - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a5248758e37ec23c</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------


Our Company If you’re thinking ‘scale’, think bigger and don’t stop there. At Walmart Labs, we don’t just innovate, we enable transformations across stores and different channels for the Walmart experience. We innovate to deliver a simple and seamless experience for our customers. Our tech talent solves the biggest and most complex problems. They drive digital transformation where data science and analytics are enabling us to better serve our customers and create a digital relationship with them. As our customers evolve and adapt, we are taking it a few notches further here. We’re changing what customers can expect from the experience of shopping, from the physical stores, to mobile social and even online; we’re not just ready for the future of shopping, we’re creating it. Our Team Market Intelligence (MINT) team at Walmart Global Tech delivers on the promise of EDLP (Every Day Low Prices) to</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Software Engineer Intern (Delivery Marketplace), United States - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=be700be9655d5573</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates in the machine learning and optimization domain to intern with our Delivery Marketplace team during summer 2026 (12 weeks). You will be embedded in an engineering team and work closely with other specialists, data scientists, and product managers. As a PhD intern, you will work on an exciting yet bold problem independently, under the supervision of an experienced engineer on that team.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

At Uber, we work on many ambitious engineering products covering many lines of business as well as the underlying platform technologies that power those businesses. We foster growth and increase profitability of Uber by pushing the frontiers of machine learning, constrained optimization, statistics, data science and economics and developing highly reliable and scalable platforms to accelerate Uber's impact on the transportation industry.
  

  

As a PhD software engineer intern, you will have a lot of opportunities to work with product m</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Experimental Physicist - KBR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e0154ab80ddd5538</link>
        <description>**Title:**


Experimental Physicist**BELONG. CONNECT. GROW. with KBR.**


Around here, we define the future. We are a company of innovators, thinkers, creators, explorers, volunteers, and dreamers. But we all share one goal: to improve the world responsibly and safely.

**Job Description:**

  

We are seeking an Experimental Physicist with specialized expertise in acoustic testing of cryogenic propellant transfer lines to:

* Conduct acoustic testing of unwanted bubbles in cryogenic liquids propellent lines.
* Analyze and interpret data to understand the acoustic behavior and characteristics of the bubbles.
* Collaborate with a team of physicists and engineers on testing and data analysis.
* Utilize LabView, SolidWorks, and MATLAB for data acquisition, analysis, and reporting.
* Contribute to the development of protocols and standards for acoustic detection or "bubble alarm".
  

This person will lead independent research through numerical and theoretical analysis, exploring quantum e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Principal AI/ML Scientist - Abbott</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e3c986d7589d1600</link>
        <description>Abbott is a global healthcare leader that helps people live more fully at all stages of life. Our portfolio of life\-changing technologies spans the spectrum of healthcare, with leading businesses and products in diagnostics, medical devices, nutritionals and branded generic medicines. Our 115,000 colleagues serve people in more than 160 countries.


Our medical devices help more than 10,000 people have healthier hearts, improve quality of life for thousands of people living with chronic pain and movement disorders, and liberate more than 500,000 people with diabetes from routine ﬁngersticks.

**Working at Abbott**


At Abbott, you can do work that matters, grow, and learn, care for yourself and family, be your true self and live a full life. You’ll also have access to:

* Career development with an international company where you can grow the career you dream of.
* Employees can qualify for free medical coverage in our Health Investment Plan (HIP) PPO medical plan in the next calendar</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA) Senior, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df5419f309e5132</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

  

As a Senior Software Engineer, you will lead the delivery of scalable software solutions by managing feature implementation, testing, and ongoing support within collaborative teams. This role requires expertise in multiple programming languages and a strong focus on software lifecycle execution, including automation and continuous integration. You will integrate AI and machine learning components to enhance system capabilities while ensuring alignment with platform objectives. By applying sound technical judgment and fostering innovation, you will contribute to high\-quality, reliable software that meets business goals and supports continuous improvement across the organization. **\*\*\*\*\*Immigration Sponsorship support will NOT be available for this**  

**position\*\*\*\*\***
  

**About the team:**
  

The Walmart Business (B2B) group focuses on delivering innovative solutions that em</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer - Palo Alto Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8f020aa6341a736b</link>
        <description>Santa Clara, California, United States Product Engineering Ref ID: JR\-015122  

**Our Mission**


At Palo Alto Networks®, we’re united by a shared mission—to protect our digital way of life. We thrive at the intersection of innovation and impact, solving real\-world problems with cutting\-edge technology and bold thinking. Here, everyone has a voice, and every idea counts. If you’re ready to do the most meaningful work of your career alongside people who are just as passionate as you are, you’re in the right place.

**Who We Are**


In order to be the cybersecurity partner of choice, we must trailblaze the path and shape the future of our industry. This is something our employees work at each day and is defined by our values: Disruption, Collaboration, Execution, Integrity, and Inclusion. We weave AI into the fabric of everything we do and use it to augment the impact every individual can have. If you are passionate about solving real\-world problems and ideating beside the best and t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer with AI/ML Focus - Tata Consultancy Services (TCS)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d0fc0f491c9f4bb</link>
        <description>JOB DESCRIPTION:
Core Responsibilities
1\. Data Architecture \&amp; Pipeline Design
* Identify good data set and data candidates for building AI based recommendation engine
* Design denormalized data structures optimized for LLM consumption
* Aggregate data from multiple CRM modules/tables into one for LLM consumption
* Implement data quality monitoring and validation frameworks

2\. CRM Data Expertise
* Analyze complex CRM schemas (Accounts, Opportunities, Notes, Order History, Account Actuals)
* Understand business relationships between entities and their impact on recommendations
* Map data lineage from source systems to AI\-ready datasets

 3\. AI/ML Data Preparation
* Data preprocessing and normalization for LLM consumption
* Create training datasets for recommendation model improvement
* Implement data versioning for model reproducibility

4\. Performance Optimization
* Query optimization for large\-scale data aggregation
* Caching strategies for frequently accessed recommendation da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Sutter Health</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9e4eb366f4273b09</link>
        <description>We are so glad you are interested in joining Sutter Health!

**Organization:**


SHSO\-Sutter Health System Office\-Bay**Position Overview:**


\*\*\*\*Please Note: While this position is listed as hybrid, regular in\-office attendance is required. Candidates should be prepared to commute to the San Francisco office on a consistent basis to support team collaboration and business needs.\*\*\*\*
  

  

Responsible for leading the design, build, and maintain Sutter Health’s artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) infrastructure, including end to end pipelines for ML and large language models (LLM) that support analytics, data science, and enterprise AI use cases. This includes how AI models and associated data are ingested, processed, trained, deployed, monitored, governed, and secured across cloud and on premises environments. Ensures that AI systems meet high standards of performance, reliability, and compliance, enabling the organization to safely and effectively integ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Observability - CRUSOE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7439ce0a1c20dfd8</link>
        <description>Crusoe's mission is to accelerate the abundance of energy and intelligence. We’re crafting the engine that powers a world where people can create ambitiously with AI — without sacrificing scale, speed, or sustainability.


Be a part of the AI revolution with sustainable technology at Crusoe. Here, you'll drive meaningful innovation, make a tangible impact, and join a team that’s setting the pace for responsible, transformative cloud infrastructure.

**About This Role:**


We’re seeking a Senior Software Engineer to play a key role on our Observability team within the Cloud Infrastructure organization. This team owns the real\-time observability platforms that underpin visibility, reliability, and operational insight across our cloud and data center infrastructure.

**What You’ll Be Working On:**

* Maintain and manage core observability tools, including platforms for metrics, events, logs and tracing.
* Develop and operate data pipelines to move telemetry data from various sources to b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Head of AI - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc47fcacc4c7ee4a</link>
        <description>**About Highlight AI**


We're a small, senior team building the intelligent OS for the agentic age. Highlight is a proactive AI that captures your team's context, surfaces what matters, and handles the busywork so you can focus on decisions and building. We ship fast, obsess over craft, and care deeply about user experience and trust. Backed by General Catalyst, Valor, SV Angel, and Conviction, we’re looking for like\-minded people to help define how the next generation of knowledge workers get things done.

**The Role**


We're hiring a **Head of AI Engineering** to lead and scale our ML and AI efforts as we build the engine that powers Highlight. You'll own the architecture, quality, and roadmap for how we ingest, model, and surface context, starting from data pipelines and evals to the context graph that makes our system truly useful. This is a hands\-on leadership role: you'll write code, set technical direction, mentor engineers, and collaborate closely with Backend and Product t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer - Unity Technologies</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f6aac306145591a6</link>
        <description>**The opportunity**  

At Unity, we're building a world\-class advertising platform that operates at a massive global scale. The Ads team powers the systems that connect advertisers with creators and players, driving performance, reliability, and growth across our ecosystem.



As a Data Engineer on the Feature Platform team, you'll play a critical role in building the data foundations that power machine learning, experimentation, and optimization across our ads ecosystem. You'll operate at the core of our ML infrastructure, transforming raw, high\-volume event data into reliable, production\-grade feature datasets used for bidding, attribution, and ranking systems.



You will work at the intersection of business logic, large\-scale distributed processing, and platform engineering — translating complex and evolving product requirements into scalable, well\-modeled, and reproducible data systems. This role goes beyond analytics enablement; it focuses on building durable, high\-quality </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer - Unity Technologies</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6cd0d0f24117572d</link>
        <description>**The opportunity**  

At Unity, we're building a world\-class advertising platform that operates at a massive global scale. The Ads team powers the systems that connect advertisers with creators and players, driving performance, reliability, and growth across our ecosystem.



As a Data Engineer on the Feature Platform team, you'll play a critical role in building the data foundations that power machine learning, experimentation, and optimization across our ads ecosystem. You'll operate at the core of our ML infrastructure, transforming raw, high\-volume event data into reliable, production\-grade feature datasets used for bidding, attribution, and ranking systems.



You will work at the intersection of business logic, large\-scale distributed processing, and platform engineering — translating complex and evolving product requirements into scalable, well\-modeled, and reproducible data systems. This role goes beyond analytics enablement; it focuses on building durable, high\-quality </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Product Development Engineer - Ampere Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=966199665d7530b9</link>
        <description>**Description**  



  

Invent the future with us.  

  

Ampere is a semiconductor design company for a new era, leading the future of computing with an innovative approach to CPU design focused on high\-performance, energy efficient AI compute.
  

  

As a pioneer in the new frontier of energy efficient high\-performance computing, Ampere is part of the Softbank Group of companies driving sustainable computing for AI, Cloud, and edge applications.  

  

Join us at Ampere and work alongside a passionate and growing team \- we’d love to have you apply!  

  

**About the role:**  

  

The Principal Product Development Engineer will be instrumental in leveraging system to tester data to define SKU binning and developing performance binning models for our products. This role requires a detail\-oriented engineer who can quickly identify root causes and implement corrective actions to enhance product performance and quality. The ideal candidate will have a strong background in data ana</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer, Machine Learning, Google Customer Solutions - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c1941d6bcff541c0</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, a related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience working on data and creating reports, and with database query (e.g., SQL) and visualization tools (e.g., Tableau, dashboards).
* Experience with one or more general purpose programming languages (e.g., Python, C/C\+\+, Java).
* Experience with Artificial Intelligence or Machine Learning Pipelines.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience with TensorFlow, TFX, TorchX, JAX, PyTorch, YDF, Vertex AI or other ML modeling and pipeline technologies.
* Experience with Big Data or scaled/sharded system design.
* Experience with Apache Beam, or Python and SQL.
* Proficiency in machine learning, data analysis, or data science, working knowledge of ML tas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer, Machine Learning, Google Customer Solutions - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6740e0aa5c417dbb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, a related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience working on data and creating reports, and with database query (e.g., SQL) and visualization tools (e.g., Tableau, dashboards).
* Experience with one or more general purpose programming languages (e.g., Python, C/C\+\+, Java).
* Experience with Artificial Intelligence or Machine Learning Pipelines.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience with TensorFlow, TFX, TorchX, JAX, PyTorch, YDF, Vertex AI or other ML modeling and pipeline technologies.
* Experience with Big Data or scaled/sharded system design.
* Experience with Apache Beam, or Python and SQL.
* Proficiency in machine learning, data analysis, or data science, working knowledge of ML tas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Manager, Borglet Machine Learning - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=30daa84520906bb7</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 3 years of experience with developing large\-scale infrastructure, distributed systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage or hardware architecture.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role.
* 2 years of experience in a people management or team leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* Experience with system software, distributed systems, and complex multi\-component software systems.
* Experience in developing and releasing system software products.
* Familiarity with the Linux kernel interface, and containers.
* Understanding of key concepts of performance analysis and tuning with excellent C/C\+\+ programming skills.
* Excellent data analysis and SQL skills.

**About the job**
-----------------


Like Google's own a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Business Data Scientist, Ads Marketing Analytics - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2a7d67ccbdbf6b6</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a relevant PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Statistics or related quantitative discipline.
* 4 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analys</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Business Data Scientist, Ads Marketing Analytics - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3ce24daeaeff408d</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a relevant PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Statistics or related quantitative discipline.
* 4 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analys</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Manager, Ads Personalization, User Modeling Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=54c037913817d125</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 3 years of experience in AI/ML related engineering, developing, deploying, managing, and maintaining machine learning infrastructure.
* 2 years of experience in a people management or team leadership role.
* Experience working in the digital advertising industry.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience building end\-to\-end solutions either in an infrastructure or product\-based team.
* Experience building and testing highly\-scalable distributed systems or low\-latency/streaming batch systems.
* Experience collaborating with cross\-functional teams in a global organization and managing stakeholders.
* Ability to take full ownership and execute highly\-visible projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


Like Google's own ambitions, the work of a Software Engineer goes beyond just Sea</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Group Product Manager, AI Personalization, Data Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2f5482de3e4b77a6</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience as a Product Manager in the data or AI/ML domain.
* 5 years of experience in people management, with technical leadership.
* 5 years of experience taking technical products from conception to launch (e.g., ideation to execution, end\-to\-end, 0 to 1, etc).
* Experience developing and scaling data management infrastructure products at a global level.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or a business related field.
* Experience in building back\-end systems, with the knowledge of the infrastructure to power Generative AI (Gen AI) and agentic experiences.
* Experience supporting the Machine Learning development lifecycle, particularly regarding Retrieval\-Augmented Generation (RAG) or personalization models.
* Knowledge of data management best practices where privacy and consent are paramount.
* Ability to conduct market research and parti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, YouTube Shorts, Viewer Feed Quality - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7acfcca82f4cff33</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or equivalent practical experience.
* 15 years of experience in engineering.
* Experience with cross\-functional technical innovation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 7 years of experience in a technical leadership role responsible for multiple technical areas and setting technical direction.
* Ability to manage multiple complex assignments simultaneously and to work with geographically dispersed, cross\-functional teams.
* Deep expertise in large\-scale recommendation systems (Retrieval/Ranking), Generative AI for content understanding, and machine learning Infrastructure.

**About the job**
-----------------


The Viewer Growth team within the Shorts Discovery organization aims at bringing step\-changes in the viewer Shorts recommendations through improved understanding of users’ interests, preferences \&amp; behavior patterns, and leveraging advanced AI/ML technology.
  

  

In this Princip</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Developer Technology Intern, High-Performance Databases - Summer 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ef37ae83835c672f</link>
        <description>Our work at NVIDIA is dedicated towards a computing model focused on visual and AI computing. For two decades, NVIDIA has pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics, with our invention of the GPU. The GPU has also shown to be spectacularly effective at solving some of the most complex problems in computer science. Today, NVIDIA’s GPU simulates human intelligence, running deep learning algorithms and acting as the brain of computers, robots and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. We are looking to grow our company and teams with the smartest people in the world and there has never been a more exciting time to join our team!
NVIDIA is hiring passionate, extraordinary interns to work in its Developer Technology (DevTech) team. Artificial intelligence, the dream of computer scientists for over half a century, is no longer science fiction. And in the next few years, it will transform every industry. As high\-performance accelerators conti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Developer Technology Intern, AI - Summer 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a5c709a8675e35c</link>
        <description>Our work at NVIDIA is dedicated towards a computing model focused on visual and AI computing. For two decades, NVIDIA has pioneered visual computing, the art and science of computer graphics, with our invention of the GPU. The GPU has also shown to be spectacularly effective at solving some of the most complex problems in computer science. Today, NVIDIA’s GPU simulates human intelligence, running deep learning algorithms and acting as the brain of computers, robots and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. We are looking to grow our company and teams with the smartest people in the world and there has never been a more exciting time to join our team!
Developer Technology team at NVIDIA plays a pivotal role in extracting maximum performance from our computing platform which enables researchers to develop and productize these state\-of\-the\-art technologies. Do you share our passion for Artificial Intelligence? Come join a team full of outstanding engineers to w</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Fullstack Engineer - Cargomatic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5ce602fc17eef5ff</link>
        <description>Join a rapidly growing company disrupting the trucking industry! Cargomatic is the \#1 technology platform and digital marketplace powering world\-class local trucking. Take a look around you. Literally everything humans build, grow, or sell has spent time on a truck. Local trucking is the lifeblood of every regional economy, yet this $82 billion industry still relies heavily on phone calls and fax machines. Cargomatic is transforming the way goods move through every local node in the supply chain by connecting shippers and commercial truck drivers with powerful mobile and web\-based technology. We are solving complex, real\-world problems every day and bringing transparency and efficiency to the shipping process.


**Senior Full Stack Engineer – React / Node / Go / AWS / MongoDB**



Cargomatic is seeking a Senior Full Stack Engineer who is passionate about building highly scalable, event\-driven systems for a real\-time logistics marketplace. This role will play a critical part in de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer - Cathexis</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ac3cc50fb4458aec</link>
        <description>Team CATHEXIS elevates the government contracting experience through rapid response, deep skill, and thoughtful problem\-solving and communication. Our core capabilities are our top\-tier program and project management, data analytics, and audit services, the backbone of which is our integrated approach to operational excellence.


You worked hard to get to where you are. You strive to make every day better than the day before. So do we. Team CATHEXIS operates with an all\-in mindset. We are working together to create a company that supports our shared values and individual goals. Our values are centered around Respect, Engagement, Customer Service, Integrity, Teamwork, and Excellence in everything we do for our employees, clients, partners, and communities. We believe success is best when we listen and lead with empathy; model high standards of ethics to provide a rewarding candidate experience; work hard, have fun, and appreciate the strengths we all bring to the team; and empower ou</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Worldwide Specialist Solutions Architect - GenAI, Data &amp; AI GTM - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=db9fa99e1434951b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you passionate about Generative AI (GenAI)? Do you want to help define the future of Go to Market (GTM) at AWS using generative AI? In this role, you will help some of our largest customers build and deploy GenAI enabled applications using Amazon Bedrock and SageMaker, fine tune and build Generative AI models, and help enterprise customers leverage these models to power end applications. You will engage with AWS product owners to influence product direction and help our customers tap into new markets by utilizing GenAI along with AWS Services.  

  

At Amazon, we’ve been investing deeply in artificial intelligence for over 20 years, and many of the capabilities customers experience in our products are driven by machine learning. Amazon.com’s recommendations engine is driven by machine learning (ML), as are the paths that optimize robotic picking routes in our fulfillment centers. Our supply chain, forecasting, and capacity planning are also inform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Worldwide Specialist Solutions Architect - GenAI, Data &amp; AI GTM - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b8d1649c6d2735a8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you passionate about Generative AI (GenAI)? Do you want to help define the future of Go to Market (GTM) at AWS using generative AI? In this role, you will help some of our largest customers build and deploy GenAI enabled applications using Amazon Bedrock and SageMaker, fine tune and build Generative AI models, and help enterprise customers leverage these models to power end applications. You will engage with AWS product owners to influence product direction and help our customers tap into new markets by utilizing GenAI along with AWS Services.  

  

At Amazon, we’ve been investing deeply in artificial intelligence for over 20 years, and many of the capabilities customers experience in our products are driven by machine learning. Amazon.com’s recommendations engine is driven by machine learning (ML), as are the paths that optimize robotic picking routes in our fulfillment centers. Our supply chain, forecasting, and capacity planning are also inform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Quality Engineer, Agent LLM - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=270605f9b0d70944</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Data Analyst, Purchasing &amp; Cost Analytics - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e9687074e0a91841</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
The Supply Chain Analytics team at Tesla is seeking a highly skilled and motivated Data Analyst to support our rapidly growing global supply chain organization by analyzing and visualizing data to drive informed decisions for launching and scaling various programs. In this role, you will lead the effective utilization of large supply chain datasets for our global supply management team, deliver impactful analytics solutions for Supply Chain Managers and Supplier Industrialization Engineers, and contribute to strategic projects and continuous improvement efforts across Supply Chain. You will interact with stakeholders at all levels, including executives, requiring a sharp business focus, excellent communication skills, and the ability to synthesize complex issues into data\-driven solutions. As part of a fast\-paced, innovative environment, flexibility, adaptability, and a proactive mindset are essential, and the ideal candidate will be a self\-starter with a passion </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Model Risk &amp; Data Analytics, Internal Audit - AMS - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=974f4a3a534da030</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Senior Data Scientist, Model Risk \&amp; Data Analytics, Internal Audit \- AMS
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A174184
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About The Team
  
Internal Audit is a global function responsible for providing independent assurance and evaluating the company's risk management, governance and internal control processes to determine if they are designed and operating effectively. The Internal Audit team plans and executes audit projects according to our risk\-based audit plan by evaluating financial, compliance, operational, and IT processes and controls. We work with business functions in addressing risks and improving the control environment through timely and comprehensive audit work and tracking of remediation actions until completion.
  
  

We are looking for data scientists and AI developers who will power our mission by building data products that enable and empower conti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Global Data Analytics for Internal Audit Function - AMS - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c276ceaec78f13bf</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Senior Data Scientist, Global Data Analytics for Internal Audit Function \- AMS
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A245992
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About The Team
  
Internal Audit is a global function responsible for providing independent assurance and evaluating the company's risk management, governance and internal control processes to determine if they are designed and operating effectively. The Internal Audit team plans and executes audit projects according to our risk\-based audit plan by evaluating financial, compliance, operational, and IT processes and controls. We work with business functions in addressing risks and improving the control environment through timely and comprehensive audit work and tracking of remediation actions until completion.
  
  

We are looking for a data scientist who will power our mission by building data products that enable and empower continuous auditi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Intuit Customer Success - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=54469ad0fe08d617</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California; San Diego, California **Job ID** 19870
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the Intuit Customer Success data science team as a Staff Data Scientist to shape the strategy to enable best\-in\-class customer experiences for QuickBook customers.The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most impo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7769c33c8462acdc</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across disciplines to run rapid experiments, conduct deep analytical investigations, and drive cross\-functional alignment that unlocks durable customer and revenue growth.



As a Sr. Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a senior technical leader and strategic thought partner to product and business executives. You will shape the growth roadmap by framing ambiguous opportunities, defining measurable hypotheses, and leading the design and interpretation of complex experiments. You will elevate the analytical bar across the organization, applying advanced causal infere</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=18a97eec706734ad</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across disciplines to run rapid experiments, conduct deep analytical investigations, and drive cross\-functional alignment that unlocks durable customer and revenue growth.



As a Sr. Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a senior technical leader and strategic thought partner to product and business executives. You will shape the growth roadmap by framing ambiguous opportunities, defining measurable hypotheses, and leading the design and interpretation of complex experiments. You will elevate the analytical bar across the organization, applying advanced causal infere</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - AI/ML - Stanford Health Care</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dbf0827f26d217a0</link>
        <description>1\.0 FTE Full time Day \- 08 Hour R2654168 Hybrid 108480039 TDS Data Science Innovation Technology \&amp; Digital Solutions PALO ALTO, 1830 Embarcadero, California
If you're ready to be part of our legacy of hope and innovation, we encourage you to take the first step and explore our current job openings. Your best is waiting to be discovered.

  


Day \- 08 Hour (United States of America)**This is a Stanford Health Care job.**


The Data Scientist will be part of a team building Stanford Health Care's (SHC) solutions incorporating Artificial Intelligence including providing health care solutions in the areas of patient care, medical research and administrative services. This group is designed to bring Artificial Intelligence (AI), and other emerging machine learning (ML) based innovations in data science into healthcare and will partner closely with individuals across clinical specialties and operations areas to deploy algorithms that can lead to better patient outcomes.
  

  

Reportin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI/ML Applied Scientist - Generative AI - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c90e19a4662171d7</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **Summary:**


We are searching for an experienced Sr AI/ML Applied Scientist to join our newly formed ABAP Foundation Model team in New Port Beach. This dynamic team is at the forefront of SAP’s cloud transformation efforts, leveraging large language models to accelerate our customers’ data and code transformation. The team collaborates closely with established teams in Europe and India, various SAP stakeholders, UC Irvine, and early adopter customers. You will play a key role in shapi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Scientific Lead - Forward Deployed AI Engineer, Applied Intelligence for Discovery - Eli Lilly</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3febd775780f1670</link>
        <description>At Lilly, we unite caring with discovery to make life better for people around the world. We are a global healthcare leader headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana. Our employees around the world work to discover and bring life\-changing medicines to those who need them, improve the understanding and management of disease, and give back to our communities through philanthropy and volunteerism. We give our best effort to our work, and we put people first. We’re looking for people who are determined to make life better for people around the world.

**The Opportunity**


We are building something unprecedented — an AI foundation that will push the frontier on what is possible today across drug discovery research, from target identification and disease biology through translational science.


The Applied Intelligence for Discovery (AI4D) team is a newly formed group within Lilly Research Laboratories that operates at the intersection of scientific delivery and core platform development. AI4</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Scientific Lead, Applied Intelligence for Discovery - Eli Lilly</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5c16e06c2d5aa993</link>
        <description>At Lilly, we unite caring with discovery to make life better for people around the world. We are a global healthcare leader headquartered in Indianapolis, Indiana. Our employees around the world work to discover and bring life\-changing medicines to those who need them, improve the understanding and management of disease, and give back to our communities through philanthropy and volunteerism. We give our best effort to our work, and we put people first. We’re looking for people who are determined to make life better for people around the world.


The Opportunity


We are building something unprecedented, an AI foundation that will fundamentally change how drug discovery research is conducted.


The Applied Intelligence for Discovery (AI4D) team is a newly formed group within Lilly Research Laboratories that operates at the intersection of scientific delivery and core platform development. AI4D’s mission is to connecting scientists to petabyte\-scale data through natural language interf</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist II - Avathon</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2b79f4ac6055475e</link>
        <description>**Who We Are \&amp; Why Join Us**


**Avathon** is revolutionizing industrial AI with a powerful platform that enables businesses to harness the full potential of their operational data. Our technology seamlessly integrates and contextualizes siloed datasets, providing a 360\-degree operational view that enhances decision\-making and efficiency. With advanced capabilities like digital twins, natural language processing, normal behavior modeling, and machine vision, we create real\-time virtual replicas of physical assets, enabling predictive maintenance, performance simulation, and operational optimization. Our AI\-driven models empower companies with scalable solutions for anomaly detection, performance forecasting, and asset lifetime extension—all tailored to the complexities of industrial environments.



**Cutting\-Edge AI Innovation** – Join a team at the forefront of AI, developing groundbreaking solutions that shape the future.  

**High\-Growth Environment** – Thrive in a fast\-sca</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist I - Avathon</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81f56a55e57fefe0</link>
        <description>**Who We Are \&amp; Why Join Us**


**Avathon** is revolutionizing industrial AI with a powerful platform that enables businesses to harness the full potential of their operational data. Our technology seamlessly integrates and contextualizes siloed datasets, providing a 360\-degree operational view that enhances decision\-making and efficiency. With advanced capabilities like digital twins, natural language processing, normal behavior modeling, and machine vision, we create real\-time virtual replicas of physical assets, enabling predictive maintenance, performance simulation, and operational optimization. Our AI\-driven models empower companies with scalable solutions for anomaly detection, performance forecasting, and asset lifetime extension—all tailored to the complexities of industrial environments.



**Cutting\-Edge AI Innovation** – Join a team at the forefront of AI, developing groundbreaking solutions that shape the future.  

**High\-Growth Environment** – Thrive in a fast\-sca</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Director, Head of Clinical Statistical Programming - Jazz Pharmaceuticals</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4da42b6503465781</link>
        <description>**If you are a current Jazz employee please apply via the Internal Career site.**



Jazz Pharmaceuticals is a global biopharma company whose purpose is to innovate to transform the lives of patients and their families. We are dedicated to developing life\-changing medicines for people with serious diseases — often with limited or no therapeutic options. We have a diverse portfolio of marketed medicines, including leading therapies for sleep disorders and epilepsy, and a growing portfolio of cancer treatments. Our patient\-focused and science\-driven approach powers pioneering research and development advancements across our robust pipeline of innovative therapeutics in oncology and neuroscience. Jazz is headquartered in Dublin, Ireland with research and development laboratories, manufacturing facilities and employees in multiple countries committed to serving patients worldwide. Please visit www.jazzpharmaceuticals.com for more information.


The Senior Director, Head of Clinical Stat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist - Payment - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=372a5aa10d953557</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
Overall Purpose  

  

This position is a senior technical role within Data Sciences. This role assumes analytic project ownership, starting from conceptualization and design. Oversees the process of development, implementation and enhancement of the analytically derived models</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Spatial Data Analyst - Temporary - Northeastern University</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c15a5b993c04c378</link>
        <description>**About the Opportunity**

**Job Summary**
===============

Conduct spatial analysis and statistical modeling to evaluate cannabis cultivation density patterns across tribal, private, and boundary lands. Develop refined sampling grids, analyze temporal trends, and produce visualizations and reports to support cannabis remediation research on tribal lands.


**Minimum Qualifications**
==========================

* ### **Knowledge of spatial statistics, GIS analysis, and statistical modeling using R.**
* ### **Ability to integrate and analyze complex environmental datasets; as normally acquired through a Master's degree in Geography, Environmental Science, Statistics, or related field**
* ### **2\-3 years of relevant experience.**

**Key Responsibilities**
========================

* Refine sampling grid methodology and develop statewide grids that improve land\-type resolution while maintaining privacy requirements. Conduct spatial distribution analysis of tribal and private lands and v</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Product Analytics - Gallup</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c4d58f6128c6ddc6</link>
        <description>**Shape product road maps and strategies with data\-driven analytics and insights.**



As a senior/principal data scientist focused on product analytics for our Technology team, you'll work with product managers, engineers and designers to define success, validate hypotheses, and measure user behavior and product performance.



We're looking for self\-driven, curious analytics partners who thrive in ambiguity, learn continually and help teams accelerate decision\-making.



At Gallup, our analytics reflect what the world is thinking, empower millions of people to thrive using their strengths, and help leaders create exceptional workplaces. If you want your work to influence products that bring that mission to life, we'd love to hear from you.


**What You'll Do**


* Partner with product teams early in discovery, road map discussions and launch planning to turn goals into measurable outcomes
* Define and govern success metrics by building trusted metric definitions, dashboards and da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Maps Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3aa1994b2bca8bde</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in C\+\+ and SQL.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* Experience with Deep Learning.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or a related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience with Python.
* Experience with ML model fine\-tuning, evaluation, and performance optimization for user\-facing systems.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of user</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Preparedness - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2a0d07656da4ae30</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

The Preparedness team is an important part of the
  
  

Safety Systems
  
  

org at OpenAI, and is guided by OpenAI’s
  
  

Preparedness Framework
  
  

.
  
  

Frontier AI models have the potential to benefit all of humanity, but also pose increasingly severe risks. To ensure that AI promotes positive change, the Preparedness team helps us prepare for the development of increasingly capable frontier AI models. This team is tasked with identifying, tracking, and preparing for catastrophic risks related to frontier AI models.
  
  

**The mission of the Preparedness team is to:**  

Closely monitor and predict the evolving capabilities of frontier AI systems, with an eye towards misuse risks whose impact could be catastrophic to our society
  
  

Ensure we have concrete procedures, infrastructure and partnerships to mitigate these risks and to safely handle the development of powerful AI systems
  
  

Preparedness tightly connects capability assessment, eval</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df0d976afd057a4</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California; San Diego, California; San Francisco, California **Job ID** 19894
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across discipline</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Shield - Box</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=88492e295288a867</link>
        <description>**WHAT IS BOX?**



Box (NYSE:BOX) is the leader in Intelligent Content Management. Our platform enables organizations to fuel collaboration, manage the entire content lifecycle, secure critical content, and transform business workflows with enterprise AI. We help companies thrive in the new AI\-first era of business. Founded in 2005, Box simplifies work for leading global organizations, including JLL, Morgan Stanley, and Nationwide. Box is headquartered in Redwood City, CA, with offices across the United States, Europe, and Asia.



By joining Box, you will have the unique opportunity to continue driving our platform forward. Content powers how we work. It's the billions of files and information flowing across teams, departments, and key business processes every single day: contracts, invoices, employee records, financials, product specs, marketing assets, and more. Our mission is to bring intelligence to the world of content management and empower our customers to completely transfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Reinforcement Learning - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=013d92448b2ca44d</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
------------------



Come help us build the world's most reliable local e\-commerce platform for on\-demand last\-mile grocery and retail delivery! We're looking for an experienced senior machine learning engineer to help us develop the cutting\-edge reinforcement learning models that power DoorDash's growing grocery and retail business.


**About the Role**
------------------



We're looking for a passionate Applied Machine Learning expert to join our team. As a Reinforcement Learning expert, you'll be conceptualizing, designing, implementing, and validating algorithmic improvements to the reinforcement learning system at the heart of our fast\-growing grocery and retail delivery business. You will use our robust data and machine learning infrastructure to implement new ML solutions to make our product selection and inventory information more accurate and real time, as well as help Dasher efficiency. We're looking for someone with a command of production\-level ma</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=60720148c44c7f1d</link>
        <description>Job Description
  
We are seeking a Senior ML Engineer to join our team of dedicated machine learning and software engineers. This role involves timely engineering, system development, ML model assessment, constructing data pipelines, composing prototypes, evaluation, operationalization.
  
  

Looking for individuals skilled in classical and deep learning, able to build and implement ML solutions for production environments. If you thrive on delivering innovative customer features, adopting new technologies, and contributing to high\-visibility projects, this role may be a good match. The atmosphere is dynamic, fast\-paced, creative, collaborative, and data\-centric.
  
What you’ll do
  
  

Contribute to the backend services supporting ML and Generative\-AI functionalities.
  
  

Build, develop, implement, and evaluate machine learning models using classical and deep learning approaches, as well as GenAI.
  
  

Collaborate with cross\-functional teams to integrate ML solutions into</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sensing ML Algorithm Engineer - HID - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d79d2420c3dd4e30</link>
        <description>Join the engineering team creating next\-generation touch interfaces for iPad, Pencil, iPhone, Watch and more. We are an eclectic group with backgrounds in signal processing, machine learning, computer science, estimation algorithms, human factors, and more, dedicated to inventing new ways of interacting with Apple products and shipping amazing products every year.  

  

We are looking for a signal processing and machine learning engineer with C/C\+\+ implementation skill. Your good communication skills, and ability to drive discussions with cross\-functional teams would come in very handy. Have you gained any experience with user interface design or graphics programming skills as well? That’s great! It will further help broaden your role and effectiveness in this position.  

  

To summarize, you will be working on innovative projects and will be responsible for productizing algorithmic solutions, and you will be part of the team shipping products to millions of users every year.  
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Staff Machine Learning Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=29948ca580d32a2c</link>
        <description>Join a team at the forefront of ML infrastructure and generative AI, where data and model workflows come together to enable the next generation of intelligent experiences on Apple products and services. We focus on building robust systems that connect scalable data pipelines with advanced ML workflows to accelerate the development of real\-world AI applications.  

  

**Description**  

  

The ADP ML Data Platform team enables future Apple intelligent products by providing Apple engineers with cutting edge ML technologies, large scale compute and data systems specifically designed for machine learning.  

  

You will build the data foundation that powers ML training across Apple. Our team enables governed, scalable sharing of text and multimodal datasets, ensuring teams can safely discover, access, and use high\-quality data for training.  

  

We focus on turning raw data into usable training assets with streamlining data preparation, enabling rapid iteration, and supporting advan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=71572c5f6ccbf091</link>
        <description>The Siri team is creating groundbreaking technology for large scale systems, spoken language, machine learning, and LLMs to enable better conversational experience with Siri. The features we create are redefining how hundreds of millions of people use their computers and mobile devices to fulfill their requirements and find what they are looking for. As part of the Siri team, you will work with the talent dense team who crafted the intelligent assistant that helps users get things done \- just by asking.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a machine learning engineer at Siri, you will be responsible for doing development and research in the deep learning field and building the most advanced natural language and conversation understanding systems. You should be passionate about working with software and platform engineers to integrate the models on\-device and improve natural language understanding ability of Siri. Excellent interpersonal skills will be required to coordinate work across m</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Backend/Data Engineer: Agentic Workflows, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5acacc4e6b5650a1</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there’s no telling what you could accomplish.  

  

Do you want to make Siri and Apple products more intelligent for our users? The Siri \&amp; Information Intelligence team is building groundbreaking technology to revolutionize how users interact with Apple devices.  

  

As part of this group, you will contribute to build the infrastructure to power the development of multi\-modal agentic workflows.  

  

**Description**  

  

We design, build and maintain infrastructure to support agentic workflows for Siri. Our team is in charge of data generation, introspection and evaluation frameworks that are key to efficiently developing foundation models and agentic workflows for Siri applications. In this team you will have the opportunity to work at the intersection of with cutting edge foundation models an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Backend/Data Engineer: Agentic Workflows, Siri Core Modeling - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9bd2215e3360dc3b</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, great ideas have a way of becoming great products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there’s no telling what you could accomplish.  

  

Do you want to make Siri and Apple products more intelligent for our users? The Siri \&amp; Information Intelligence team is building groundbreaking technology to revolutionize how users interact with Apple devices.  

  

As part of this group, you will contribute to build the infrastructure to power the development of multi\-modal agentic workflows.  

  

**Description**  

  

We design, build and maintain infrastructure to support agentic workflows for Siri. Our team is in charge of data generation, introspection and evaluation frameworks that are key to efficiently developing foundation models and agentic workflows for Siri applications. In this team you will have the opportunity to work at the intersection of with cutting edge foundation models an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Developer, Machine Learning - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0f1e9cbbaa334324</link>
        <description>This posting is for a new vacancy.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Waterloo, ON, Canada**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in software development using one or more programming languages.
* Experience in one or more of the following: video compression, video processing, video encoding, or video decoding.
* 2 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools, building production quality Machine Learning (ML) systems and infrastructure.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience with image processing, computer vision, or machine learning applications.
* Experience in one or more of the following: video compression, video processing, signal/image pro</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Search Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f62798825ba5e785</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Cambridge, MA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 3 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 6 years of work experience with a PhD degree.
* Experience articulating business questions and using mathematical techniques to arrive at an answer using available data.
* Experience translating analysis results into business recommendati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineering NERD, AI.x - Charles Schwab</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3b5b02de118510ad</link>
        <description>**Your opportunity**
--------------------

  

At Schwab, you will build a rewarding career while making a difference in the lives of our millions of clients. Here, innovative thinking meets creative problem solving as we work together to challenge the status quo. We believe in the power of collaboration and value being together in the office, which is why this role is based on\-site in our San Francisco office. Joining Schwab means joining a company committed to transforming the financial industry and putting clients at the center of everything we do.  

Schwab’s AI Strategy \&amp; Transformation team, known as AI.x, is the central hub for Artificial Intelligence at Schwab. We are an integrated product, engineering, strategy and risk team, all based in San Francisco. We help set the enterprise vision for AI, invest in the most promising opportunities, and accelerate delivery across the company. We also build the core platform that powers AI at scale and explore next\-generation GenAI effo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Satff Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5df7d07727627e4e</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refine innovative growth strategies. Your expertise—especially in causal inference and advanced analytics—will be instrumental in surfacing critical insights and translating them into actionable hypotheses that fuel sustained customer and revenue growth.

 **Responsibilities**


* Drive Business Strategy through Data \- Translate business problems into analytical frameworks. Connect data across multiple function</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Computer Vision - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f873a17a79fe7304</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
==================



Come help us build the world's most reliable on\-demand, logistics engine for last\-mile grocery and retail delivery! We're looking for an experienced senior machine learning engineer to help us develop the cutting\-edge Computer Vision models that power DoorDash's growing grocery and retail business.


**About the Role**
==================



We're looking for a passionate Applied Machine Learning expert to join our team. As a Computer Vision expert, you'll be conceptualizing, designing, implementing, and validating algorithmic improvements to the computer vision system at the heart of our fast\-growing grocery and retail delivery business. You will use our robust data and machine learning infrastructure to implement new ML solutions to make our product knowledge graph and inventory information more accurate and real time, as well as help Dasher efficiency. We're looking for someone with a command of production\-level machine learning and exper</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Lead AI Engineer - Capital One</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=456d0f19df5de27e</link>
        <description>Senior Lead AI Engineer**Overview:**


At Capital One, we are creating responsible and reliable AI systems, changing banking for good. For years, Capital One has been an industry leader in using machine learning to create real\-time, personalized customer experiences. Our investments in technology infrastructure and world\-class talent — along with our deep experience in machine learning — position us to be at the forefront of enterprises leveraging AI. From informing customers about unusual charges to answering their questions in real time, our applications of AI \&amp; ML are bringing humanity and simplicity to banking. We are committed to continuing to build world\-class applied science and engineering teams to deliver our industry leading capabilities with breakthrough product experiences and scalable, high\-performance AI infrastructure. At Capital One, you will help bring the transformative power of emerging AI capabilities to reimagine how we serve our customers and businesses who h</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Experienced Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd02371cc6e6817c</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Driven by curiosity, you are a reliable, contributing member of a team. In our fast\-paced environment, you are expected to adapt to working with a variety o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Experienced Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=68db4a7fee83b003</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Driven by curiosity, you are a reliable, contributing member of a team. In our fast\-paced environment, you are expected to adapt to working with a variety o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:33:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
