<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI/ML Engineer-5 - Realign</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2b37a599430fcece</link>
        <description>San Francisco, California 94016 Posted February 25th, 2026
 Looking for more job opportunities? Click here!


  
Job Type: Contract


Job Category: IT


Job Description


**Role: Sr. AI/ML Engineer**

* **Experience** – 10\+ Years
* **Location** \- San Francisco, CA – LOCALS Only

**Required Qualifications**  

* Deep expertise in Machine Learning, Generative AI, LLMs, RAG, and AI orchestration.
* Strong understanding of Azure OpenAI, AWS Bedrock, or similar platforms.
* Experience deploying AI in regulated environments.
* Hands\-on architectural and engineering leadership capabilities.
* Strong communication skills with VP/Senior Director stakeholders.


 Preferred Qualifications  

* 12\+ years in AI/ML, data engineering, or digital transformation.
* Prior experience leading enterprise AI programs.
* Utility domain experience (wildfire, grid, operations).
* Knowledge of Responsible AI frameworks (NIST AI RMF, ISO 42001\).

  

**Roles \&amp; Responsibilities**  

**Role Overview**  

Uti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Intel and AI Intern - NetApp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6db7384c8151e55b</link>
        <description>**Own Every Moment at NetApp**


At NetApp, your ideas power innovation. We lead in intelligent data infrastructure—delivering unified storage, integrated data services, and solutions that help organizations unlock the full potential of their data, from AI to multicloud.


Ready to innovate and contribute to our path to $10B? Here, you'll collaborate with passionate teams, tackle real\-world challenges, and see your impact in how customers transform and grow. If you're ready to bring curiosity, creativity, and drive to every moment, NetApp is where your journey begins.


  
**Job Summary**
---------------


Organization Overview


NetApp storage systems hold 70 Exabytes of enterprise data. The Data Intelligence and AI Business Unit builds vision is to bring AI to data. We build platforms and services that enable enterprises to operationalize this data and AI at scale within the compliance boundaries of data. AIDE (AI Data Engine) is a core data platform product within the BU, focused o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ML Ops Intern - Mercedes-Benz Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d57da6647a38babb</link>
        <description>At Mercedes\-Benz Research \&amp; Development North America (MBRDNA), we are committed to delivering world\-class automotive technologies that push the boundaries of what is possible. Our teams of highly skilled engineers and designers use cutting\-edge software and technology, to enhance the driving experience and reduce environmental impact.  

The Mercedes\-Benz AI Experiences team is seeking a Machine Learning Engineering Intern to join our ML Product Development Team for Summer 2026\. In this role, you will help enhance our MLOps platform to support a diverse range of use cases powering AI projects that shape the future of Mercedes\-Benz vehicles. You will contribute to the development of ML pipelines, tools, and platform capabilities that enable experimentation, CI/CD, deployment, verification, validation, and monitoring of production models, while upholding strong data privacy standards and responsible AI principles. Working closely with cross\-functional development teams, you will</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Data for Perception Machine Learning - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=65a3faa19fa4d8ee</link>
        <description>We are seeking an experienced and highly skilled data scientist to join the Perception Data and Labeling team.. The team is responsible for training and evaluation data powering the perception (vision, lidar, and other modalities) ML models at Zoox. The candidate will work alongside data ops partners, ML engineers, software developers, and data engineers to improve model performance through high quality human\- and auto\-labeled data.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Define and implement scalable data quality measures across complex, multimodal data labeling pipelines
* Drive data\-centric ML model improvements to achieve critical Zoox milestones
* Support an org\-wide data ontology and class structure for perception models
* Determine trade\-offs and integrations between human\-labeled, human\-in\-the\-loop, and zero\-shot autolabeled data
* Build metrics to quantify labeling throughput, capacity, and annotator/vendor quality

### **Qualifications:**

* Master's or PhD degree in a f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Earner Growth), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e10955047184df03</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Earner Growth team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

Have you ever ordered a car service on Uber, and when the ride arrives, wondered how it got to you so fast? Ever ordered food on UberEats and wondered where the driver was before receiving your order and how long it took to get to the restaurant or if your order was ready when the courier arrived? Ever wondered why your grocery delivery from Uber always has the best apple picked? If so, Uber is for you. In our Sciences division, we strive to make magic within Uber's marketplace. This requires judgment to make difficult trade\-offs, blending algorith</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Ads &amp; Offer), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=725e0d3e0220dcf1</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Ads \&amp; Offer team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of a Scientist, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

Have you ever ordered a car service on Uber, and when the ride arrives, wondered how it got to you so fast? Ever ordered food on UberEats and wondered where the driver was before receiving your order and how long it took to get to the restaurant or if your order was ready when the courier arrived? Ever wondered why your grocery delivery from Uber always has the best apple picked? If so, Uber is for you. In our Sciences division, we strive to make magic within Uber's marketplace. This requires judgment to make difficult trade\-offs, blending algorithms with human resourceful</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (UberEats Courier Pricing), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e04bd1b2b7801fb6</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Uber Eats Marketplace team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Team**  

  

The Uber Eats Marketplace team is the heart of the Uber Eats business. We build the platform and products that power the magical experience of connecting eaters, couriers, and restaurants. As a critical component of this ecosystem, the Courier Pricing team is responsible for the complex systems that determine courier payouts on every Uber Eats delivery worldwide.
  

  

Our mission is to build and refine a fully automated pricing system that optimizes our three\-sided marketplace for consumers, couriers, and merchants. We leverage sophisti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - VSCO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=da095374fa32049c</link>
        <description>**About VSCO**



VSCO (pronounced vis–co) is a platform that equips photographers with the tools, community, and exposure they need to expand creatively and professionally. VSCO maintains a rich and authentic creative environment that serves photographers at all levels – preserving a home for creative opportunity, inspiration, and connection. Our mission is to champion photographers so they can make it. We empower photographers to connect with other creatives and businesses with our suite of creative tools that spans from mobile to desktop and across our global community.



We are looking for people who are driven and demonstrate initiative in taking our company mission to the next level. Employees here have the opportunity to make a big impact, and believe that when we build together, we achieve stronger outcomes than we could alone.



Our values are critical pillars to our team culture and shape the way we hire. Read more about what you can expect when working at VSCO on our Caree</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship, AI Performance Engineer, Performance Optimization (Summer 2026) - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8ce700aa5d8b6518</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Consider before submitting an application:


This position is expected to start May 2026 and continue through summer term (ending approximately August 2026 or later, if available). We ask for a minimum of 12 weeks, full\-time (40 hours/week) and on\-site, for most internships. Our internship program is for students who are actively enrolled in an academic program. Recent graduates seeking employment after graduation and not returning to school should apply for full\-time positions, not internships.


International Students: If your work authorization is through CPT, please consult your school on your ability to work 40 hours per week before applying. You must be able to work 40 hours per week on\-site. Many students will be limited to part\-time during the academic year.  

  



The Performance Optimization team takes research models and makes them run efficiently on Tesla's AI\-ASICs, powering Autopilot and Optimus. This role sits at the intersection of AI research</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML Services- Data Platform Engineer - GSK</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a25ec63d2a45d72c</link>
        <description>**Site Name:** South San Francisco 611 Gateway Blvd, Cambridge 300 Technology Square, Seattle Sixth Ave  

**Posted Date:** Feb 24 2026  

At GSK we see a world in which advanced applications of Machine Learning and AI will allow us to develop transformational medicines using the power of genetics, functional genomics, and machine learning. AI will also play a role in how we diagnose and use medicines to enable everyone to do more feel better and live longer. It is an ambitious vision that will require the development of products at the cutting edge of Machine Learning and AI.

  

We're looking for a highly skilled individual contributor who can consistently take a poorly defined business or technical problem, work it to a well\-defined problem/specification, and execute on it at a high level. They have a strong focus on metrics, both in the domains of system health/performance and the impact of their work. They are a model for the team on best practices for software development in ge</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr ML Ops Engineer - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=daf4a4241dc4709a</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Forward Deployed Robotics Engineer - Medra</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=347e6c832898b756</link>
        <description>**What We're Building:**
We have been quietly building the foundational layers of our Physical AI Scientist platform:  

 Physical AI that can operate scientific instruments with human\-level dexterity.  

 Scientific AI that can analyze results, reason about next steps, and close the loop autonomously.


This is an incredibly ambitious mission, but we believe that a team of ambitious people with high ownership can accomplish incredible things.

**The Team:**

* We’re a team of passionate, mission\-driven engineers from companies like Tesla, Amazon, SpaceX, and Neuralink. We’re collaborative and love moving fast, both with our product and on team trips skiing or go\-karting!
* As a team, we love nerding out about engineering and robotics — plus other topics like race cars or cooking. We like learning new things and then sharing our new knowledge with each other.
* Our team is opinionated and straightforward. We don’t mind intense discussions about design tradeoffs. If we have arguments</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Full Stack Software Engineer - Summer 2026 Internship - Medra</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ec13e877ffe52786</link>
        <description>**About the Role:**Paid Summer 2026 Internship (Jun. \- Aug., dates flexible). Candidates must work full\-time, in\-person at our San Francisco office located in the Mission.


**What We're Building:**


We have been quietly building the foundational layers of our Physical AI Scientist platform:  

 Physical AI that can operate scientific instruments with human\-level dexterity.  

 Scientific AI that can analyze results, reason about next steps, and close the loop autonomously.


This is an incredibly ambitious mission, but we believe that a team of ambitious people with high ownership can accomplish incredible things.

**The Team:**

* We’re a team of passionate, mission\-driven engineers from companies like Tesla, Amazon, SpaceX, and Neuralink. We’re collaborative and love moving fast, both with our product and on team trips skiing or go\-karting!
* As a team, we love nerding out about engineering and robotics — plus other topics like race cars or cooking. We like learning new thing</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, GPU Performance - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1cb81fad4b35b3e8</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Process Engineering Intern - Summer 2026 - Lam Research</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a21df53bf7ee40f1</link>
        <description>Requisition ID**194776**
Date posted**02/24/2026**
Work Location Model**On\-site**
Work Location**Fremont\-CA**
Work Country**United States****The group you’ll be a part of**
---------------------------------

  

The Office of the CTO is where innovation takes center stage. We inspire our global technical community to take on grand challenges, understand emerging trends, identify the critical inflections, and drive our sustainability, Environment, Social, and Governance (ESG) practices that will define the next generation of semiconductors and continued impact.

**The impact you’ll make**
--------------------------



In this role you will directly contribute to Lam Research’s Aether product group and process development efforts. You will work directly with experienced process and product development engineers developing the Aether products and process. Your work will lead to improvements in the equipment and systems that Lam provides to semiconductor manufacturers worldwide.

**What </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Machine Learning - Syntiant Corp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=342cdf5b1f51abde</link>
        <description>Syntiant Corp., a leader in the high\-growth AI software and semiconductor solutions space, is looking for an experienced and talented **Senior Software Engineer** to take on a critical role with expansive responsibilities in the Machine Learning team.


As a **Senior Software Engineer**, you will own and train computer vision models to run on edge devices. You will be responsible for ensuring the models run to spec and meet the customer needs. Ultimately, you will get the opportunity to apply machine learning in real world applications and see your work driving the latest edge AI devices.


**Requirements**
----------------

**Qualifications, Education, and Experience Required:**

* Masters in Computer Science/Engineering or related field.
* 5\+ years of experience developing and deploying ML models for vision applications.
* Strong C\+\+ and Python experience.
* Experience with ML frameworks (e.g. TensorFlow, PyTorch).
* Experience working in large, complex codebases.
* Experience wi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Machine Learning - Syntiant Corp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=845178e882aff603</link>
        <description>**Summary Description****:**


Syntiant Corp., a leader in the high\-growth AI software and semiconductor solutions space, is looking for an experienced and talented **Senior Software Engineer** to take on a critical role with expansive responsibilities in the Machine Learning team.


As a **Senior Software Engineer**, you will own and train computer vision models to run on edge devices. You will be responsible for ensuring the models run to spec and meet the customer needs. Ultimately, you will get the opportunity to apply machine learning in real world applications and see your work driving the latest edge AI devices.


**Requirements**

**Qualifications, Education, and Experience Required:**

* Masters in Computer Science/Engineering or related field.
* 5\+ years of experience developing and deploying ML models for vision applications.
* Strong C\+\+ and Python experience.
* Experience with ML frameworks (e.g. TensorFlow, PyTorch).
* Experience working in large, complex codebases.
*</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Resident - AI for Lab Automation (Early Stage Biology Project) - X Development</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=982b329352397df7</link>
        <description>InternshipMountain View, CA



**About us:**



X is Alphabet’s moonshot factory. We are a diverse group of inventors and entrepreneurs who build and launch technologies that aim to improve the lives of millions, even billions, of people. Our goal: 10x impact on the world’s most intractable problems, not just 10% improvement. We approach projects that have the aspiration and riskiness of research with the speed and ambition of a startup.


**About the team:**



The Bio Design Kitchen (BioDK) is X’s state\-of\-the\-art biology and chemistry lab that empowers Xers to tackle unique challenges to launch moonshots in biology and chemistry. Our team of resident scientists and engineers are experts at turning concepts into reality, whether it's rapid prototyping, in\-house development, or brainstorming novel solutions.


**About the role:**



We are looking for an exceptional PhD student who has experience in applied ML and a high\-level proficiency in programming to join our team for 6 mon</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer, Cash Line - Upstart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e2c28785b5b8428</link>
        <description>**About Upstart**



At Upstart, we're united by a mission that matters: to radically reduce the cost and complexity of borrowing for all Americans. Every day, we bring creativity, experimentation, and advanced AI to reshape access to credit, helping millions move forward financially with clarity and confidence.



As the leading AI lending marketplace, we partner with banks and credit unions to expand access to affordable credit through technology that's both radically intelligent and deeply human. Our platform runs over one million predictions per borrower using more than 1,800 signals, powering smarter, fairer decisions for millions of customers. But the numbers only hint at the impact. Every idea, every voice, and every contribution moves us closer to a world where credit never stands between people and their financial progress.



We're proudly digital\-first, giving most Upstarters the flexibility to do their best work from wherever they thrive, alongside teammates across 80\+ ci</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager III, Storage Systems and NPI, Cloud AI - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d0038faa55cb6382</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in program management.
* Experience in storage systems or infrastructure systems.
* Experience with new product introduction (NPI) across software or hardware products (architecture, development, launch).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of experience managing cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.
* Experience with NPI development, firmware, driving software quality and process transformation.
* Experience in software engineering as a developer or development manager, with an understanding of software development processes, tools, software test/qualification, release methodologies.
* Excellent investigative, problem\-solving, negotiation and organizational skills.
* Excellent program management skills, with the ability to successfully drive and land software programs.
* Excellent verbal and written communication and presentation sk</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Search, Speech Translation - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0011dcb0b2641eec</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in Python, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience developing and evaluating Machine Translation (MT) models and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience developing, deploying, and maintaining Machine Learning (ML) infrastructure.
* 1 year of experience conducting quantitative and qualitative evaluations of systems.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience with full stack development, including back\-end (Kotlin / C\+\+) and front\-end Android UI toolkits.
* Experience with speech recognition, translation or test to speech processing.
* Experience implementing and optimizing automated evaluation pipelines for data and models.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**Ab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Engineer, Machine Learning Accelerators - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c755f557a39c7937</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in manufacturing.
* Experience in PCBA (Printed Circuit Board Assembly) and related system assembly.
* Experience in design for manufacturability and serviceability.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Electrical, Mechanical, Industrial, Materials, or a related engineering field.
* 10 years of experience at a company developing supply chains in manufacturing and testing.
* Experience working with Original Device Manufacturers (ODMs), contract manufacturers and component suppliers for data center server accelerator products (GPU, FPGA or ASIC).
* Experience working with contract manufacturers and suppliers to drive root cause analysis, corrective actions and continuous process improvements.
* Experience of bring\-up or bench testing hardware in a lab environment.
* Knowledge of SQL queries and scripting in Python or Bash.

**Abou</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, GenAI, Device Portal - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7ce02c09d41216a1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products, and 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 5 years of experience leading ML design and optimizing ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 2 years of experience with GenAI techniques (e.g., LLMs, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) or with GenAI\-related concepts (e.g., language modeling, computer vision).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technical direction.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex organization involving cross\-functional, or cross\-busi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a5aabc4ae0be9156</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Intuit is looking for innovative and hands\-on Senior AI Scientist to join the Intuit AI team.


This team embeds artificial intelligence and machine learning into our product portfolio and business


to create smarter products, improve anti\-fraud and security and enhance customer care. Come join our


collaborative and creative group of AI scientists and machine learning engineers and build models that


directly affect hundreds of thousands of our customers. In this role you will be building and deploying


machine learning models using both analytical algorithms and deep learning approaches.

 **Responsibilities**

  

Perform hands\-on data analysis and modeling with huge data sets


Apply data mining, NLP , and machine learning (both supervised and unsupervised) to improve


relevance and personalization algorithms


Work side\-by\-side with product managers, software engineers, and designers in designing


experiments and minimum viable products


Dis</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Software Engineer - Matching ML Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fa75f948a6490ab7</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching ML Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
* Building a highly scalable ml systems \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Evolving the ML platform for matching \- enabling real\-time inference, model de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II, Matching Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2aafb69e9aa6afc2</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
  

* Building a highly scalable matching platform \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Designing extensible architectures \- creating a modular and flexible pl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Software Engineer - Matching ML Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=89146ec20f6cf6d6</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching ML Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
* Building a highly scalable ml systems \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Evolving the ML platform for matching \- enabling real\-time inference, model de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II, Matching Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7fb43f34545fb472</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
  

* Building a highly scalable matching platform \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Designing extensible architectures \- creating a modular and flexible pl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Controls Systems Engineer, Machine Learning, Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=df41500635df1342</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Science, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience designing and implementing controls systems and dynamic modeling.
* 5 years of experience with Machine Learning and construction of algorithms.
* Experience with programming in C, Python, MATLAB, or Shell.
* Experience with software development or prototyping within a business or enterprise setting.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD in Engineering, Science, or a related field.
* Experience with modeling/statistical software such as TensorFlow, Simulink, R, or MATLAB Machine Learning Toolbox.
* Experience with digital signal processing and time\-series analysis. Experience with optimization, Linear Programming, and Convex Optimization.
* Experience with dynamic system analysis, feedback control systems, and optimal control.
* Experience with developing AI/ML prototypes and conducting full\-cycle modeling experiments within</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6949073a57771923</link>
        <description>Category Data


Location Mountain View, California


Job ID 19909


  
Company Overview


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


Job Overview


Intuit is looking for innovative and hands\-on Senior AI Scientist to join the Intuit AI team.


This team embeds artificial intelligence and machine learning into our product portfolio and business


to create smarter products, improve anti\-fraud and security and enhance customer care. Come join our


collaborative and creative group of AI scientists and machine learning engineers and build models that


directly affect hundreds of thousands of our customers. In this role you will be building and deploying
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Reliability Engineer - EV Powertrain Systems - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94fa6b0d149c33e3</link>
        <description>At Zoox, we have set the goal to provide our customers with the highest level of safety and a best\-in\-class experience while using our fully autonomous vehicles. You will work with a team of world\-class engineers with diverse backgrounds, such as robotics, control, and vehicle engineering, to deliver vehicle performance using advanced virtual tools and methodologies. In taking on the virtual and physical durability development, you will predict where the vehicle is within its lifecycle and define maintenance, monitoring, and optimization strategies. Working in a startup environment gives you the chance to lead technically, influence system design, and make a meaningful impact on the final product.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Establish and refine system\- and component\-level reliability targets for the electric drive unit (EDU), high\-voltage battery (HVB), and HV to LV Power Distribution (DCDC and HV harnesses) in collaboration with Vehicle Systems Engineering and cross\-fun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer - Cargomatic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e4eebde6b6cf3dae</link>
        <description>Senior Data Architect – Data Engineering



Location: San Francisco, CA  

Reports To: VP of Engineering  

FLSA Status: Exempt  

Employment Type: Full\-Time  

Compensation: $140,000 – $160,000 annually (based on experience)



About Cargomatic



Cargomatic is transforming the local trucking industry with cutting\-edge technology that connects shippers and carriers in real time. Every product that humans build, grow, or sell has spent time on a truck. Local trucking is the lifeblood of every regional economy, yet this $82 billion industry still relies heavily on outdated systems. Cargomatic is bringing transparency, efficiency, and intelligence to local freight through modern technology and data\-driven solutions.



We are solving complex, real\-world logistics problems every day. If you thrive in a fast\-paced environment, enjoy building scalable systems, and want to help shape the future of AI\-powered logistics, we'd love to meet you.



Position Summary



Cargomatic is seeking</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=573e03fe5896fe54</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer, Trainium Manufacturing, Quality &amp; Reliability - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fc23dac21c5358a7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability (MQR) Team is part of AWS Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider. As a Senior Reliability Engineer you will engage with an experienced cross\-disciplinary staff to conceive and design infrastructure technologies. You will work closely with an internal inter\-disciplinary team, and outside partners to drive key aspects of product definition, execution and test in manufacturing. A successful candidate will be responsive, flexible and able to succeed within an open collaborative peer environment. You will:  

  

* Be responsible for the test validation of future technologies.
* Drive manufacturing process improvements to address reliability issues and concerns.
* You will have a fundamental understanding of Reliability statistics/Reliability tests and/or solid understanding of computer systems to influence des</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Expedia Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f6610ed807a1c6f6</link>
        <description>Expedia Group brands power global travel for everyone, everywhere. We design cutting\-edge tech to make travel smoother and more memorable, and we create groundbreaking solutions for our partners. Our diverse, vibrant, and welcoming community is essential in driving our success.

**Why Join Us?**


To shape the future of travel, people must come first. Guided by our Values and Leadership Agreements, we foster an open culture where everyone belongs, differences are celebrated and know that when one of us wins, we all win.


We provide a full benefits package, including exciting travel perks, generous time\-off, parental leave, a flexible work model (with some pretty cool offices), and career development resources, all to fuel our employees' passion for travel and ensure a rewarding career journey. We’re building a more open world. Join us.

**Software Development Engineer III**

**Introduction to Team:**

Expedia Platform Technology teams partner with our Product teams to create innovat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Vehicle AI - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e8f6ef0a04cb5ae</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**Work Arrangement:**  

This role is categorized as hybrid/Remote. This means the successful candidate is expected to report to Mountain View, CA three times per week at minimum or other frequency dictated by the business or Remote, Washington location.


**The Role**

GM is looking to hire highly skilled and experienced Staff Software Engineers to join our team focused on developing cutting\-edge AI agents. This role involves leading the design, development, and deployment of robust, scalable, and intelligent software agents that drive innovation across our products and services. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of AI/ML principles, distributed systems, and a track record of technical leadership.


**What You'll Do**

* Lead the architecture and implementation of next\-generation AI agents, from conceptualization to production deployment.
* Drive technical direction and strategy for the AI agent platform, ensuring scalability, reliability, and p</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, DevOps - Moveworks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9aa0a68ebe3a9f9e</link>
        <description>DevOps Mountain View, CA Full Time


  
What You Will Do:



As a member of the DevOps team, you will be responsible for building and scaling the Moveworks AI cloud infrastructure and developer platform. As Moveworks grows fast, the infrastructure team is tasked with designing and operating reliable and resilient foundational services as well as frameworks that allow our product to scale seamlessly and our engineering teams to build customer facing features very rapidly.



We’re building a team that indexes on moving fast, solving challenging product/engineering problems and providing value to our customers. To be successful, you'll be partnering with machine learning, search, product, data, and full stack teams to identify, define and build elegant solutions. This is an opportunity to play an integral role at the fastest\-growing AI startup in its space.


* Closely work with platform, machine learning, search, data, and frontend teams, understand their DevOps and infrastructure need</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Zendesk</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b808411d8487a58f</link>
        <description>**Job Description**
-------------------

Role: Machine Learning Engineer


TBH\#:


Location: US  



  

Zendesk’s people have one goal in mind: to make Customer Experience better.  



  

The Enterprise Machine Learning team drives organizational value through scalable ML solutions and data\-driven insights, fundamentally changing how business decisions are made. We collaborate closely with stakeholders, applying the latest advances in machine learning, deep learning, and large language models (LLMs) to create highly impactful outcomes. Our commitment is to advance the state of AI, statistical modeling, and robust system design to enhance and expand our core business capabilities.


### **Role Overview**

As a Machine Learning Engineer, you will serve as a technical and strategic member within the team, driving the development and deployment of advanced data science and machine learning solutions—particularly those harnessing LLMs and deep learning. You will architect and scale ML s</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Infrastructure Software Engineer - KLA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=88aca83269910cc5</link>
        <description>Company Overview
KLA is a global leader in diversified electronics for the semiconductor manufacturing ecosystem. Virtually every electronic device in the world is produced using our technologies. No laptop, smartphone, wearable device, voice\-controlled gadget, flexible screen, VR device or smart car would have made it into your hands without us. KLA invents systems and solutions for the manufacturing of wafers and reticles, integrated circuits, packaging, printed circuit boards and flat panel displays. The innovative ideas and devices that are advancing humanity all begin with inspiration, research and development. KLA focuses more than average on innovation and we invest 15% of sales back into R\&amp;D. Our expert teams of physicists, engineers, data scientists and problem\-solvers work together with the world’s leading technology providers to accelerate the delivery of tomorrow’s electronic devices. Life here is exciting and our teams thrive on tackling really hard problems. There is n</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Hardware Validation Engineer, Servers, Compute, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3a9a43da681e3e10</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Physics, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience working in board level design and testing, or 3 years of experience with an advanced degree.
* Experience with lab equipment like scopes, BERTs and analyzers.
* Experience with servers and compute platform architecture.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's or PhD degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Physics, or a related field.
* Experience managing teams and providing technical leadership for complex programs.
* Experience in collecting and organizing data to reproduce results and explain what happened.
* System\-level understanding of server products including physical, functional, logical, mechanical, electrical, software, thermal and cooling.
* Understanding of high speed transceiver interfaces like PCIe (physical, DLL and transaction layer), and memory interfaces </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer C++, Level 4 - Snap Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fe29ec411050d5c1</link>
        <description>Snap Inc is a technology company. We believe the camera presents the greatest opportunity to improve the way people live and communicate. Snap contributes to human progress by empowering people to express themselves, live in the moment, learn about the world, and have fun together. The Company’s three core products are Snapchat, a visual messaging app that enhances your relationships with friends, family, and the world; Lens Studio, an augmented reality platform that powers AR across Snapchat and other services; and its AR glasses, Spectacles.
Snap Engineering teams build fun and technically sophisticated products that reach hundreds of millions of Snapchatters around the world, every day. We’re deeply committed to the well\-being of everyone in our global community, which is why our values are at the root of everything we do. We move fast, with precision, and always execute with privacy at the forefront.
We’re looking for a C\+\+ Software Engineer to join our ML Infrastructure team!
W</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Full Stack Engineer, Content Engineering Tools - GeForce NOW - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d02f60d0ea1588bc</link>
        <description>We are seeking a Senior Full Stack Engineer to help build and enhance content engineering tools for GeForce NOW at NVIDIA. If you're experienced with various front\-end and backend technologies, are a fast learner, and have a get\-things\-done mentality, we'd love to hear from you!
You will play a significant role in crafting and guiding the future of GeForce NOW content engineering tools for our Cloud Gaming Business.
What you will be doing:* Collaborate with a world\-class team to design software platforms for content engineering tools at NVIDIA.
* Work closely with our Product and Design teams to define feature specifications and build the next generation of content engineering tools.
* Design and develop high\-performance, complex, and responsive full\-stack applications.
* Engineer brand\-new UX using JavaScript/TypeScript/HTML5, CSS; with a strong emphasis on React and similar frameworks.
* Architect and implement scalable backend services and RESTful APIs using Python and Java.
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer - Hardware - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cd9385e96a4da420</link>
        <description>We're now looking for a Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer! NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to solve, that only we can tackle, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human imagination and intelligence. Make the choice to join our diverse team today!
As a Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer at NVIDIA, you'll verify the design and implementation of our cutting edge SerDes IPs. This ground breaking technology will enable and accelerate gaming, artificial intelligence, deep learning, and autonomous driving. We have put together a best\-in\-class team that delivers IPs that will be consumed b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Neural Graphics Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=43ccee2279892053</link>
        <description>Computer graphics is experiencing its most exciting transformation in decades. Neural techniques are reshaping how we render, simulate, and create visual content in real time — and we're just getting started.
At NVIDIA, our Neural Graphics team builds technologies at the intersection of AI and real\-time rendering. We reach millions of developers and creators through products like Alpasim, open platforms like Slang, our shader language and compiler for portable GPU programming. We work on hard, meaningful problems with curiosity and collaboration — and we're looking for a Neural Graphics Engineer to grow with us. This is an opportunity to learn from some of the most accomplished people in graphics and AI, and to make a meaningful impact early in your career!
What You'll Be Doing:* Implement and optimize neural graphics techniques within real\-time rendering pipelines
* Prototype neural rendering, differentiable graphics, and generative 3D approaches
* Collaborate across teams to move i</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Recruiter, AI/ML Research - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8d6b77a5eacdd5ef</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

OpenAI’s mission is to build safe artificial general intelligence (AGI) that benefits all of humanity. Achieving this requires bringing the world’s most exceptional talent under one roof to push the boundaries of what’s possible.
  
  

Our Research Recruiting team plays a critical role in this effort. We are an embedded part of the research organization, working side by side with our research staff to deeply understand evolving priorities, build trust, and strategically shape the future of OpenAI’s talent.
  
  

About the Role
  
  

You will own and execute long\-term talent strategies to identify, engage, and recruit many of the world’s leading and emerging AI researchers, research engineers, and technical scientists working at the frontier of machine learning. This is not a traditional execution\-focused recruiting role.
  
  

You will operate as a strategic partner to OpenAI’s research staff, helping define hiring priorities, shape search strategy, influenc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer – VLM/LLM Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0df07204f739042b</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES. NEW YORK CITY, NEW YORK, UNITED STATES. KIRKLAND, WASHINGTON, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4608


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The mission of the Waymo AI Foundations team is to develop machine learning solutions address</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Decision Analytics Associate Consultant (Customer Models &amp; Motivation) - ZS Associates</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7300e9433f82a0fd</link>
        <description>:
**ZS** is a place where passion changes lives. As a management consulting and technology firm focused on improving life and how we live it, we transform ideas into impact by **bringing together data, science, technology** and **human ingenuity** to deliver better outcomes for all. Here you’ll work side\-by\-side with a powerful collective of thinkers and experts shaping life\-changing solutions for patients, caregivers and consumers, worldwide. ZSers drive impact by bringing a **client\-first mentality** to each and every engagement. We partner collaboratively with our clients to develop custom solutions and technology products that create value and deliver company results across critical areas of their business. Bring your curiosity for learning, bold ideas, courage and passion to drive life\-changing impact to ZS.  


 :
**Insights \&amp; Analytics**

**ZS's** **Insights \&amp; Analytics** **group** partners with clients to design and deliver solutions to help them tackle a broad range of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytics - Ads Product - Discord</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2cf53595ac1b9091</link>
        <description>Discord is used by over 200 million people every month for many different reasons, but there’s one thing that nearly everyone does on our platform: play video games. Over 90% of our users play games, spending a combined 1\.5 billion hours playing thousands of unique titles on Discord each month. Discord plays a uniquely important role in the future of gaming. We are focused on making it easier and more fun for people to talk and hang out before, during, and after playing games.At Discord, we're building something special \- a place where hundreds of millions of people connect, play, and belong. Our ads business is entering an exciting growth phase, and we're looking for a Senior Data Scientist who's passionate about building advertising technology that respects our users while delivering real value to brands. We are establishing the groundwork for advanced advertising capabilities that uphold user privacy and simultaneously achieve outstanding results for advertisers \- now that’s true</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Scientist, Foundation Model Understanding Data Architect - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=253ff57b1f3becac</link>
        <description>About the Role
  
We are seeking a Principal Scientist (P60\) to define and lead the data and semantic architecture that enables Adobe Firefly’s next‑generation unified foundation models —models that natively combine understanding, reasoning, and generation within a single system.
  
This role sits within the Applied Science and Machine Learning (ASML) organization and operates at the highest level of technical leadership. You will shape how meaning, intent, and abstraction are represented and learned at foundation‑model scale, influencing multiple generations of models and products. This is a highly strategic individual contributor role with broad organizational impact. What You’ll Do
  
Foundation Model Data Vision
  
Define the multi‑year vision for understanding‑centric data that enables unified comprehension and generation.
  
Establish core principles for semantic representation, supervision, and curriculum at foundation‑model scale.
  
Identify limitations in existing data parad</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Controls &amp; Reinforcement Learning Engineer - Foundation Robotics Labs Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a9407f82190de457</link>
        <description>Foundation is developing the future of general purpose robotics with the goal to address the labor shortage.

  

Our mission is to create advanced robots that can operate in complex environments, reducing human risk in conflict zones and enhancing efficiency in labor\-intensive industries.

  

We are on the lookout for extraordinary engineers and scientists to join our team. Your previous experience in robotics isn't a prerequisite — it's your talent and determination that truly count.

  

We expect that many of our team members will bring diverse perspectives from various industries and fields. We are looking for individuals with a proven record of exceptional ability and a history of creating things that work.

  

All positions are based in San Francisco.

 **Our Culture**

  

We like to be frank and honest about who we are, so that people can decide for themselves if this is a culture they resonate with. Please read more about our culture here https://foundation.bot/culture.

 </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist II - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b28f976f3803100f</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
Overall Purpose  

  

This position serves as a data science team member in the Model Validation and Monitoring Team delivering leading edge machine learning models to our clients. This includes providing effective challenges to model development, conduct model monitoring and </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (Gen AI) - EarnIn</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=39347a5af4dd60c5</link>
        <description>### **About EarnIn**



As one of the first pioneers of earned wage access, our passion at EarnIn is building products that deliver real\-time financial flexibility for those with the unique needs of living paycheck to paycheck. Our community members access their earnings as they earn them, with options to spend, save, and grow their money without mandatory fees, interest rates, or credit checks.



We're fortunate to have an incredibly experienced leadership team, combined with world\-class funding partners like A16Z, Matrix Partners, DST, Ribbit Capital, and a very healthy core business with a tremendous runway. We're growing fast and are excited to continue bringing world\-class talent onboard to help shape the next chapter of our growth journey.


**WHAT WE'RE LOOKING FOR**



EarnIn is building the next generation of AI\-powered experiences that help millions of people access their pay and improve their financial well\-being. We're looking for a self\-driven engineer eager to grow</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Data Scientist - Recommendations - Scribd</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2eb5a157e509e5b</link>
        <description>**About The Company:**
----------------------


At Scribd Inc. (pronounced “scribbed”), our mission is to spark human curiosity. Join our team as we create a world of stories and knowledge, democratize the exchange of ideas and information, and empower collective expertise through our four products: Everand, Scribd, Slideshare, and Fable.


This posting reflects an approved, open position within the organization.


We support a culture where our employees can be real and be bold; where we debate and commit as we embrace plot twists; and where every employee is empowered to take action as we prioritize the customer.


When it comes to workplace structure, we believe in balancing individual flexibility and community connections. It’s through our flexible work benefit, Scribd Flex, that employees – in partnership with their manager – can choose the daily work\-style that best suits their individual needs. A key tenet of Scribd Flex is our prioritization of intentional in\-person moments t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior ML/AI Software Engineer – Evaluation Insights - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8d3bcddfad78daa2</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**The Role:**

GM’s autonomy stack generates far more numerical data than anyone can review manually. The Evaluation Insights team builds tools that turn this data into a single, trustworthy view of performance—accelerating model iteration and improving vehicle safety.


As a Senior ML/AI Software Engineer on the Sim Insights team, you will help stakeholders—from AV developers and system engineers to leadership—reach accurate, actionable conclusions about the autonomy stack’s performance. You will apply your expertise in robotic systems, statistical analysis, and data visualization to engineer tools that answer a wide range of questions about AV stack performance.


**About the Organization:**

The Evaluation team is dedicated to creating, maintaining, and evolving the evaluation ecosystem that underpins GM’s pursuit of safe, high\-performing, and scalable driverless technology. The team delivers trusted metrics, automated workflows, and scalable tools that enable </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist III - MERCOR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ea02c074e8a62455</link>
        <description>We are seeking a highly experienced Data Science Contractor to join our team and provide essential support for strategic initiatives across a major social media platform's ecosystem. This position is ideally suited for a data scientist possessing robust analytical capabilities, substantial experience within large\-scale data environments, and a commitment to generating significant impact through data\-driven insights.

**Responsibilities**

* Conduct rigorous analysis of complex datasets to identify trends, patterns, and actionable insights pertinent to the ecosystem (products, partners, platforms, and user interactions).
* Design, implement, and meticulously maintain critical metrics to accurately measure ecosystem health, growth, and engagement.
* Develop and execute structured experiments to rigorously evaluate new features, strategic partnerships, and ecosystem strategies.
* Engage closely with cross\-functional teams (Product, Engineering) to formally define requirements, deliver </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Data Scientist, New College Grad - 2026 - Visa</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=45d3814a2a03d341</link>
        <description>**Company Description**  

Visa is a world leader in digital payments, facilitating more than 215 billion payments transactions between consumers, merchants, financial institutions and government entities across more than 200 countries and territories each year. Our mission is to connect the world through the most innovative, convenient, reliable and secure payments network, enabling individuals, businesses and economies to thrive.


When you join Visa, you join a culture of purpose and belonging – where your growth is priority, your identity is embraced, and the work you do matters. We believe that economies that include everyone everywhere, uplift everyone everywhere. Your work will have a direct impact on billions of people around the world – helping unlock financial access to enable the future of money movement.

**Join Visa: A Network Working for Everyone.**

 **Job Description**  

The Global Data Science team at Visa leverages our rich data \- spanning over 3 billion card accoun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied AI/ML Business Analytics Lead - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41829f0bf21c6a9a</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Mathematics, Statistics, Economics, Computer Science, or a related quantitative field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 6 years of experience in data analysis, statistical modeling, or a similar role.
* Experience in applying machine learning techniques and economic analysis in a business context such as simulations, statistical analysis, and nonlinear regression models.
* Experience in SQL (BigQuery, PostgreSQL, SQL Server, or MySQL).
* Experience in Python or R.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Data Science, Machine Learning, Statistics, Economics, or a related field.
* Experience with data visualization tools such as Tableau, Power BI, or similar.
* Experience in the consumer electronics industry, with a focus on promotional analytics and consumer offer management.
* Experience building and deploying statistical and machine learning models using Python.
* Knowledge of cloud\-based AI plat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Cloud AI - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=71ea97bb2e90a5bd</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 year</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Engineer, AI.x - Charles Schwab</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=925b48f9ccab421f</link>
        <description>**Your opportunity**
--------------------

  

At Schwab, your career is more than a job—it's an opportunity to impact the lives of millions. Innovation and creative problem solving thrive here, as we challenge conventional approaches and prioritize collaboration. We value in\-person teamwork, so this role is based on\-site at our San Francisco office.  

As part of Schwab’s AI Strategy \&amp; Transformation team (AI.x), you’ll join the central hub for Artificial Intelligence across the company. AI.x brings together product, engineering, strategy, and risk specialists to set enterprise AI vision, invest in transformative opportunities, and accelerate delivery organization\-wide. Our team builds the scalable core platform for AI and explores next\-generation GenAI initiatives that redefine client experiences.  

We’re seeking a Senior AI Engineer who will design and deliver cutting\-edge GenAI applications, enhancing the client journey and driving tangible business value. You’ll collaborate</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Quickbooks Workforce Solutions - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1a58af106a5dec8b</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


We are seeking a Senior Data Scientist to join our Quickbooks Workforce Solutions Data Science Team. This role is focused on growth across Intuit’s Payroll and Human Capital Management products and services. The team uses advanced analytics and artificial intelligence to deliver exceptional customer experiences and help businesses manage finances and employees more effectively.

  



As a Senior Data Scientist on the Product Data Science team, you will explore data to generate insights that influence the strategic direction of Workforce Solutions. Your work will directly shape product development, customer experience, and go\-to\-market decisions.

 **Responsibilities**

  

* Define KPIs and Success Metrics: Establish key business indicators for projects, ensuring alignment with company objectives and clear measures of success.
* Data Visualization: Translate complex data into clear, accessible dashboards and other visualizations that help stakeholders und</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Agent - Pika</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a550f1035b38bdf3</link>
        <description>*Senior Software Engineer, Agent*  

  

*Department:* Engineering \| *Location:* Palo Alto HQ \| *Type:* Full\-time, On\-site  

  

*About the Role*  

We're looking for a Senior Agent Engineer to push the boundaries of what AI agents can do at Pika. You'll work on the systems that give AI agents their personality, memory, reasoning, multi\-modal capabilities, and ability to act autonomously across platforms. This is the core of what makes Pika's AI products feel alive.  

  

You'll design agent architectures, build tool\-use frameworks, optimize LLM interactions, and create the systems that allow agents to learn, remember, and evolve over time. If you're excited about building AI systems that feel genuinely intelligent — not just wrappers over chat APIs — this role is for you.  

  

*What You'll Do*  

* Design and evolve the agent runtime — the core loop that handles reasoning, tool use, memory retrieval, and response generation
* Build agent capabilities — image generation, voic</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Data Analyst - Super Micro Computer, Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4fcebd76e0743460</link>
        <description>Sr. Data Analyst

  

**Date:** Feb 24, 2026


**Location:** San Jose, California, United States


**Company:** Super Micro Computer


**Job Req ID: 28380**
**About Supermicro:**

Supermicro® is a Top Tier provider of advanced server, storage, and networking solutions for Data Center, Cloud Computing, Enterprise IT, Hadoop/ Big Data, Hyperscale, HPC and IoT/Embedded customers worldwide. We are the \#5 fastest growing company among the Silicon Valley Top 50 technology firms. Our unprecedented global expansion has provided us with the opportunity to offer a large number of new positions to the technology community. We seek talented, passionate, and committed engineers, technologists, and business leaders to join us.  

**Job Summary:**

Supermicro is seeking a Sr. Data Analyst to drive business process analysis, documentation, and optimization across various strategic initiatives. This role is ideal for a self\-starter who can work with limited structure, engages take holders, and develo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Marketing Innovation - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=50da1a7d4cd0e76a</link>
        <description>Careers
  
  

Data Scientist, Marketing Innovation
  
  

Data Science \- San Francisco
  
  

About the Role
  
  

We’re hiring a Data Scientist to support our Marketing Innovation pod, a cross\-functional team building the internal tools and agentic systems that fundamentally change how we do marketing and serve customers.
  
  

**We build product\-like systems that:**  

Deliver high\-touch, consultative experiences to millions of SMB customers through agentic lifecycle and sales experiences
  
  

Adapt messaging, creative, and outreach using real\-time behavioral signals
  
  

Power intelligent routing, targeting, and engagement decisions at scale, with minimal human\-in\-the\-loop
  
  

In this role, you’ll be embedded with Product and Engineering to ensure these systems drive measurable business outcomes.
  
  

What You’ll Do
  
  

Define success metrics for agentic marketing systems (e.g., incremental pipeline generated, conversion lift, rep hours saved), including leadi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist (Start-Up) - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=868be077d2a214f1</link>
        <description>### **Qualifications \&amp; Experience**


* Minimum of 4\+ years of hands\-on experience in data science within high\-performing product analytics environments, ideally supporting B2B software platforms.
* Advanced proficiency in **Python and SQL** , including strong working knowledge of pandas, NumPy, StatsModels or Scikit\-learn, and experience working within modern data warehouses such as BigQuery or Snowflake.
* Strong command of statistical sampling methodologies, including stratified sampling, bootstrapping techniques, and reliable extrapolation approaches.
* Proven track record of independently designing, building, and deploying analytics tools or frameworks that were successfully adopted by product, growth, or cross\-functional teams.
* Deep expertise in experimentation and causal measurement, including A/B testing, difference\-in\-differences analysis, propensity score matching, matched market testing, and statistical power calculations.
* Hands\-on experience working with large </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Global Product R&amp;D Center - San Francisco - Plaud</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41d0957d2d36fcb4</link>
        <description>**About Plaud Inc.**


Plaud is building the world's most trusted AI work companion for professionals to elevate productivity and performance through note\-taking solutions, loved by over 1,500,000 users worldwide since 2023\. With a mission to amplify human intelligence, Plaud is building the next\-generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, and utilize what you say, hear, see, and think.

  

Plaud Inc. is a Delaware\-incorporated, San Francisco\-based company pushing the boundary of human–AI intelligence through a hardware–software combination. With ISO 27001, ISO 27701, GDPR, SOC 2, HIPAA, and EN 18031 compliance, Plaud is committed to the highest standards of data security and privacy protection.

  

To learn more about Plaud, please visit https://www.plaud.ai and follow along on Instagram, X, Facebook, LinkedIn, and YouTube

 **Why You Should Join Us**


Plaud is building the next generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, ex</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Analyst, Teams - San Francisco - Plaud</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4cbf72e080da509b</link>
        <description>**About Plaud Inc.**


Plaud is building the world's most trusted AI work companion for professionals to elevate productivity and performance through note\-taking solutions, loved by over 1,500,000 users worldwide since 2023\. With a mission to amplify human intelligence, Plaud is building the next\-generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, and utilize what you say, hear, see, and think.


Plaud Inc. is a Delaware\-incorporated, San Francisco\-based company pushing the boundary of human–AI intelligence through a hardware–software combination. With ISO 27001, ISO 27701, GDPR, SOC 2, HIPAA, and EN 18031 compliance, Plaud is committed to the highest standards of data security and privacy protection.


To learn more about Plaud, please visit https://www.plaud.ai and follow along on Instagram, X, Facebook, LinkedIn, and YouTube

**Why You Should Join Us**


Plaud is building the next generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Specialist - DocuSign</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=aeab1ee32b95dd3c</link>
        <description>**Company Overview**
--------------------

  

Docusign brings agreements to life. Over 1\.5 million customers and more than a billion people in over 180 countries use Docusign solutions to accelerate the process of doing business and simplify people’s lives. With intelligent agreement management, Docusign unleashes business\-critical data that is trapped inside of documents. Until now, these were disconnected from business systems of record, costing businesses time, money, and opportunity. Using Docusign’s Intelligent Agreement Management platform, companies can create, commit, and manage agreements with solutions created by the \#1 company in e\-signature and contract lifecycle management (CLM).  

  

**What You'll Do**
------------------

  

The Senior AI Specialist – Partner Digital Transformation \&amp; Success plays a pivotal role in empowering our global partner ecosystem to accelerate digital transformation and achieve measurable business outcomes through advanced AI technologies</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=76e37f7d1610c50e</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; New York, NY, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structu</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=391141c6ac856cb9</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python and C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Engineer - AI/LLM - Super Micro Computer, Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8147e3e533cff873</link>
        <description>Sr. Software Engineer \- AI/LLM

  

**Date:** Feb 23, 2026


**Location:** San Jose, California, United States


**Company:** Super Micro Computer


**Job Req ID: 28343**
**About Supermicro:**

Supermicro® is a Top Tier provider of advanced server, storage, and networking solutions for Data Center, Cloud Computing, Enterprise IT, Hadoop/ Big Data, Hyperscale, HPC and IoT/Embedded customers worldwide. We are the \#5 fastest growing company among the Silicon Valley Top 50 technology firms. Our unprecedented global expansion has provided us with the opportunity to offer a large number of new positions to the technology community. We seek talented, passionate, and committed engineers, technologists, and business leaders to join us.**Job Summary:**

Supermicro is seeking an experienced and exceptional Sr. Software Engineer to work on web\-based applications for business process automation. This is a key role that will give you the opportunity to expand your existing knowledge in programmin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:49 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
