<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Engineer- Machine Learning - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8357261a46f0d4d3</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.  

Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.When you join our company, we want you to fe</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1eb0d19c64b72edd</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Staff Engineer is a lead member of the engineerin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3742eddcc5e71f7a</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Senior Staff Engineer is a lead member of the eng</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Engineer, Interactive Voice Response - AI/ML - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e924304b2daed071</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Service Engineering team at GEICO is revolutionizing customer service using AI and multi\-agent systems. If you're passionate about creating large\-scale, distributed AI applications with significant business impact, this opportunity is perfect for you. Our focus is on enhancing self\-service rates across all communication channels, from voice (IVR) to chat.


Our Senior Engineer is a leading member of the engine</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Manager, Network Engineering - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4adac333080e98d0</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Our Senior Manager is an engineering leader who works with the engineering staff to innovate and build new engineering solutions, improve, and enhance existing solutions and leverage engineering solutions to solve critical operational problems. A Senior Manager will lead the strategy and execution of a technical roadmap that will increase the speed of delivering products and unlock new engineering capabilities. The N</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director of Machine Learning Engineering, Document Intelligence - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6ef8f66cb9be61a8</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


Title: Director of Machine Learning Engineering, Document Intelligence

 **Overview**:  

GEICO is on a multi\-year journey to transform the insurance industry with  

Artificial Intelligence.  

**The Team****:** The AI Modeling and Research team is part of the AI Org, which is Geico’s strategic investment with the mission to transform Geico into an AI\-first company. AI org is led by Vice President, Head of AI. AI </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Infrastructure Efficiency Analyst - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4833f9206ca158cf</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

As an Infrastructure Analyst within the Cloud C.O.R.E team you will be a key driver of financial accountability and optimization across our cloud environments. You will play a critical role in cloud billing data analysis, forecasting, and the identification and impact analysis of engineering and financial optimizations. You will leverage your expertise in data analysis, machine learning, and engineering to drive insights, optimize our infrastructure, improve our forecasts, and deliver efficient growth for Uber.
**\- What the Candidate Will Do \-**  

  

* Translate complex cloud consumption data into actionable insights for leadership and engineering.
* Identify and track optimizations and realized savings.
* Establish key price\-performance metrics and partner with engineering to implement price\-performance optimizations within production scaling.
* Define and manage reporting of cloud consumption metrics and KPIs, ensuring transparency, accuracy, and acco</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Architect - Fallback Stack - Applied Intuition</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=05ef98f8cd6503bc</link>
        <description>**About Applied Intuition**
---------------------------


Applied Intuition, Inc. is powering the future of physical AI. Founded in 2017 and now valued at $15 billion, the Silicon Valley company is creating the digital infrastructure needed to bring intelligence to every moving machine on the planet. Applied Intuition services the automotive, defense, trucking, construction, mining and agriculture industries in three core areas: tools and infrastructure, operating systems, and autonomy. Eighteen of the top 20 global automakers, as well as the United States military and its allies, trust the company's solutions to deliver physical intelligence. Applied Intuition is headquartered in Sunnyvale, California, with offices in Washington, D.C.; San Diego; Ft. Walton Beach, Florida; Ann Arbor, Michigan; London; Stuttgart; Munich; Stockholm; Bangalore; Seoul; and Tokyo. Learn more at applied.co.
*We are an in\-office company, and our expectation is that employees primarily work from their Applie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Intern, Software Engineering (Computational Modeling) - Eikon Therapeutics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd0ead9322f6b4e1</link>
        <description>Eikon Therapeutics is a new biopharmaceutical company employing revolutionary technology at the intersection of chemistry, engineering, computation, and biology to discover novel treatments for life\-threatening diseases. Eikon's discovery platform is built on groundbreaking innovations from its founders (Nobel Prize, 2014\), culminating in the creation of microscopes which enable real time, molecular\-resolution measurements of protein movement in living cells, thereby unlocking otherwise intractable classes of proteins as drug targets.

**Position**



This 10\-week summer internship provides an opportunity to gain hands\-on experience within the Software Engineering and Computational Modeling function in a collaborative, fast\-paced research environment. The Software Intern will support development and application of Bayesian statistical methods, machine learning models, and computational approaches used to characterize complex single\-molecule and photophysical systems. In this rol</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Intern, Software Engineering (Machine Learning) - Eikon Therapeutics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41d314d894be12c5</link>
        <description>Eikon Therapeutics is a new biopharmaceutical company employing revolutionary technology at the intersection of chemistry, engineering, computation, and biology to discover novel treatments for life\-threatening diseases. Eikon's discovery platform is built on groundbreaking innovations from its founders (Nobel Prize, 2014\), culminating in the creation of microscopes which enable real time, molecular\-resolution measurements of protein movement in living cells, thereby unlocking otherwise intractable classes of proteins as drug targets.

**Position**



This 10\-week summer internship provides an opportunity to gain hands\-on experience within the Software Engineering and Machine Learning function in a collaborative, fast\-paced research environment. The Software Intern will support research and development initiatives focused on image processing, computer vision, and machine learning systems used to improve internal scientific and analytical tools. In this role, you will gain exposur</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Signal and Power Integrity Engineer - Astera Labs</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ef3958f73b808183</link>
        <description>Astera Labs (NASDAQ: ALAB) provides rack\-scale AI infrastructure through purpose\-built connectivity solutions. By collaborating with hyperscalers and ecosystem partners, Astera Labs enables organizations to unlock the full potential of modern AI. Astera Labs' Intelligent Connectivity Platform integrates CXL®, Ethernet, NVLink, PCIe®, and UALink™ semiconductor\-based technologies with the company's COSMOS software suite to unify diverse components into cohesive, flexible systems that deliver end\-to\-end scale\-up, and scale\-out connectivity. The company's custom connectivity solutions business complements its standards\-based portfolio, enabling customers to deploy tailored architectures to meet their unique infrastructure requirements. Discover more at www.asteralabs.com.


At Astera Labs, we seek motivated **Principal Signal and Power Integrity Engineers** to work on our game\-changing portfolio of connectivity products for Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning applications</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior, Data Scientist (Personalization) - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=48789add1d9755e1</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------


***Immigration sponsorship is not available for this role. Applicants must******be authorized to******work for any employer in the United States without current or future visa sponsorship.***

Walmart Global Tech is looking to hire a seasoned Senior Data Scientist for their Personalization team in Sunnyvale, CA to support the Personalization and Recommendation development efforts with our eCommerce team.  

  

**About the Team:**
The Personalization team consists of platform, application engineers, scientists and product visionaries all working together to design, prototype and build technology\-driven products and experiences that will change the future landscape of ecommerce. We are focused on building end\-to\-end customer experience, from finding the product to delivering it to the customer. This will span many markets, business models and form factors; therefore, we are looking for data</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=37726c0c01aaa426</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of robots </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Science Manager - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=40166b7351317d3e</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Science Manager - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=95d474789ef56e02</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Machine Learning Engineer - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2a588910b3c90edf</link>
        <description>Adobe Firefly’s Generative AI Services team is seeking Senior Machine Learning Engineers for our GenAI Services area. In this high\-impact role, you will work with a team of talented engineers in building scalable, high\-performance generative AI systems—powering features across Adobe products like Firefly, Photoshop, Illustrator, Express, Stock, and Premiere. You will design and develop efficient inference pipelines, optimize models for latency and through at inference, and build APIs and ecosystems that integrate both Adobe’s first\-party and third\-party generative models into Adobe suite of products that serve individual and enterprise customers. You will tackle Adobe’s most complex engineering challenges at the forefront of the the industry, set technical direction, and mentor other ML engineers. Job Responsibilities
  
  

Design and evelopment of core GenAI services and APIs that integrate a wide range of generative models into Adobe’s flagship products.
  
  

Design and build </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Engineer (Modeling), Support - Block</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5725651c9d02ac23</link>
        <description>Block is one company built from many blocks, all united by the same purpose of economic empowerment. The blocks that form our foundational teams — People, Finance, Counsel, Hardware, Information Security, Platform Infrastructure Engineering, and more — provide support and guidance at the corporate level. They work across business groups and around the globe, spanning time zones and disciplines to develop inclusive People policies, forecast finances, give legal counsel, safeguard systems, nurture new initiatives, and more. Every challenge creates possibilities, and we need different perspectives to see them all. Bring yours to Block.


**The Role**



Block's Support ML Modeling team is a central driver of innovation in customer support experiences across our entire ecosystem—including Cash App, Square, and other business units. We are dedicated to advancing the state of intelligent, automated support through machine learning and generative AI. From customer\-facing chatbots to smart in</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6cd2d083ebcb9f16</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8fc668c83d504086</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior System Architect, Infrastructure Reliability - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d6c838ef9acddcaf</link>
        <description>NVIDIA is seeking a Senior System Architect: Heterogeneous EDA Systems to solve a complex challenge in accelerated computing: Failure Attribution at Scale. As EDA or equivalent experience workloads scale across thousands of heterogeneous nodes, a single failure can cause massive resource waste. We need an engineer to develop and build an automated framework. This framework will ingest telemetry from CPU and GPU clusters to identify the root cause of job failures in real\-time. It will distinguish between hardware faults, infrastructure instability, and software defects.  

What you'll be doing:* Architect Failure Attribution Frameworks: Build a scalable "flight recorder" for EDA jobs that captures high\-fidelity state across the CPU, GPU, and Fabric at the moment of failure.
* Build automated diagnostics that correlate GPU XID errors, PCIe bus failures, and CUDA memory exceptions. Connect these errors with system\-level events such as OOM kills or NUMA\-related hangs.
* Distributed Log</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Visualization Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=867f580c7e3bb0e7</link>
        <description>NVIDIA is seeking a Senior Data Visualization Engineer to define the visual interface of our most advanced data products. You will sit at the intersection of UX design and massive\-scale engineering, turning petabyte\-scale data lakes into real\-time, ML\-infused analytical applications. We aren't just building dashboards; we are building the "cockpit" for the world’s most advanced AI infrastructure.  

What you'll be doing:* Rapid Dashboard Prototyping: Build and deploy high\-fidelity visuals at speed. You will be responsible for taking raw requirements and delivering intuitive, production\-ready dashboards in accelerated timelines.
* Architect Intelligence Products: Design and build high\-performance, interactive data applications that translate complex system telemetry into actionable insights.
* Bridge ML and UX: Partner with Data Science teams to visualize predictive model outputs, making anomaly detection and forecasting intuitive for executive decision\-makers.
* Engineered Data</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Staff Engineer - Virtual Expert Platform - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9811a0fb1ed6ab2a</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


The Virtual Expert Platform (VEP) team is looking for a Senior Software Engineer to help deliver innovative, full\-stack experiences for TurboTax and QuickBooks Live. This technical leader will have true technical depth, business acumen, and a desire to create delight in every customer experience. S/he will have a passion for driving technical product direction, technology blueprint, leading and inspiring cross\-functional teams, and influencing executives as well as engineers.  

Designing and building platform solutions that allow teams across Intuit to release independently while bringing together a cohesive experience into our customer\-facing applications is key to this role. We are looking for an engineer who has a strong understanding of large\-scale system design. This leader is expected to innovate and enable applications that are highly interactive, fast and can scale to billions of interactions. **Responsibilities**

* Drive end\-to\-end architect</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Advanced Degree Cloud Engineer - Customer Success Services - Oracle</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7a3c50ab53202726</link>
        <description>**FTE \- Intended for students graduating with their Master's degree by, or have graduated within, 12 months of cohort start date in July 2026**

**Target Start Date: July 13th, 2026**

**The Program:**

Our future success depends on hiring world\-class, early in career talent who are looking to power next\-generation services and solutions leveraging AI capabilities. We are hiring students with a diverse set of skills and experiences to work in and across teams. Our program is intended to enhance your overall learning experience, help build your network, and accelerate your opportunity to make an impact.


**The Team:**

As a key member of Oracle Customer Success Services, you will join an international network of experts dedicated to driving customer success through innovation and expertise. Our One Oracle approach ensures you will be part of a team delivering comprehensive, end\-to\-end services and solutions that accelerate the entire customer journey.


This team is at the forefro</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Advanced Degree Cloud Engineer Intern - Customer Success Services - Oracle</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f57074fe6b21caca</link>
        <description>**Must be enrolled in a university prior to and post internship.**

**Target Internship Duration: May 18** **th** **\- Aug 7** **th** **, 2026**

**The Program:**

Our future success depends on hiring world\-class, early in career talent who are looking to power next\-generation services and solutions leveraging AI capabilities. We are hiring students with a diverse set of skills and experiences to work in and across teams. Our program is intended to enhance your overall learning experience, help build your network, and accelerate your opportunity to make an impact.


**The Team:**

As a key member of Oracle Customer Success Services, you will join an international network of experts dedicated to driving customer success through innovation and expertise. Our One Oracle approach ensures you will be part of a team delivering comprehensive, end\-to\-end services and solutions that accelerate the entire customer journey.


This team is at the forefront of advancing the adoption and success</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Lead AI Engineer - Information Technology Senior Management Forum</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dbb596328a1995cd</link>
        <description>Posted Date


2/25/2026


Description


Senior Lead AI Engineer**Overview:**


At Capital One, we are creating responsible and reliable AI systems, changing banking for good. For years, Capital One has been an industry leader in using machine learning to create real\-time, personalized customer experiences. Our investments in technology infrastructure and world\-class talent — along with our deep experience in machine learning — position us to be at the forefront of enterprises leveraging AI. From informing customers about unusual charges to answering their questions in real time, our applications of AI \&amp; ML are bringing humanity and simplicity to banking. We are committed to continuing to build world\-class applied science and engineering teams to deliver our industry leading capabilities with breakthrough product experiences and scalable, high\-performance AI infrastructure. At Capital One, you will help bring the transformative power of emerging AI capabilities to reimagine how we </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Privacy Engineer - DoorDash</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8dc91b013abb160a</link>
        <description>**About the Team**
------------------



At DoorDash we're building the industry's most scalable and reliable delivery network to support our three\-sided marketplace of consumers, merchants, and Dashers. Security is paramount to the success of our business, and DoorDash Security aspires to be the world's most admired security team. We are committed to building the world's most trusted on\-demand, logistics engine for delivery! We're expanding our team of great minds to help us secure and maintain a 24x7, no downtime, global infrastructure system that powers DoorDash's multi\-sided marketplace of consumers, merchants, and dashers.


**About the Role**
------------------



Our Security Engineering team is looking for a **Principal Privacy** **Engineer** to set and lead the technical direction for privacy engineering at DoorDash globally.



You will be a part of our inclusive, collaborative global team responsible for building "paved road" privacy preserving controls to ensure a safe, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director, Forward Deployed AI Engineering - Traba</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=783b819839d1e8c7</link>
        <description>**Who We Are**
--------------


Traba is building a world where the global supply chain operates at peak efficiency. We are a technology company that enhances the productivity and potential of the industrial supply chain by connecting businesses with reliable workers. We leverage location monitoring, predictive algorithms, machine learning, AI, computer vision, and other advanced technologies to drive an unparalleled customer experience.


We’re proud to be backed by some of the world’s best investors, including Founders Fund, Khosla Ventures, and General Catalyst.

**The Role**
------------


If you’ve ever wanted to build an engineering organization from scratch, partner directly with industrial CEOs to design real\-world AI systems, and operate like a technical founder inside a high\-growth startup, this is your chance.


This quarter, we are launching **Traba Atlas**, our AI engineering arm embedding elite engineers inside industrial enterprises to build AI agents and automation to</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, PhD Intern - Handshake</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e54d039f0f2616c5</link>
        <description>**Machine Learning Engineer, PhD Intern**
=========================================

**About Us**
------------


Handshake is the career network for the AI economy. More than 20 million knowledge workers, 1,600 educational institutions, and 1 million employers — including 100% of the Fortune 50 — trust Handshake to power career discovery, hiring, and upskilling. From freelance AI training gigs to first internships to full\-time careers and beyond, we connect talent with opportunity at every stage.


This unique position in the ecosystem is driving exceptional growth — in 2025, we tripled ARR at scale.

**Why join Handshake now:**

* Shape how careers evolve in the AI economy at global scale, with visible real\-world impact
* Work directly with leading AI labs, Fortune 500 partners, and top educational institutions
* Help build a rapidly scaling business on a path toward multi\-billion\-dollar revenue

**The Role**
------------


As a **Machine Learning Engineering Intern**, you will co</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Founding Machine Learning Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=885a983695c9da37</link>
        <description>Founding ML Engineer

**San Francisco, on\-site, full\-time \- $200,000 \- $500,000 per year.**

***$10k referral bonus*** *for successful hires (half equity, half cash).*

  

It's Monday, 10 AM. You walk through the glass doors at the company's San Francisco headquarters, grab a coffee, grab a Red Bull, and pull up the overnight dashboard.


Yesterday's mouse data has already been crunched. The house AI parsed the PK curves, flagged the outliers, and ranked the candidates while you slept. Two peptides from last week's batch showed decent half\-lives. One was a dud. You skim the summary, make a note, and move on.


At noon, the head of science from a major AI lab walks in. He's got access to a frontier model that isn't public yet and wants to understand your assay data well enough to train on it. You spend forty\-five minutes at the whiteboard explaining our record\-setting feedback loop to someone who understands transformers better than anyone alive but has never pipetted anything.
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, Model LifeCycle - CRUSOE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1ce43f7cd886aa45</link>
        <description>Crusoe's mission is to accelerate the abundance of energy and intelligence. We’re crafting the engine that powers a world where people can create ambitiously with AI — without sacrificing scale, speed, or sustainability.


Be a part of the AI revolution with sustainable technology at Crusoe. Here, you'll drive meaningful innovation, make a tangible impact, and join a team that’s setting the pace for responsible, transformative cloud infrastructure.

**About the Role:**


The Senior Staff Engineer for the Model LifeCycle team will play a crucial role in building a comprehensive managed platform for the entire application development lifecycle, with a specific focus on leveraging Machine Learning models, including Large Language Models (LLMs).

**What You'll Be Working On:**

* Manage fine\-tuning systems for large foundation models (SFT, PEFT, LoRA, adapters), including multi\-node orchestration, checkpointing, failure recovery, and cost\-efficient scaling.
* Implement and maintain end\</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Cloud/Backend - SCP (Hybrid) - CrowdStrike</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9101165c057c709</link>
        <description>As a global leader in cybersecurity, CrowdStrike protects the people, processes and technologies that drive modern organizations. Since 2011, our mission hasn’t changed — we’re here to stop breaches, and we’ve redefined modern security with the world’s most advanced AI\-native platform. We work on large scale distributed systems, processing almost 3 trillion events per day and this traffic is growing daily. Our customers span all industries, and they count on CrowdStrike to keep their businesses running, their communities safe and their lives moving forward. We’re also a mission\-driven company. We cultivate a culture that gives every CrowdStriker both the flexibility and autonomy to own their careers. We’re always looking to add talented CrowdStrikers to the team who have limitless passion, a relentless focus on innovation and a fanatical commitment to our customers, our community and each other. Ready to join a mission that matters? The future of cybersecurity starts with you.
About </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (Scala) - Quantifind</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b2f69574da81c80</link>
        <description>### **Who You Are**



Quantifind is seeking a Software Engineer for our Platform team to help define and deliver data services and machine learning infrastructure. The Platform team owns all the infrastructure that powers the SaaS products we build for our customers. We process terabytes of data each day on our own dedicated Hadoop clusters. We use real\-time data services to enable interactive investigations in our web applications. We use Kubernetes and Docker for our container ecosystem, and we develop standalone services in Scala and Python and use Spark for MapReduce jobs.



You care deeply about your work and its impact on the work your team does. You hold yourself to a high standard when it comes to writing clean, performant, and maintainable code that powers well\-designed microservices and enhances Quantifind's distributed data platform. You work well with cross\-functional teams that include Data Scientists, DevOps Engineers, Front\-end Engineers and Product Managers. You a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Information Technology (IT) Systems Administrator (Systems Application Analyst 3) - HII</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0bb8f79e831189f8</link>
        <description>**Date:** Feb 25, 2026


**Location:** Mountain View, CA, California, United States


**Company:** HII's Mission Technologies division


Requisition Number: 27302



Required Travel: 0 \- 10%



Employment Type: Full Time/Salaried/Exempt



Anticipated Salary Range: $96,278\.00 \- $125,000\.00



Security Clearance: Secret


Level of Experience: Mid

  


**Meet HII’s Mission Technologies Division**  

Our team of more than 7,000 professionals worldwide delivers all\-domain expertise and advanced technologies in service of mission partners across the globe. Mission Technologies is leading the next evolution of national defense – the data evolution \- by accelerating a breadth of national security solutions for government and commercial customers. Our capabilities range from C5ISR, AI and Big Data, cyber operations and synthetic training environments to fleet sustainment, environmental remediation and the largest family of unmanned underwater vehicles in every class. Find the role that’</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II - Embedded Systems - Hewlett Packard Enterprise | HPE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f7d643ae0057cd3d</link>
        <description>Software Engineer II \- Embedded Systems  



This role has been designed as ‘’Onsite’ with an expectation that you will primarily work from an HPE office.**Who We Are:**


Hewlett Packard Enterprise is the global edge\-to\-cloud company advancing the way people live and work. We help companies connect, protect, analyze, and act on their data and applications wherever they live, from edge to cloud, so they can turn insights into outcomes at the speed required to thrive in today’s complex world. Our culture thrives on finding new and better ways to accelerate what’s next. We know varied backgrounds are valued and succeed here. We have the flexibility to manage our work and personal needs. We make bold moves, together, and are a force for good. If you are looking to stretch and grow your career our culture will embrace you. Open up opportunities with HPE.

**Job Description:**

  



We’re looking for people who are excited about building infrastructure that global businesses rely on \- </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, AI - Okta</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=836f642fc92a044b</link>
        <description>**Get to know Okta**  

  

Okta is The World’s Identity Company. We free everyone to safely use any technology, anywhere, on any device or app. Our flexible and neutral products, Okta Platform and Auth0 Platform, provide secure access, authentication, and automation, placing identity at the core of business security and growth.  

  

At Okta, we celebrate a variety of perspectives and experiences. We are not looking for someone who checks every single box \- we’re looking for lifelong learners and people who can make us better with their unique experiences.  

  

Join our team! We’re building a world where Identity belongs to you.

**The Global AI Engineering Team**
----------------------------------



At Okta, you’ll be part of a **unified global AI engineering team** that spans the US and India. You’ll work on cutting\-edge applied AI projects while shaping the **platform foundations** that make secure, scalable AI possible at enterprise scale. If you’re passionate about building</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Engineer - Automation Anywhere</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=73fc1a9a504ab369</link>
        <description>About Us:
Automation Anywhere is the leader in Agentic Process Automation (APA), transforming how work gets done with AI\-powered automation. Its APA system, built on the industry’s first Process Reasoning Engine (PRE) and specialized AI agents, combines process discovery, RPA, end\-to\-end orchestration, document processing, and analytics—all delivered with enterprise\-grade security and governance. Guided by its vision to fuel the future of work, Automation Anywhere helps organizations worldwide boost productivity, accelerate growth, and unleash human potential.
Our opportunity:
Automation Anywhere, the leader in Agentic Process Automation (APA), is seeking a Staff Machine Learning Engineer to help power the next generation of AI\-driven digital agents transforming enterprise operations.
In this role, you will design, build, and deploy cutting\-edge machine learning systems that operate at real\-world scale—advancing Generative AI, Natural Language Processing, and Computer Vision cap</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Research Scientist, Applied AI, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=50c8d2c7d0406c6c</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Computer Science, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience leading a research agenda.
* 2 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools, or Applied ML (e.g., LLM's, Generative AI, NLP, Recommendations).
* Experience coding in Python, JavaScript, R, Java, or C\+\+.
* One of more scientific publication submission(s) for conferences, journals, or public repositories (such as CVPR, ICCV, NeurIPS, ICML, ICLR, etc.).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 2 years of experience in coding and leading multiple research efforts and influencing research direction.
* 2 years of coding experience in Python, JavaScript, R, Java, or C\+\+.
* Experience developing and deploying AI solutions to solve large\-scale problems.
* Ability to articulate technical concepts and influence technical directions.
* Excellent communication skills.

**About the job**
-----------------


As an organization, Google </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Machine Learning, Shopping Targeting - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c6d972f514e010d1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: information retrieval, reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML Modeling, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience with LLMs and Generative AI modeling (e.g., prompt engineering, reinforcement learning, model fine tuning).
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with informa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, Production Engineering, Google Distributed Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d70d7958016e708d</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related field.
* 15 years of experience in software development for technical infrastructure.
* Experie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, AI/ML Recommendations, Rankings, Predictions, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f3b7778b66baa90</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 7 years of experience leading technical project strategy, ML design, and working with industry\-scale ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience with design and architecture; and testing/launching software products.
* 5 years of experience building and deploying recommendation systems models (retrieval, prediction, ranking, embedding) in production and experience building architecture in different modeling domains.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of industry experience working on Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning (AI/ML) recommendations.
* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 5 years of experience in a technical leadership role le</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Generative AI and LLMs, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a092eeb18e110586</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products, and 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools (e.g. TensorFlow), artificial intelligence, deep learning, or natural language processing.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience designing and implementing complex context retrieval systems (context scaffolding) for large language models in production.
* Experience leading technical strategy for large\-scale projects and mentoring executive engineers.
* Proficiency in SQL.
* Understanding of vector space models, semantic search, and experience evaluating embedding techniques (e.g., dense versus sparse retrieval, re\-ranking strategies).
* Ability to independently query massive data</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Mechanical Engineering, Instruments Intern - Pleasanton, CA - Calyxo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0295aa9a8490d503</link>
        <description>Calyxo, Inc. is a medical device company headquartered in Pleasanton, California, USA. The company was founded in 2016 to address the profound need for improved kidney stone treatment. Kidney stone disease is a common, painful condition that consumes vast amounts of healthcare resources each year. Our team is led by executives and investors with a proven track record of commercializing paradigm\-shifting devices to meet unmet needs within urology.



Are you ready to change the future of kidney stone treatment? We are seeking high achievers who want to be part of a dynamic team working in a fun, diverse atmosphere.


The Instruments Engineering team is a highly energetic and actively growing team that is responsible for developing and ultimately driving Calyxo's instruments and accessories through to launch. As a Mechanical Engineering Intern on the Instruments team, you will support the design and development of new solutions for both released and next\-generation critical components </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Intern - Pleasanton, CA - Calyxo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b41d53c045908438</link>
        <description>Calyxo, Inc. is a medical device company headquartered in Pleasanton, California, USA. The company was founded in 2016 to address the profound need for improved kidney stone treatment. Kidney stone disease is a common, painful condition that consumes vast amounts of healthcare resources each year. Our team is led by executives and investors with a proven track record of commercializing paradigm\-shifting devices to meet unmet needs within urology.



Are you ready to change the future of kidney stone treatment? We are seeking high achievers who want to be part of a dynamic team working in a fun, diverse atmosphere.


The Software Engineering Internship is aimed at providing hands\-on insight into the day\-to\-day activities of a medical device software department that produces solutions to improve the lives of our patients and support medical professionals who treat their conditions. Our interns will work within the Software Engineering Group and collaborate with Electrical Engineering</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II - Ripple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6988d9d372dc66d3</link>
        <description>At Ripple, we're building a world where value moves like information does today. It's big, it's bold, and we're already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs.



If you're ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.

**The work:**
-------------



In this role, As a Software Engineer II, you will be one of the core engineers within Ripple's central Data Engineering. This team implements the data ingestion and transformation for analytics, machine learning and powering various business functions at Ripple. You are curious about the bottlenecks and failure modes of a system and look for opportuniti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Research Scientist, Perception - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e36e68b8141386cd</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| SAN FRANCISCO, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4389


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Perception team builds the system which learns the spatial\-temporal representation and their semantic meanings of the sur</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA) Senior, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=173d001bc4af220b</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**Position Summary**  

 We are looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join our team and build the Search backend services processing billions of queries for millions of products on Walmart sites and apps worldwide.  

**About Team:**  

 The Search team at Walmart processes billions of queries across millions of products on our global websites and apps. Whether a customer is searching for a specific item or browsing through categories, our platform powers the intelligence behind product discovery. We leverage structured and semi\-structured data at massive scale \- drawing from catalogs, transaction logs, social data, and more. By combining cutting\-edge information retrieval, machine learning, and ranking algorithms, we build low\-latency, high\-availability systems that directly impact customer experience and business metrics. Immigration support is not available for this role.  

  

**</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Signal Integrity Engineer - Amphenol</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2ff821f054a2af27</link>
        <description>**Position: Signal Integrity Engineer**

**Location: Santa Clara, CA**


Amphenol Cable Backplane System group is the market leader for high speed, high bandwidth integrated cable and connector systems for the AI/Machine Learning market not excluding (Mobile Networks, Storage, Servers, Routers, Switches, etc.). Our products help to enable the electronics revolution and remain a key enabler for all the major Tier 1 OEMs globally. Our global headquarters are located in Nashua, NH and we have design, sales and manufacturing locations globally. We are currently seeking a Signal Integrity Engineer with our CBS Team. The position will be located in Santa Clara, CA.

**RESPONSIBILITIES:**

* Contribute to dedicated teams responsible for customer system development and support from concept to production.
* Develop integration and test strategies in support of new product introduction.
* Assist with providing solutions to customers across a wide range of sectors with their high speed data trans</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI/ML Engineer (AI Automation) - Spanidea Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=030013dc9d5218c7</link>
        <description>**No C2C or vendor involvement. No sponsorship provided.**

**Role: Senior AI / ML Engineer (Automation \&amp; Agentic AI)**

**Experience:** 10\+ years  
**Location:** Santa Clara, CA (Hybrid)

**Role Overview**

We are looking for a highly experienced **AI / ML Engineer** with a strong **data engineering and applied AI background** to lead automation initiatives across **code generation and test automation**. This role will work closely with core engineering teams to design, build, and scale **AI\-driven and agentic automation solutions** that improve developer productivity and software quality.

**Key Responsibilities**

* Lead and drive **AI\-powered automation** initiatives for **code generation, refactoring, and test automation**
* Design and implement **Agentic AI systems** using modern LLM frameworks and orchestration tools
* Collaborate with engineering teams to embed AI/ML solutions into existing development and CI/CD workflows
* Build, train, fine\-tune, and evaluate ML and LLM </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Signal Integrity Engineer - Amphenol</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=67d5769687669d5a</link>
        <description>**Location:**

Santa Clara, California
  

**Posted:**

2/25/2026
  

**Location Name:**

Santa Clara
  

**Wage Max:**

214,500\.00
  

**Wage Min:**

80,750\.00
  

**Position Type:**

Full Time  

  

  

Amphenol Communications Solutions (ACS), a division of Amphenol Corporation, is a world leader in interconnect solutions for Communications, Mobile, RF, Optics, and Commercial electronics markets. Amphenol Corporation is one of the world’s largest designers and manufacturers of electrical, electronic and fiber optic connectors and interconnect systems, antennas, sensors and sensor\-based products and coaxial and high\-speed specialty cable. ACS has an expansive global presence in research and development, manufacturing, and sales. We design and manufacture a wide range of innovative connectors as well as cable assemblies for diverse applications including server, storage, data center, mobile, RF, networking, industrial, business equipment, and automotive.


**Position: Signal Integ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI/ML Lead (Agentic AI) - Spanidea Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a98fce0b0b1eaf47</link>
        <description>**No C2C or vendor involvement. No sponsorship provided.**

**Role: Senior AI / ML Engineer (Automation \&amp; Agentic AI)**

**Experience:** 10\+ years  
**Location:** Santa Clara, CA (Hybrid)

**Role Overview**

We are looking for a highly experienced **AI / ML Engineer** with a strong **data engineering and applied AI background** to lead automation initiatives across **code generation and test automation**. This role will work closely with core engineering teams to design, build, and scale **AI\-driven and agentic automation solutions** that improve developer productivity and software quality.

**Key Responsibilities**

* Lead and drive **AI\-powered automation** initiatives for **code generation, refactoring, and test automation**
* Design and implement **Agentic AI systems** using modern LLM frameworks and orchestration tools
* Collaborate with engineering teams to embed AI/ML solutions into existing development and CI/CD workflows
* Build, train, fine\-tune, and evaluate ML and LLM </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager, ML Fleet Planning and Operations - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c04fc8e45e5234ed</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year
  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the follo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager, ML Fleet Planning and Operations - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd0db9793748b750</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year
  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the follo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Computer Vision, Map Geometry - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=beb79b7e6c11b09b</link>
        <description>The application window will be open until at least March 4, 2026\. This opportunity will remain online based on business needs which may be before or after the specified date.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Boulder, CO, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* 1 year of experience with Computer Vision (e.g., image classification and processing, object detection, visual search), video generation, or signal processing.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or a related technical field.
* 2 years of exp</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Rust - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f3c2b991579da048</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Seattle, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Machine Learning, Information Systems, a similar research\-related field, or equivalent practical experien</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Research Data Scientist, Network and Machines Optimization, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=69aafedde169a79e</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 3 years of work experience with a PhD degree.
* 4 years of experience in data analysis or related fields as a Statistician, Data Scientist, etc.
* Experience with statistical software (e.g., R, Python, MATLAB, pandas) and database languages (e.g., SQL).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Data Science, Operations Research, Industrial Engineering, Statistics, or related quantitative field.
* 4 years of relevant work experience (e.g., as a data scientist), including experience applying advanced analytics to planning and infrastructure problems.
* Experience working on technical infrastructure for cloud computing with designing and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Manager I, XR Apps - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b2300ef626946503</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience in product management or a related technical role.
* 1 year of experience taking technical products from conception to launch (e.g., ideation to execution, end\-to\-end, 0 to 1, etc.).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience developing completely new apps, features, and interfaces.
* Experience building products with machine\-learning, computer vision, and AI features.
* Experience delivering zero\-to\-one products and technologies (i.e., new technology introduction), and developing consumer electronics hardware products.
* Knowledge of product craft, with the ability to develop seamless and magical experiences in XR.
* Ability to initiate, develop and build support for ideas.
* Passion for human\-centric design and wants to build technology that feels natural, invisible, and deeply integrated into daily life.

**About the job**
-----------------


At Google, we</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Silicon Power Engineer - Meta</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f44f70133003d0d9</link>
        <description>Reality Labs focuses on delivering Meta's roadmap through creating advanced AI enabled wearables. The compute performance and power efficiency requirements of wearables require custom silicon. Reality Labs Silicon team is driving the state\-of\-the\-art forward with breakthrough work in AI, augmented reality, computer vision, machine learning, graphics, displays, and sensors. Our chips will enable wearable devices where our real and virtual world will mix and match throughout the day.We are growing our team and are seeking engineers who will work with a group of individuals using your skills to implement and contribute to the development and optimization of accelerators for emerging technologies and applications.  

  

  

### **Silicon Power Engineer Responsibilities:**

* Detailed modeling, analysis and optimization of silicon use case power for Machine Learning Hardware accelerator, and create detailed cost/benefit analysis
* Collaborate with ML architects and designers to understa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Camera Imaging Engineer - Meta</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0e8db4ae5828102d</link>
        <description>As a Camera Imaging Engineer, you will be integral to the end\-to\-end image quality of RL camera products. This can involve driving enhancements through cutting\-edge camera technology development, optimizing and tuning camera imaging pipelines, and conducting thorough image quality evaluations.  

  

  

### **Camera Imaging Engineer Responsibilities:**

* Develop and refine image processing pipelines for camera systems
* Lead perceptual and objective image quality studies to guide product and technology development
* Innovate and implement algorithmic solutions to enhance camera product image quality
* Create and improve tools, metrics, and workflows for the camera tuning process
* Coordinate and communicate image quality deliverables to cross\-functional teams
* Review the comprehensive camera system design

  

  

  

### **Minimum Qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Science, Image Processing, Color Science or a related field
* 10\+ years o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>CCB Risk program Senior Associate - JPMorganChase</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3a3339cce49ccc7b</link>
        <description>**JOB DESCRIPTION**  

Come and join us in reshaping the future!


As a Risk program Senior Associate within the Chase consumer Bank, you'll be the analytical expert for identifying and retooling suitable machine learning algorithms that can enhance the fraud risk ranking of particular transactions and/or applications for new products. This includes a balance of feature engineering, feature selection, and developing and training machine learning algorithms using cutting edge technology to extract predictive models/patterns from data gathered for billions of transactions. Your expertise and insights will help us effectively utilize big data platforms, data assets, and analytical capabilities to control fraud loss and improve customer experience.

**Job Responsibilities:**

* Identify and retool machine learning (ML) algorithms to analyze datasets for fraud detection in the Chase Consumer Bank.
* Perform machine learning tasks such as feature engineering, feature selection, and developin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Engineer - BillionToOne</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ab7e4e62ffd83084</link>
        <description>**Ready to redefine what's possible in molecular diagnostics?**
---------------------------------------------------------------



Join a team of brilliant, passionate innovators who wake up every day determined to transform healthcare. At BillionToOne, we've built something extraordinary—a culture where transparency fuels trust, collaboration drives breakthroughs, and every voice matters in our mission to make life\-changing diagnostics accessible to all. We don't just aim for incremental improvements; we strive to build products that are 10x better than anything that exists today. Our people are our greatest asset:talented scientists, engineers, sales professionals, and visionaries united by an unwavering commitment to changing the standard of care in prenatal and cancer diagnostics. This is where cutting\-edge science meets human compassion—every innovation you contribute helps remove fear of unknown from some of life's most critical medical moments. **If you're driven by purpose, e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Research Data Analyst, Deportation Data Project (5274C), Berkeley Law - 84426 - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a016b57b2f13ad65</link>
        <description>Senior Research Data Analyst, Deportation Data Project (5274C), Berkeley Law \- 84426 About Berkeley
  
  

At the University of California, Berkeley, we are dedicated to fostering a community where everyone feels welcome and can thrive. Our culture of openness, freedom and belonging make it a special place for students, faculty and staff.
  
  

As a world\-leading institution, Berkeley is known for its academic and research excellence, public mission, diverse student body, and commitment to equity and social justice. Since our founding in 1868, we have driven innovation, creating global intellectual, economic and social value.
  
  

We are looking for applicants who reflect California's diversity and want to be part of an inclusive, equity\-focused community that views education as a matter of social justice. Please consider whether your values align with our Guiding Values and Principles , Principles of Community , and Strategic Plan .
  
  

At UC Berkeley, we believe that learnin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Assistant/Associate/Full Project Scientist - Machine Learning &amp; Data Analytics Advanced Bioimaging Center Department of Molecular and Cell Biology - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dba0365e43fa8a4f</link>
        <description>**Position overview Position title:** Project Scientist
  
**Salary range:** The UC academic salary scales set the minimum pay determined by rank and step at appointment. See the following table for the current salary scale for this position: https://www.ucop.edu/academic\-personnel\-programs/\_files/2025\-26/represented\-july\-2025\-scales/t37\-b.pdf . A reasonable estimate for this position is $181,700 \- $229,700\.
  
  

**Percent time:** 100%
  
  

**Anticipated start:** Winter/Spring 2026
  
  

**Position duration:** Initial appointment is for one year with the possibility of renewal based on performance and funding availability.
  
  

Application Window
  
**Open date:** February 25, 2026
  
  

**Next review date:** Wednesday, Mar 11, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Apply by this date to ensure full consideration by the committee.
  
  

**Final date:** Friday, Mar 27, 2026 at 11:59pm (Pacific Time)
  
Applications will continue to be accepted until this date, but those re</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Data Scientist - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a47372d5ad18a5fe</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Lead Data Scientist who thinks in systems, understands B2C business problems deeply, and can build the models and analyses that power real growth outcomes for the world's largest consumer companies — all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "build models in isolation and hand off a notebook" role. You'll own the entire data science function — from problem framing through model development through business impact — and you'll do it for enterprise customers where the stakes are real and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist / ML Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbeb93fbc7e35bb4</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Data Scientist who understands B2C business problems deeply, builds models that work with real\-world data, and delivers analyses that drive real growth outcomes — all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "receive a ticket, train a model, hand off a notebook" role. You'll own problems end\-to\-end — from framing through modeling through impact — for enterprise customers where the stakes are real and the feedback loop is tight. If you understand why churn analysis matters differently f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead AI Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c681cf735c207c93</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for a Lead AI Engineer who can own the technical direction of Hilbert's AI stack, ship production\-grade systems hands\-on, and elevate a growing engineering team; all with the ownership and urgency of a founder.


This is not a "manage from a distance" role. You'll write code, make architecture calls, set the bar for quality and velocity, and build the engineering culture as we scale. You're the person the team looks to when the problem is ambiguous, the stakes are high, and the path forward hasn't been written y</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f3f89d6e8b828d2e</link>
        <description>### **Hilbert is a scalable, data science\-first growth engine that gives B2C teams predictive clarity into user behavior, revenue drivers, and the actions that drive sustainable growth. Fully agentic by design, Hilbert shrinks months\-long decision cycles to minutes.**


From Fortune 10 enterprises to beloved brands like FreshDirect, Blank Street, and Levain Bakery, operators run their growth on Hilbert. We're also co\-building alongside leading AI companies.


We're looking for an AI Engineer who can build production\-grade AI systems end\-to\-end \- from prototype to pipeline to product \- with the ownership and urgency of a startup culture.


This is not a "fine\-tune a model and hand it off" role. You'll own core pieces of the AI stack that power Hilbert's demand intelligence platform, ship fast in conditions where the spec is evolving, and communicate what you're building (and why) with clarity to the rest of the team. If you write clean Python, think in systems, and want to buil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5187e2377e02df66</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle informatio</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0acc40891131c6bb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Irvine, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Satff Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=31dfff0141bbc219</link>
        <description>Category Data


Location Mountain View, California


Job ID 19495


  
Company Overview


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


Job Overview


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with pe</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Principal AI/ML Engineer - Abbott</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9a8101317b40f77</link>
        <description>Abbott is a global healthcare leader that helps people live more fully at all stages of life. Our portfolio of life\-changing technologies spans the spectrum of healthcare, with leading businesses and products in diagnostics, medical devices, nutritionals and branded generic medicines. Our 115,000 colleagues serve people in more than 160 countries.


Our medical devices help more than 10,000 people have healthier hearts, improve quality of life for thousands of people living with chronic pain and movement disorders, and liberate more than 500,000 people with diabetes from routine ﬁngersticks.

**Working at Abbott**


At Abbott, you can do work that matters, grow, and learn, care for yourself and family, be your true self and live a full life. You’ll also have access to:

* Career development with an international company where you can grow the career you dream of.
* Employees can qualify for free medical coverage in our Health Investment Plan (HIP) PPO medical plan in the next calendar</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Developer Efficiency - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=926a2a0f154ea1f4</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------

Job Overview
------------


The Development Efficiency Data Science team within PDX is responsible for ensuring that Intuit’s Development Efficiency metric is analytically correct, interpretable, and trusted as it becomes a core input to FY26 execution, planning, and finance conversations.


We are seeking a Staff DS to lead Development Efficiency Data Science. This role owns the analytical strategy, measurement framework, and interpretation standards for Development Efficiency across the Product Development Lifecycle. The role is explicitly focused on measurement science and decision support, not on building developer platforms, enforcing tooling, or operating systems.


This leader will manage a team of senior data scientists and partner closely with Finance, PDX leadership, and senior stakeholders to translate complex analytical outputs into clear, defensible narratives that inform planning, prioritization, and investment decisions.

 **Responsibilities**
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff ML Engineer - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a4109c28ae423d42</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Overview:** We are seeking an accomplished Staff ML Engineer who will serve as a technical leader for Generative AI applications at GEICO. In this individual contributor role, you will be collaborating with a dynamic team of AI and software engineers to design, develop and deploy systems that ensure scalability, reliability and usability of generative AI solutions, applications and workflows across GEICO. You will p</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Product - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c7648d4c72f96b91</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

### **At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities. Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose. When you join our company, we want you to</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff ML Engineer - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=207b864aab8f0afb</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Overview:** We are seeking an accomplished Senior Staff ML Engineer who will serve as a technical leader for Generative AI applications at GEICO. In this individual contributor role, you will be collaborating with a dynamic team of AI and software engineers to design, develop, and deploy systems that ensure scalability, reliability and usability of generative AI solutions, applications, and workflows across the orga</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Member of Technical Staff, Applied AI - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e2a87e144efa3f14</link>
        <description>**TL;DR:** We are seeing strong market demand and an aggressive 6\-month product roadmap, so we are expanding our engineering team. We're looking for someone highly technical (our current team includes 3 IOI medalists) who wants to build a product that is changing how companies make decisions. If you're excited about tackling complex problems end\-to\-end, we should talk.

**Background**


Listen Labs is an AI\-powered research platform that helps teams uncover insights from customer interviews in hours — not months. We help customers analyze conversations, surface themes, and make faster, smarter product decisions.

**Company highlights — entirely product\-led:**

* **World\-Class Team:** Founded by serial entrepreneurs (previous AI exit), former co\-founders, and talent from Jane Street, Twitter, Stripe, Affirm, Bain, Goldman Sachs, and many more Sequoia\-backed startups (plus IOI/ICPC backgrounds).
* **Hypergrowth:** We’re a 40\-person team backed by Sequoia, growing from $0 to a $1</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Forward Deployed AI Engineer - turing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2f067230dc25ca0b</link>
        <description>**About Turing**



Based in San Francisco, California, Turing is the world's leading research accelerator for frontier AI labs and a trusted partner for global enterprises looking to deploy advanced AI systems. Turing accelerates frontier research with high\-quality data, specialized talent, and training pipelines that advance thinking, reasoning, coding, multimodality, and STEM. For enterprises, Turing builds proprietary intelligence systems that integrate AI into mission\-critical workflows, unlock transformative outcomes, and drive lasting competitive advantage.



Recognized by Forbes, The Information, and Fast Company among the world's top innovators, Turing's leadership team includes AI technologists from Meta, Google, Microsoft, Apple, Amazon, McKinsey, Bain, Stanford, Caltech, and MIT. Learn more at www.turing.com

**The Role**



We are looking for an elite engineer who builds like a hacker and communicates like a consultant. You will not just be building models in a notebook</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Creator Ecosystem - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=146772f8fa5737b5</link>
        <description>Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.



At Roblox, we're building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We're on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.



A career at Roblox means you'll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior/Principal Data Scientist, you will be a strategic thought partner to our product and engineering leadership, specifically aligning with the Ecosystem team to help shape the future of the Roblox Creator </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist – AI &amp; Machine Learning Systems (Dublin, CA) - SavvyMoney</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e01821abea23411c</link>
        <description>**Data Scientist – AI \&amp; Machine Learning Systems** (Dublin, CA)

  

\*\*In order to have your application considered, you must complete every question on this application

  

SavvyMoney is a leading San Francisco East Bay fintech company. We provide integrated credit score and personal finance solutions to 1,600 \+ bank and credit union partners nationally. The SavvyMoney solutions integrate with more than 43 digital banking platforms.

 **SavvyMoney was recently recognized by the San Francisco Business Times and the Silicon Valley Journal as one of the "Top 25 Places to Work in the San Francisco Bay Area" and is an Inc. 5000 Fastest Growing Company.**

  

We’re headquartered in Dublin, CA, and offer a flexible hybrid work environment that blends in\-office collaboration with the freedom of remote work.

  

We are seeking a **Data Scientist with strong Machine Learning Engineering capabilities** to lead initiatives in predictive modeling, personalization, and AI\-driven financial </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software AI Engineer - US - Jade Global</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b7fe9dbaa9a91c42</link>
        <description>**Job Title: Software AI Engineer/Architect**

**Location: Santa Clara, CA (onsite preferred but remote candidates can be considered)**

**Experience: 8\- 10 yrs**

**Job Type: Contract/ FTE**

This role requires deep, end\-to\-end understanding of how Large Language Models are built, trained, optimized, deployed, and operated.  



Candidates must demonstrate hands\-on experience beyond consuming hosted LLM APIs, with a strong grasp of the underlying ML theory, system trade\-offs, and production realities of AI/ML solutions.  



**Mandatory Competency Areas (Non\-Negotiable)**

**1\. Foundations of LLMs (How They Actually Work)**

Candidate must demonstrate first\-principles understanding, including:


* Transformer architectures (attention, embeddings, positional encoding)
* Tokenization strategies and their impact on cost \&amp; performance
* Training vs inference behavior
* Loss functions, pre\-training objectives, and alignment techniques (SFT, RLHF)
* Limitations: hallucinations, bi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist Manager, Product, Home - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e4895c78d6141910</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field or equivalent practical experience.
* 13 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), or 10 years of work experience with an advanced degree.
* 5 years of experience working as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 15 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL).
* 6 years of experience working as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

**About the job**
-----------------


Help serve Google's worldwide user base of more than a billion people. </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer, Agent Systems - Salesforce</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=27a11923c9d60175</link>
        <description>*To get the best candidate experience, please consider applying for a maximum of 3 roles within 12 months to ensure you are not duplicating efforts.*

Job Category


Software Engineering
Job Details


**About Salesforce**

Salesforce is the \#1 AI CRM, where humans with agents drive customer success together. Here, ambition meets action. Tech meets trust. And innovation isn’t a buzzword — it’s a way of life. The world of work as we know it is changing and we're looking for Trailblazers who are passionate about bettering business and the world through AI, driving innovation, and keeping Salesforce's core values at the heart of it all.


Ready to level\-up your career at the company leading workforce transformation in the agentic era? You’re in the right place! Agentforce is the future of AI, and you are the future of Salesforce.


We are seeking a Lead AI Engineer, Agent Systems to join the Salesforce AI Research Incubation Team.
  

In this role, you will design and build production\-g</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer, ML Systems - Salesforce</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ded5878ed549bb8b</link>
        <description>*To get the best candidate experience, please consider applying for a maximum of 3 roles within 12 months to ensure you are not duplicating efforts.*

Job Category


Software Engineering
Job Details


**About Salesforce**

Salesforce is the \#1 AI CRM, where humans with agents drive customer success together. Here, ambition meets action. Tech meets trust. And innovation isn’t a buzzword — it’s a way of life. The world of work as we know it is changing and we're looking for Trailblazers who are passionate about bettering business and the world through AI, driving innovation, and keeping Salesforce's core values at the heart of it all.


Ready to level\-up your career at the company leading workforce transformation in the agentic era? You’re in the right place! Agentforce is the future of AI, and you are the future of Salesforce.


We are seeking a Lead AI Engineer, ML Systems to join the Salesforce AI Research Incubation Team.
  

In this role, you will own the engineering systems that </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Analyst, Advanced Analytics - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2291d9ca101a00a7</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------


We’re seeking an intellectually curious, analytical, and detail\-oriented self\-starter to join our team as Senior Analyst. This role is an individual contributor position central to the continued growth, efficiency, and success of the Walmart Connect team. You’ll work alongside Analytics, Sales, and Campaign Management teams and oversee unlocking insights, building analytic solutions and models, and telling the story that helps move media decisions forward. The ideal candidate will have a strong background in analytics with a deep understanding of the retail/media industry.**What you'll do...**
---------------------


* Collaborate with the Walmart Connect cross\-functional teams for the development, execution and delivery of short and long\-term analytic projects that influence media investment strategies and business growth opportunities
* Ensure delivery of assigned insights analyses with end\-to\-end ownership, clear communication,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director, Data Standards &amp; Statistical Programming - IDEAYA Biosciences</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fb054c59fd68d0a6</link>
        <description>**Non\-Solicitation Policy and Notice to Agencies and Recruiters:**
===================================================================

**IDEAYA's Non\-Solicitation Policy strictly prohibits agencies and recruiters from any contact and communication with IDEAYA employees, managers, and leaders to submit unsolicited candidate resumes and/or to solicit business partnerships** . Submission of unsolicited candidate resumes by agencies or recruiters with or without a contract in place with IDEAYA Biosciences Inc. will not create any implied obligation. Failure to comply with this policy will result in disqualification from current and future business opportunities with IDEAYA Biosciences. All recruiting and talent agency decisions are strictly managed by the internal IDEAYA Human Resources function. All communication by external agencies and recruiters must be directed to humanresources@ideayabio.com. We ask that you only email your interest once.


Job Summary


About IDEAYA Biosciences:
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Data Scientist, Pixel - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c149e0ea0d9973c</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Chicago, IL, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of experience with analysis applications (e.g., extracting insights, performing statistical analysis, or solving business problems), and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL) or 2 years of experience with a Master's degree.
* Experience analyzing device telemetry to triage issues; distinguishing between software regressions and hardware limitations (i.e., power, performance, connectivity, or stability domains).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* Experience analyzing time\-series data or telemetry from hardware devices.
* Experie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist Manager, Product, Health - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d9808ed843f289f0</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 13 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL) (or 10 years of experience with a Master's degree).
* 5 years of experience as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 15 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL).
* 6 years of experience as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

**About the job**
-----------------


Help serve Google's worldwide user base of more than a billion people. Data Scientists provide quantitative support, market und</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, YouTube Live Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=28c5f9db463cff38</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages (e.g., Python, C, C\+\+, Java, JavaScript).
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex, matrixed organization.
* 3 years of experience with ML classification systems, ranking and recommendation systems or similar.
* Experience in computer vision/NLP/ML/data mining areas.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all areas, including info</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, YouTube Shopping and Horizontal - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=981fe57c11e663e9</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 8 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 6 years of experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 8 years of experience with a PhD degree.
* Experience with classifiers.

**About the job**
-----------------


At YouTube, we believe that everyone deserves to have a voice, and that the world is a better place when we listen, share, and build community through our stories. We work together to give everyone the power to share their story, explore what they love, and connect with one another in the process. Working at the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=301105ee76fbeeda</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most important customer and business challenges.
We are seeking a Staff Data Scientist to deliver impactful models and insights, and drive measurable outcomes for the Workforce Solutions segment within QuickBooks. **Responsibilities**

* Drive Business Strategy through Data \- Translate business problems into analytical frameworks. Provides guidance and support leadership on how best to harness available data in support of critical business needs and goals
* Build \&amp; Operationalize Advanced Models \- Develop and deploy machine learning models and statistical frameworks to forecast growth, uncover pattern</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=84dfcf6f124a3c30</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team. This role is focused on driving Intuit Mid Market penetration through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refine innovative growth strategies. Your expertise—especially in causal inference and advanced analytics—will be instrumental in surfacing critical insights and translating them into actionable hypotheses that fuel sustained customer and revenue growth.

 **Responsibilities**

* Set Technical Vision and Strategy:
	+ Contribute to and help refine a data science roadmap aimed at driving product funnel optimization and scalable growth initiatives.
	+ Apply rig</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6aefe58f5368dbe6</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9835877a10c98aee</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:37:59 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
