<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Machine Learning Engineer - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=eb95321ae409e815</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Overview:** We are seeking an accomplished Senior Staff ML Engineer who will serve as a technical leader for the generative AI domain at GEICO. In this individual contributor role, you will be collaborating with a dynamic team of AI and software engineers to design, develop and deploy systems that ensure scalability, reliability and usability of generative AI workflows and approaches across the organization which dr</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Engineer - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3856a93e700383ff</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Overview:** We are seeking an accomplished Staff ML Engineer who will serve as a technical leader for the generative AI space at GEICO. In this individual contributor role, you will be collaborating with a dynamic team of AI and software engineers to design, develop and deploy systems that ensure scalability, reliability and usability of generative AI solutions, applications and workflows across GEICO. You will prov</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b09166cd6c260952</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**

**Overview:** We are seeking an accomplished Senior ML Engineer to serve as an individual contributor to the generative AI space at GEICO. In this role, you will be collaborating with a dynamic team of AI and software engineers to design, develop, and deploy systems that drive business value. Your passion for scalability, reliability, and usability of generative AI workflows and approaches will allow you to provide ha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI/ML Engineer - Sigma Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4527ef702cec15d7</link>
        <description>#### **About the Role**



At Sigma, we're not just adding AI—we're building the future of how people work with data. Our platform already lets users explore billions of rows of data in seconds with a spreadsheet\-like interface, analyze and present their data in workbooks, and build data apps and workflows. Now we're pushing further, applying AI to reshape how people build in Sigma, discover insights, and make smarter decisions—fast.



That's where you come in. As an AI/ML Engineer, you'll join a growing team focused on building the AI foundation that will power Sigma for the future. Your work will become an integral part of the workflow for the thousands of enterprises that run on Sigma.


### **What You'll Do**


* Partner with product, design, and engineering teams to identify high\-impact AI/ML opportunities
* Prototype and productionize AI systems that feel intuitive but do a lot under the hood—recommendations, natural language interfaces, agentic workflows, and more
* Develop a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager, Data Center Contract Manufacturing - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7ed7b039799444d6</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Atlanta, GA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Engineering, Business, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in PCBA/MOBO L6, L10 integration, L11 Rack integration in engineering or manufacturing.
* 7 years of experience with operations in general assembly and automation technologies.
* 5 years of experience as a technical program manager or program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of experience managing cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead multi\-disciplinar</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior software engineer, Machine Learning, Core ML - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=21be4a21c554fd91</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Computer Science, Machine Learning, Computer Engineering, or a related technical field.
* Experience scaling machine learning models (e.g., Large Language Models (LLMs) or foundation models), managing the complexities of transitioning architectures from data\-parallel to model, tensor, pipeline\-parallel configurations, or related fields.
* Experience with deep learning frameworks (e.g., JAX, PyTorch, or TensorFlow), including a track record of contributing to or modifying their core internals to support novel and emerging use cases.
* Experience with co\-designing hardware\-aware optimizations to accelerate model execution.
* Knowledge of machin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff AI/ML Engineer - Sigma Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=990160bc7ecf4a43</link>
        <description>#### **About the Role**



At Sigma, we're not just adding AI—we're building the future of how people work with data. Our platform already lets users explore billions of rows of data in seconds with a spreadsheet\-like interface, analyze and present their data in workbooks, and build data apps and workflows. Now we're pushing further, applying AI to reshape how people build in Sigma, discover insights, and make smarter decisions—fast.



That's where you come in. As an AI/ML Engineer, you'll join a growing team focused on building the AI foundation that will power Sigma for the future. Your work will become an integral part of the workflow for the thousands of enterprises that run on Sigma.


### **What You'll Do**


* Partner with product, design, and engineering teams to identify high\-impact AI/ML opportunities
* Prototype and productionize AI systems that feel intuitive but do a lot under the hood—recommendations, natural language interfaces, agentic workflows, and more
* Develop a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Engineer, Global E-commerce - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d5da820e8618ee64</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Research Engineer, Global E\-commerce
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A177957
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

The e\-commerce industry has seen tremendous growth in recent years and has become a hotly contested space amongst leading internet companies. With millions of loyal users globally, we believe TikTok is an ideal platform to deliver a brand new and better e\-commerce experience to our users.
  
  

Our AI Innovation team is dedicated to building next\-generation e\-commerce experiences powered by AIGC and agentic shopping systems. We explore how AI\-generated content and intelligent agents can meaningfully enhance user experiences and reshape the way people discover, evaluate, and purchase products.
  
  

**Responsibilities:**  

* Develop and optimize AIGC video generation models, with a focus on multimodal post\-training for e\-commerce short\-video scenarios.
* Design and implement p</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-22</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Infrastructure Engineer – Distributed AI Systems - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e7a1b91b42fe800</link>
        <description>Job Description

We are seeking a highly experienced infrastructure engineer (**phD Only**) to design and maintain large\-scale distributed systems that support machine learning workloads, high\-throughput data pipelines, and real\-time model serving.

This role involves building robust backend services, optimizing GPU resource orchestration, and implementing advanced system monitoring to ensure low\-latency and highly reliable AI infrastructure.

The ideal candidate is comfortable working at the intersection of **distributed systems, ML infrastructure, and performance engineering**, and has strong experience with large\-scale production environments.

Responsibilities

* Design and implement high\-performance backend services supporting AI model training and inference pipelines
* Develop distributed systems capable of handling multi\-petabyte datasets and high\-throughput data processing
* Optimize GPU cluster scheduling, memory utilization, and workload orchestration
* Build internal</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-22</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - AI Machine Learning - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=90785d4b0ecee872</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position title: SAP iXp Intern \- AI Machine Learning


Location: Palo Alto, CA (in\-person)


Expected start date: June 2026


Contract Duration: 6 months (extendable)


Workin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-22</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Researcher - kiddom</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6d7006cf9ed1f5c5</link>
        <description>**About Kiddom**  

Kiddom is a groundbreaking educational platform that promotes student equity and growth by uniting high\-quality instructional materials with dynamic digital learning. Through unparalleled curriculum management functionality, Kiddom empowers schools and districts to take ownership of their curriculum – resulting in learning experiences tailored to meet the unique needs and goals of local communities. Kiddom’s high\-quality curriculum is layered with robust teacher and leader data insights to drive the continuous improvement of instructional decisions, school/district programming, and professional learning.  

Join our mission to revolutionize K\-12 education at the intersection of cutting\-edge AI and impactful learning outcomes. As a **Machine Learning Researcher**, you will play a pivotal role in pushing the boundaries of what’s possible with AI in education. Your work will assist teachers by personalizing their teaching experience and improving student outcomes. </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-22</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Partner Engineer, Snowflake Alliance - Sigma Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6956e4da3ecfc20e</link>
        <description>A Senior Partner Engineer, Snowflake Alliance is the principal technical advisor and advocate for the Sigma\-Snowflake partnership, both internally at Sigma and externally with Snowflake. This role requires a deep, current, and comprehensive understanding of both the Sigma and Snowflake products and the differentiated value they deliver together to joint customers. The Senior Partner Engineer provides technical thought leadership and strategic guidance across the partnership lifecycle, including: enabling technical sales and solution development, managing high\-priority technical engagements, driving enablement for field teams, and contributing to overall revenue growth and customer success.



Responsibilities:


* **Strategic Technical Alliance Leadership:** Serve as the primary technical leader and advocate for the Sigma Computing/Snowflake strategic alliance. Drive the mutual success of joint customers by ensuring seamless technical integration, optimal performance, and maximized u</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ML / AI Infrastructure Engineering Intern - Arcline</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9afaefdf5d1354cd</link>
        <description>**About Arcline**

Arcline builds AI\-powered data tools that help K\-12 school districts turn fragmented student data into clear, actionable decisions. We work with superintendents and district leaders across Alabama, California, Kentucky, Texas, Wisconsin, and more — replacing months of manual reporting with instant, AI\-driven answers.

We're a small, AI\-native team that ships fast and builds with real users. Our interns ship real features to real classrooms.

**The Role**

You'll work on the core intelligence layer that powers Arcline's natural language query engine — the system that lets educators ask questions in plain English and get accurate, cited answers from their district's data.

Day to day, that means:

* Designing and optimizing RAG pipelines using LangChain, LlamaIndex, and vector databases (pgvector, Pinecone)
* Preprocessing and normalizing messy education data from multiple district sources for use in ML pipelines
* Evaluating retrieval quality, answer accuracy, and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI/ML PhD Intern (Summer 2026) - Sigma Computing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dc146c2949984839</link>
        <description>**About the Role**



At Sigma, we're not just adding AI—we're building the future of how people work with data. Our platform already lets users explore billions of rows of data in seconds with a spreadsheet\-like interface, analyze and present their data in workbooks, and build data apps and workflows. Now we're pushing further, applying AI to reshape how people build in Sigma, discover insights, and make smarter decisions—fast. You can learn more about our vision for AI/ML at Sigma in our recent blog post.



That's where you come in. As an **AI/ML PhD Intern**, you'll join a growing team focused on building the AI foundation that will power Sigma for the future. Your work will become an integral part of the workflow for the thousands of enterprises that run on Sigma. We're looking for **PhD students** that are passionate about the intersection of AI, business, and data.


**What You'll Do**


* Conduct original AI/ML research in search, recommendations, natural language processing, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist, Biosensing - Vivalnk, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=edc2b088d4f16363</link>
        <description>**POSITION: Principal Data Scientist, Biosensing**

PURPOSE OF JOB

The Principal Data Scientist will oversee development of novel algorithms and AI/ML methods to bridge densely collected digital measures from wearable sensor devices to multimodal systems. This role will focus on creating edge\- and cloud\-based algorithmic pipelines for biomedical signal processing and translating research findings into practical, production\-ready solutions to empower users of the Vivalink platform.

Projects will involve establishing methodologies for building and implementing machine learning models using multi\-modal data sets, and extracting the features from raw data that correlate to measures of interest. In addition to modeling, development will include software tools and scripts at scale to support data analysis and interpretation.

MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

The principal data scientist will apply biomedical knowledge and data science to develop new algorithm\-based products and feat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
