<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Analyst - Strava</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b036e535ada0a751</link>
        <description>**Location**
------------


Strava SF

**Employment Type**
-------------------


Full time

**Location Type**
-----------------


Hybrid

**Department**
--------------


DepartmentTechnologyData and Insights

**Compensation**
----------------

* $176K – $187K • Offers Equity


This range reflects base compensation only and does not include equity or benefits. Your recruiter can share more details about the full compensation package during the hiring process.


At Strava, we know our employees are the most important ingredient to our success, and our compensation and total rewards programs reflect that. We take a market\-based approach to pay, and pay may vary depending on the department and your location. Salary ranges are categorized into one of three zones based on a cost of labor index for that geographic area. We will determine the candidate’s starting pay based on job\-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location, and market conditions. We may modify these ranges in t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Scope Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e61f2258f4732d6d</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Waymo's Product Management Team is a mission\-driven team responsible for writing and enacting first\-of\-their\-kind playbooks to bring fully autonomous driving technology to market. Our team develops simple solutions for complex problems by orchestrating cross\-functional efforts to safely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Scope Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=42bcec796a8d44e3</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Waymo's Product Management Team is a mission\-driven team responsible for writing and enacting first\-of\-their\-kind playbooks to bring fully autonomous driving technology to market. Our team develops simple solutions for complex problems by orchestrating cross\-functional efforts to safely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship, Audio &amp; Sensor Software Engineer, Vehicle Engineering (Summer 2026) - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8d6be84292cf2a58</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Consider before submitting an application:

  

This position is expected to start May 2026 and continue through summer term (ending approximately August 2026 or later, if available). We ask for a minimum of 12 weeks, full\-time (40 hours/week) and on\-site, for most internships. Our internship program is for students who are actively enrolled in an academic program. Recent graduates seeking employment after graduation and not returning to school should apply for full\-time positions, not internships.


International Students: If your work authorization is through CPT, please consult your school on your ability to work 40 hours per week before applying. You must be able to work 40 hours per week on\-site. Many students will be limited to part\-time during the academic year.


The Internship Recruiting Team is driven by the passion to recognize and develop emerging talent. Our year\-round program places the best students in positions where they will grow technically, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Process Development Engineer, Metrology - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1d5062b85d2f9868</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Tesla is looking for a highly motivated process development engineer to create, develop and scale up manufacturing processes for our cutting\-edge Tesla battery cell manufacturing line. This role will invent, develop, scale up and optimize battery manufacturing processes within a cross\-functional engineering team responsible for the development lifecycle and launch into manufacturing. In this role, you will work closely with many organizations both internal and external to Tesla taking new battery designs from initial concept through into full production.


The battery cell is a critical component in Tesla vehicles and storage systems. This role will have the opportunity to make meaningful contributions to our products. The work environment is demanding, fast\-paced and incredibly exciting. The ideal candidate should be ready to push their limits, as they join in highly motivated and capable team to make unbelieve things into reality.

 **What You'll Do*** Drive dev</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Competitive Intelligence) - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=522b2a91c85811e4</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Competitive Intelligence Team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

The Competitive Intelligence team works to understand the strategy and performance of Uber and other companies with similar products through a combination of external and internal data. Uber operates in a diverse array of markets and product categories filled with rapidly evolving competing options; assessing the success or failure of a product or strategy depends on understanding this context. Doing this, and doing it well, is an interesting and challenging problem. The team uses its data analysis, statistical modeling, economics, and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Competitive Intelligence) - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=78f0ac2a20b8c548</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Competitive Intelligence Team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

The Competitive Intelligence team works to understand the strategy and performance of Uber and other companies with similar products through a combination of external and internal data. Uber operates in a diverse array of markets and product categories filled with rapidly evolving competing options; assessing the success or failure of a product or strategy depends on understanding this context. Doing this, and doing it well, is an interesting and challenging problem. The team uses its data analysis, statistical modeling, economics, and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>IC Wire Bond, Die Attach and Flip Chip Engineer - Silitronics Solutions, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ed1e43b68da97b94</link>
        <description>Silitronics takes pride in delivering Vertically Integrated Design and Assembly Services for next\-generation products in AI/ML, Silicon Photonics, High Performance Computing, IoT Sensors, Medical, Defense, LiDAR, RF, and Commercial Applications. Our team brings over 100 years of combined domain expertise in Complex Assembly, Substrate and Board Design, Silicon Assembly, and automated Photonics Active Alignment. Silitronics specializes in advanced Semiconductor IC and Photonics PIC assembly, complemented by value\-added design engineering services.

We are seeking a driven IC Assembly Engineer to support the development of fully automated die attach and flip chip assembly processes. This role involves contributing to complex tooling, precision fixtures, and advanced assembly solutions, including photonics applications. It is an excellent opportunity for an engineer passionate about hands\-on engineering, learning advanced photonics assembly techniques, and pioneering silicon photonics </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applications Engineer (ML/Auto Defect Classification) - PDF Solutions, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c81b35d3235a3b42</link>
        <description>Overview:

**Role Summary**  

We are seeking a **Senior Applications Engineer** to join our team, focusing on the development of cutting\-edge machine learning and artificial intelligence solutions for the semiconductor industry. The ideal candidate will have extensive experience in creating robust and scalable software, with a strong background in data analysis, machine learning, and containerization technologies.
Responsibilities:
* **Design and Implement ML/AI Algorithms:** Help develop and implement advanced machine learning and AI\-based algorithms for the automatic classification of defects in semiconductor inspection tools.
* **Data Analysis:** Analyze large volumes of defect data to identify critical patterns, trends, and anomalies, using this analysis to inform model development.
* **Training and Model Development:** Train, validate, and deploy defect classification models, ensuring they meet strict performance and accuracy requirements.
* **System Optimization:** Continuousl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Scientist (Senior Consultant) - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4628289a62607241</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ConvergeCONSUMER - Data Scientist (Senior Consultant) - Innovation_Delivery_Transformation - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=58cea49ce108a9bb</link>
        <description>Are you an experienced Data Scientist who has led the development of world\-class software or digital products? Are you looking for an opportunity to expand your scope and lead products used by some of the biggest and most influential businesses around the world? If the answer to these questions is yes, we would like to talk with you.  

  

**The Team**  

  

ConvergeCONSUMER **™** is a product\-driven business that combines differentiated consumer insights with robust prediction and optimization capabilities to help consumer\-focused businesses improve decision\-making and deliver personalized experiences to drive growth, consumer loyalty, and profitability. We operate with the speed and agility of a startup within the world's largest professional services firm.  

  

We drive value for our clients by optimizing decisions and actions at a level of granularity only made possible with today's data and technology. ConvergeCONSUMER's suite of solutions helps consumer\-facing businesses</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Operations Engineer (DevOps/MLOps) - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ab59de9298cecf92</link>
        <description>We are seeking an experienced Staff Software Development Engineer with deep expertise in cloud infrastructure and a passion for building scalable, production‑grade ML systems. As part of the Applied Research and Technology Services organization, you will play a meaningful role crafting the operational backbone for high‑performance, reliable, and globally scaled machine learning services. In this role, you’ll work closely with multi\-functional collaborators. These include Adobe Research, Adobe AI Platforms, and product engineering teams. Together, you will architect solutions that speed up innovation and improve service resilience. You will also provide technical leadership and define, document, and enforce guidelines adopted across teams. You will own technical direction for core service infrastructure and MLOps, influence architectural decisions across multiple teams, and raise the operational maturity of the organization through standards, reusable platforms, and mentorship. You wil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer - Test Automation - KLA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=463a562e09f02043</link>
        <description>Company Overview
KLA is a global leader in diversified electronics for the semiconductor manufacturing ecosystem. Virtually every electronic device in the world is produced using our technologies. No laptop, smartphone, wearable device, voice\-controlled gadget, flexible screen, VR device or smart car would have made it into your hands without us. KLA invents systems and solutions for the manufacturing of wafers and reticles, integrated circuits, packaging, printed circuit boards and flat panel displays. The innovative ideas and devices that are advancing humanity all begin with inspiration, research and development. KLA focuses more than average on innovation and we invest 15% of sales back into R\&amp;D. Our expert teams of physicists, engineers, data scientists and problem\-solvers work together with the world’s leading technology providers to accelerate the delivery of tomorrow’s electronic devices. Life here is exciting and our teams thrive on tackling really hard problems. There is n</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager III, AI/ML, Cloud AI Systems - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cdb47d7888796038</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in program management.
* Experience managing machine learning or artificial intelligence programs.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of experience managing cross\-functional and cross\-team projects.
* Experience with quantitative analysis, cost\-effectiveness assessment techniques, and data quality metrics for AI products.
* Experience with machine learning algorithms and tools (e.g. TensorFlow), artificial intelligence, or deep learning.
* Experience in large\-scale high performance serving systems.
* Experience in communicating technical concepts to non\-technical audiences.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, yo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=362115024eda6496</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in product management or related technical role.
* 3 years of expe</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a5c9d6b28c62945</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager I, Machine Learning, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=16bd58a0803ea8bf</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Kirkland, WA, USA; New York, NY, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a relevant field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in program management.
* 8</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7e12063abf52b3ad</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Data &amp; Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=85dcda190e4e1590</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4617


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Waymo Mapping team's goal is to build a high resolution map of the world to support safe autonomous driving. We work on creating the map using a combination of automa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer II, Search - PlayStation</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6a9117e61d6c35de</link>
        <description>Position Type:
Location(s):
United States, San Mateo, CA
Date Posted:
Job ID:
R\-123175
  
**Why PlayStation?**


PlayStation isn’t just the Best Place to Play — it’s also the Best Place to Work. Today, we’re recognized as a global leader in entertainment producing The PlayStation family of products and services including PlayStation®5, PlayStation®4, PlayStation®VR, PlayStation®Plus, acclaimed PlayStation software titles from PlayStation Studios, and more.


PlayStation also strives to create an inclusive environment that empowers employees and embraces diversity. We welcome and encourage everyone who has a passion and curiosity for innovation, technology, and play to explore our open positions and join our growing global team.


The PlayStation brand falls under Sony Interactive Entertainment, a wholly\-owned subsidiary of Sony Group Corporation.

**Mid\-Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Search**

**San Mateo, CA**


Do you want to join a Machine Learning team committed to personaliz</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Manager - AI Context - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3da9eb2dac6469d6</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the AI Foundations Product Management Team at Intuit as a Senior Staff Product Manager for our AI Context Platform. Our AI Foundations team is part of the Product Development Acceleration (PDX) organization. We empower developers, including data scientists, ML engineers, and software engineers, across Intuit to build, train, deploy, and innovate with Machine Learning, Generative AI, and Agentic AI technologies. Our goal is to deliver high\-impact, AI\-native product experiences that delight our customers and transform the industry.  

  

 We are seeking a highly technical product manager to define the future of our developer platform capabilities that provide context to the AI. You will be the driving force in bridging Data and AI Platform capabilities, recognizing that high\-quality data is the foundational pillar for high\-quality AI. You will own and innovate on key platform services, including but not limited to: Feature Management: Defining t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI/ML Modeling Engineer I (Intern)- United States - Cisco</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9ee6c25aede7fb7f</link>
        <description>Please note this posting is to advertise potential job opportunities. This exact role may not be open today but could open in the near future. When you apply, a Cisco representative may contact you directly if a relevant position opens.
  
  

Applications are accepted until further notice.
  
  

Meet the Team
  
  

Join a dynamic team of engineers and data scientists focused on building the next generation of intelligent systems. We work at the intersection of software engineering and machine learning, developing scalable pipelines and models that power Cisco’s vast ecosystem. Our team thrives on collaboration, innovation, and the drive to turn complex data into seamless user experiences.
  
  

Your Impact
  
  

As an AI/ML Modeling Engineer Intern, you will apply your foundational knowledge of computer science and mathematics to solve real\-world challenges. You will work closely with senior engineers to support the machine learning lifecycle, from data acquisition and cleaning t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI/ML Modeling Engineer II (Intern)- United States - Cisco</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6ceb9d972aef5924</link>
        <description>Please note this posting is to advertise potential job opportunities. This exact role may not be open today but could open in the near future. When you apply, a Cisco representative may contact you directly if a relevant position opens.
  
  

Applications are accepted until further notice.
  
  

Meet the Team
  
  

Join a dynamic team of engineers and data scientists focused on building the next generation of intelligent systems. We work at the intersection of software engineering and machine learning, developing scalable pipelines and models that power Cisco’s vast ecosystem. Our team thrives on collaboration, innovation, and the drive to turn complex data into seamless user experiences.
  
  

Your Impact
  
  

As an AI/ML Modeling Engineer Intern, you will apply your foundational knowledge of computer science and mathematics to solve real\-world challenges. You will work closely with senior engineers to support the machine learning lifecycle, from data acquisition and cleaning t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (entry) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=594024dd0919edef</link>
        <description>Hi there! If you're looking to make a real\-world impact fast while leveling up your skills in a high\-growth startup, we might be the right place for you!**Why join Jerry?**


We’re Jerry, and we’re building the first AI\-powered AllCar™ app to completely rethink what it means to own a car. Car insurance, maintenance, repairs, financing—we’re simplifying it all into one seamless mobile experience. Our users already save over $1,000/year with us, and we’ve grown revenue 60x in the last 5 years.


Now we’re scaling from 5M to 50M users, and we need sharp, curious engineers located in the SF area to help us get there.


**Here’s what you’ll get:**


✅ Impact from Day One — you’ll be writing production code within your first few weeks.


✅ Backed and booming — we’ve raised $240M\+ and are cash\-flow positive.


✅ Modern tech stack — React, Node, Python, AWS, TypeScript, and more.


✅ Mentorship \+ learning — work with top engineers from companies like Nvidia, TikTok, and Cepton.


✅ Merit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Data Scientist, Risk and Payments - Owner.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d2a27a7b46fffea8</link>
        <description>**About** **Owner.com**


Owner is the AI growth system for local restaurants.

  

Our AI continuously improves SEO, marketing, and online ordering to grow first\-party orders. Unlike other companies that force small business owners to master their software to drive sales, Owner gives them a proven system run by experts.

  

Owner is like having an army of engineers and marketers on your side, just like the big chains.

 **Our vision**


We’re starting by helping independent restaurants succeed online.

  

But it’s not just restaurants that need our help. Most local businesses are struggling with these same problems. Huge technology corporations are taking their customers, bleeding their profits, and making it hard for them to survive.

  

Once we nail the solution for restaurants – we’ll scale it into every other local business type.

  

In the future we envision, tens of millions of local business owners will use our technology to succeed in the digital age.

  

Read our Series</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Systems Engineer - Middleware &amp; Diagnostics - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f33b311fd90226e3</link>
        <description>This is an opportunity to join the Software Systems Engineering team to participate in building the Zoox robotaxi, the first in the world to operate on public roads. The Software Systems Engineering team is responsible for defining SW development processes and ensuring that all safety\-critical software meets a high safety bar for production vehicles.  

In this role, you will help introduce and drive the adoption of software development best practices across middleware components, including requirements, architectural design, code quality, and testing strategy; contributing to defining diagnostics strategies and appropriate system reactions to ensure robust, safe, and maintainable operation.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Act as a cross\-functional bridge between middleware developers, and safety teams to ensure aligned design decisions and requirements.
* Develop and maintain a holistic architectural view of the middleware stack, including dependencies, interfaces and potential f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Manufacturing Diagnostics Engineer - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dabaece54a95d792</link>
        <description>As a Manufacturing Diagnostics Engineer on the Test \&amp; Diagnostics Engineering team, you will play a critical role in driving the troubleshooting and debug efforts to ensure we meet our aggressive scaling plans. In this role, you will provide leadership on the line and build a team of engineers to triage, respond to, and resolve vehicle/system issues across multiple manufacturing lines. Being able to advocate and implement new test coverage, diagnostic tooling, and infrastructure is essential for this role.  

  

The Manufacturing Diagnostics Engineer will begin with a 6\-month assignment in Alabama before being based in the Bay Area full\-time.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Perform troubleshooting and debug efforts on the main robotaxi assembly line and other manufacturing locations. You will triage issues spanning vehicle software, harnesses, networking and communication (CAN, LIN, automotive Ethernet), hardware, and infrastructure.
* Troubleshoot, contain, fix, and escalate (a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Data &amp; Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f5979d3730e144c9</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Waymo Mapping team's goal is to build a high resolution map of the world to support safe autonomous driving. We work on creating the map using a combination of automatic and manual techniques and build the infrastructure to store, process, and distribute the map. Our team collaborates wit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Vision Algorithm Engineer - PICO Lab (San Jose) - ByteDance</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6b0b100c46440674</link>
        <description>**Location:**  

San Jose
  
  

**Team:**  

Technology
  
  

**Employment Type:**  

Regular
  
  

**Job Code:**  

A174273
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About Team
  
PICO’s Imaging Systems \&amp; Human Engineering team is looking for passionate and versatile imaging experts to work on next\-generation imaging algorithms that deliver top\-tier visual experiences across PICO products, from camera capture to display rendering.
  
  

Our team focuses on the end\-to\-end imaging pipeline, bridging camera systems, display technologies, and human visual perception. We develop and evaluate imaging algorithms that span optical design, digital image processing, computer vision, and system\-level optimization, with a strong emphasis on image quality, efficiency, and real\-world user experience.
  
  

Team members play a key role in shaping both technology direction and productization roadmaps, contributing to the future of imaging technologies and their applications in VR/MR/AR devices
  
  </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer - Backend - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=371b123ed1445e56</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

You will be a Senior Software Engineer in the Machine Learning Platform team and involved in the development and implementation of the infrastructure layer for multi\-modal data processing and ML. The ideal candidate will be able to identify issues, provide solutions and implement the fixes as well as setting a high technical excellence bar in all things we do. You'll be able to collaborate across Platform Engineering teams which include areas such as networking, storage, compute, big data and cloud engineering.  

  

**What the Candidate Will Need / Bonus Points**
  

  

Design and deliver software and tools as part of our state\-of\-the\-art Machine Learning platform  

* Systems architecture design, including management of upstream and downstream dependencies
* Provide technical leadership, influence and partner with fellow engineers to architect, design and build scalable solutions for ML technology that can stand the test of scale and availability, whi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026) - Cadence Design Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=55f7883904d0c65e</link>
        <description>At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology.
AI \&amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026\)
As an intern, you will join a dynamic team of software developers and research‑minded engineers shaping the future of AI‑accelerated chip design and verification. You will be part of the SVG (System Verification Group), whose charter is to develop state‑of‑the‑art EDA software and hardware platforms used for high‑performance functional verification of advanced integrated circuits.
Our products include industry‑leading simulation (Xcelium), formal (Jasper), hardware acceleration (Palladium), FPGA prototyping (Protium), and embedded software bring‑up environments (Helium). Increasingly, these next‑generation verification systems incorporate AI, automation, and advanced data‑driven workflows \- and that’s where you come in!
What You’ll Work On
You will contribute to applied research and engineering projects that sit at the intersection of AI</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Anti-Cheat Engineer, ARM64 - Electronic Arts</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=168a826695554fb0</link>
        <description>### **General Information**

**Locations**: Redwood City, California, United States of America
* Location: Redwood City
* State: California
* Country: United States of America

  

Role ID
212781
Worker Type
Regular Employee
Studio/Department
CT \- Security
Work Model
Hybrid
### **Description \&amp; Requirements**

Electronic Arts creates next\-level entertainment experiences that inspire players and fans around the world. Here, everyone is part of the story. Part of a community that connects across the globe. A place where creativity thrives, new perspectives are invited, and ideas matter. A team where everyone makes play happen.
### **EA Security**

**Location:**Hybrid and Possibly Remote work options available across most North America locations


Join the SPEAR (Secure Product Engineering \&amp; Anti\-Cheat Response) Anti\-Cheat Engineering team, part of EA Security! Our mission is to ensure fair play across our many PC titles. We deliver EA Javelin Anticheat, a kernel anti\-cheat solution</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Agent Automation - Zoom Communications</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f5af786d5985c54f</link>
        <description>What you can expect


We're seeking an experienced AI Engineer specialized in agent orchestrator design and implementation, agent workflow, and LLM evaluation metrics and pipeline design. You'll be instrumental in developing and deploying intelligent agent systems that can understand context, orchestrate multi\-step processes, automate complex workflows, and execute tasks autonomously across Zoom. Your expertise will help us create agents that streamline operations, reduce manual intervention, and optimize end\-to\-end business processes through intelligent automation.


About the Team


The Agentic Workflow Automation team is committed to revolutionizing productivity by streamlining complex workflows, automating routine tasks, and making decisions with great speed and clarity. We are passionate about leveraging cutting\-edge technology to drive significant advancements in how people communicate and collaborate.


Responsibilities


* Designing and implementing agent architectures that</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Bioinformatics Research Engineer II - Freenome</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81f00d48d521c4d0</link>
        <description>**About this opportunity:**

  


As a Senior Bioinformatics Research Engineer, you will work on Freenome's computational platform for R\&amp;D, developing and deploying bioinformatics research software and tooling. As part of an interdisciplinary R\&amp;D team, you will work in close collaboration with computational biologists, machine learning scientists and software engineers. You will develop cutting edge solutions at the intersection of machine learning, genetic sequencing technology, biological data, and distributed systems. These contributions will drive our mission to diagnose cancer at its most actionable and early stages.



The role reports to a Director of Bioinformatics Research Engineering. This role can be a Hybrid role based in our Brisbane, California headquarters (2\-3 days per week in office), or remote.


**What you'll do:**


* Work at the intersection of computational biology, machine learning research, software engineering and biological data.
* Lead the development of F</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Application Engineer, Foundry - Parallel Bio</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0a00640e862bca2d</link>
        <description>At Parallel Bio, we are leveraging the human immune system to unlock safer, more effective drugs. We believe immunotherapies are the future of medicine, but their discovery is hindered by outdated models that fail to capture the complexity of the human immune system.


Our platform overcomes these challenges by combining best\-in\-class human immune organoids with massive scale and advanced computational methods, including AI and machine learning. This allows us to generate unprecedented, population\-scale insights into human health and disease.


We can rapidly discover new drugs that we know will work in patients from the start and understand how they will perform across an entire population—something not possible with today's technology. This knowledge will allow us to engineer therapies that will work for as many people as possible, ensuring a safe and effective cure for everyone.


We are a fast\-paced, venture\-backed company at a pivotal moment of growth. Join us on our journey </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, GenAI Quality, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbb72fcd176e000a</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Cambridge, MA, USA; New York, NY, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 7 years of experience leading technical project strategy, ML design, and working with industry\-scale ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience with design and architecture; and testing/launching software products.
* Experience with Generative AI technologies (e.g., LLM capabilities and applications).
* Experience working on search quality.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 5 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technic</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Manager, GenAI Workspace Safety and Security - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c4fac855740b6fce</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; New York, NY, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in product management, or a related technical role.
* 3 years of experience developing or launching products or technologies within Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning (AI/ML).
* Experience working with AI technologies and generative models.
* Experience taking products from conception to launch.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* 5 years of experience in a business function or role (e.g., strategic marketing, business operations, consulting).
* 5 years of experience in product management, specifically bringing innovative software products to market.
* 4 years of experience in a role preparing and delivering technical presentations to exec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Engineer, AI Compute, Google Distributed Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ce936191f4ed0023</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Cambridge, MA, USA; Raleigh, NC, USA; Durham, NC, USA; Seattle, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or related technical field, or equival</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Search Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=24a214971b475f10</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Pittsburgh, PA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience with software development in C\+\+ and Python.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all areas, including information </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Data Center Infrastructure Management Cooling - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=638776a688f698d1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with coding in C\+\+ and Python, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with distributed computing.
* 1 year of experience with SQL.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience working with two or more from the following: data analysis, data processing pipelines, distributed and parallel systems, machine learning, information retrieval, web application development, Unix/Linux environments, mobile application development, natural language processing, networking, developing large software systems, or security software development.
* Experience with monitoring systems and cooling systems.

**About the job**
-----------------


The DCIM (Data Center Infrastructure Management) Cooling team's mission is to deliver reliable, efficient, and intelligent cooling soluti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, YouTube ML Recommendations Systems - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9eb19e998f2c09f2</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, similar technical field of study, or equivalent practical experience
* 15 years of software engineering experience, including technical leadership
* Engineering experience in machine learning with a focus in ML systems and recommendations, software development, and implementation

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Computer Science or related field
* 15 years of professional experience in engineering
* Experience with full\-stack backend software development and implementation of sustainable, well\-designed systems and data pipelines, with production launch/impact
* Deep technical expertise in building large\-scale machine learning systems, and knowledge of ML models/algorithm design/implementation, and their application to real\-world problems
* Ability to communicate and collaborate effectively to create a shared sense of vision or purpose
* Demonstrated track record of technical</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=462e153bfa108b02</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**About Team:**
**The Merchant Technology team builds best\-in\-class experiences to make the Merchant's life easier for millions of buying decisions. We are a group of software engineers, data scientists, and machine learning experts pushing the boundaries of GenAI technology in complex enterprise applications. The Merchant Technology team is part of the US Omni Tech organization in Walmart Global Tech. We partner with our product, business and UX teams to drive significant measurable business impact. Our mission is to help Merchants make the right decisions for buying the best assortment mix for our customers to save money and live better.**
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bb26820e22eaf9c6</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**The Merchant Technology team builds best\-in\-class experiences to make the Merchant's life easier for millions of buying decisions. We are a group of software engineers, data scientists, and machine learning experts pushing the boundaries of GenAI technology in complex enterprise applications. The Merchant Technology team is part of the US Omni Tech organization in Walmart Global Tech. We partner with our product, business and UX teams to drive significant measurable business impact. Our mission is to help Merchants make the right decisions for buying the best assortment mix for our customers to save money and live better.**
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Manager - AI Context - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92e658ee3102acc</link>
        <description>**Category** Product Management **Location** Mountain View, California **Job ID** 19995
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the AI Foundations Product Management Team at Intuit as a Senior Staff Product Manager for our AI Context Platform. Our AI Foundations team is part of the Product Development Acceleration (PDX) organization. We empower developers, including data scientists, ML engineers, and software engineers, across Intuit to build, train, deploy, and innovate with Machine Learning, Generative AI, and Agentic AI technologies. Our goal is to deliver </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist – EDA Datacenter Observability and Reliability - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bce841bced1704c0</link>
        <description>NVIDIA’s Hardware Infrastructure organization is seeking a Senior Data Scientist to support EDA datacenter observability, hardware reliability, and capacity forecasting. In this role, you will work closely with hardware, software, and infrastructure engineering teams to analyze large\-scale observability and telemetry data generated by EDA workloads running across global CPU and GPU compute clusters.
We work with observability and platform teams to turn raw infrastructure and workload data into meaningful conclusions. These conclusions will help improve reliability, availability, performance, and long\-term datacenter scaling. Our work will directly inform operational decisions and long\-term planning for NVIDIA’s rapidly growing EDA environment.
What You’ll Be Doing:* Collaborate with hardware, software, infrastructure, and observability teams to define analytical requirements for EDA datacenter monitoring and reliability
* Examine large\-scale observability data, hardware health sign</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Compiler Engineer - Backend GPU - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d49adbd656acb48d</link>
        <description>NVIDIA's invention of the GPU 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing — with the GPU acting as the brain of computers, robots, and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. Today, we are increasingly known as “the AI computing company”.
We are searching for a Senior Backend Compiler Engineer with experience in LLVM code generation for an exciting and fun role in our GPU Software organization. Our Compiler team is responsible for constructing and emitting the highest performance GPU machine instructions for Graphics (OpenGL, Vulkan, DX) and Compute (CUDA, PTX, OpenCL, Fortran, C\+\+). This team is comprised of worldwide leading compiler engineering experts who provide leading edge performance and capabilities for NVIDIA's current and future complex parallel SIMT architectures.
What you will be doing:* Guid</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Mask Design Engineer - Hardware - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cbe8136cd407fb52</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to take on, that only we can pursue, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human creativity and intelligence. We would love to hear from you!
We are looking for a Senior Mask Layout Design Engineer, someone who is excited to join a growing and dynamic group of diverse individuals responsible for handling meaningful high\-speed mixed\-signal circuit designs.
What you'll be doing:* Performing physical layout for mixed\-signal functions like PLL's, high speed SerDes, Analog to Digital converters, ESD structures designs in state\-of\-the\-art sub\-micron CMOS technologies usi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products Off-Search Sourcing - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0969968bb2ebefdf</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover more about Sponsor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Development Engineer, C/C++ Hardware/Software Co-Design - MLA Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2d9eab0fadfa52e2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer II, C/C++ Hardware/Software Co-Design - MLA Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6d01d19d815085ac</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Off-Search, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=58374074f622ce59</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights.
  

  

We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover mo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate, Digital Finance Transformation - Data Scientist - Private Equity Performance Improvement (OPEN TO ALL US LOCATIONS) - Alvarez &amp; Marsal</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=92087e0417204ffa</link>
        <description>Location: San Francisco, CA, United States  

Date Posted: Feb 28, 2026

  

**Description**


**Digital Finance Transformation \- Data Scientist: Associate – Private Equity Performance Improvement**

**About Alvarez \&amp; Marsal**


Alvarez \&amp; Marsal (A\&amp;M) is a global consulting firm with over 10,000 entrepreneurial, action and results\-oriented professionals in over 40 countries. We take a hands\-on approach to solving our clients' problems and assisting them in reaching their potential. Our culture celebrates independent thinkers and doers who positively impact our clients and shape our industry. The collaborative environment and engaging work—guided by A\&amp;M's core values of Integrity, Quality, Objectivity, Fun, Personal Reward, and Inclusive Diversity—are why our people love working at A\&amp;M.

**The Team**


A\&amp;M’s Private Equity Performance Improvement Services (PEPI) practice works with private equity held portfolio companies and provides our clients with solutions to preserve and g</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Director, Translational Data Science – Hematology R&amp;D - AstraZeneca</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4f7c5393a788aea4</link>
        <description>**Job Title:** Associate Director, Translational Data Science – Hematology R\&amp;D  

**Location:** South San Francisco, California, United States

  

At AstraZeneca, we put patients first and strive to meet their unmet needs worldwide. Working here means being entrepreneurial, thinking big and working together to make the impossible a reality. If you are swift to action, confident to lead, willing to collaborate, and curious about what science can do, then you’re our kind of person.


Recognizing the importance of individualized flexibility, our ways of working allow employees to balance personal and work commitments while ensuring we continue to create a strong culture of collaboration and teamwork by engaging face\-to\-face in our offices **3 days a week**. Our head office is purposely designed with collaboration in mind, providing space where teams can come together to strategize, brainstorm and connect on key projects.


Our dedication to sustainability is also central to our cultur</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Qcells</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=56d181c3f0e6aa90</link>
        <description>**Description**


### **POSITION DESCRIPTION:**

  

We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Grid \&amp; Energy Analytics team within G\&amp;ES. In this role, you will lead the implementation of enterprise\-grade microservices that support the real\-time optimization and simulation of diverse energy assets participating in U.S. wholesale electricity markets including CAISO, ERCOT, NYISO, ISO\-NE, and PJM.  

  

This position will be preferably based out of our Santa Clara, San Francisco, Houston, or Seattle, or Atlanta offices.### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

* Work closely with Technical Lead to improve microservices including optimization, simulation, and market emulation.
* Drive microservice benchmarking, develop operations metrics, and continuously improve system performance using data\-driven insights.
* Own significant software components, including documentation and testing suites, training junior engineers where appropriate.
* Contribute to the next\-generation mercha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Qcells</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cfe6cc1991668234</link>
        <description>**Description**


### **POSITION DESCRIPTION:**

  

We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Grid \&amp; Energy Analytics team within G\&amp;ES. In this role, you will lead the implementation of enterprise\-grade microservices that support the real\-time optimization and simulation of diverse energy assets participating in U.S. wholesale electricity markets including CAISO, ERCOT, NYISO, ISO\-NE, and PJM.  

  

This position will be preferably based out of our Santa Clara, San Francisco, Houston, or Seattle, or Atlanta offices.### **RESPONSIBILITIES**

* Work closely with Technical Lead to improve microservices including optimization, simulation, and market emulation.
* Drive microservice benchmarking, develop operations metrics, and continuously improve system performance using data\-driven insights.
* Own significant software components, including documentation and testing suites, training junior engineers where appropriate.
* Contribute to the next\-generation mercha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Cloud Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8211a592f6d505ca</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's sof</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=253f2c1dc16a7e33</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML Recommendations, Rankings, Predictions, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b46b5caf995b062</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience building and deploying recommendation systems models (retrieval, prediction, ranking, personalization, search quality, embedding) in production; and experience building architecture.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation tec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, AI/ML GenAI, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0190ac1e33679a35</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience leading ML design and optimizing ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products.
* 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 2 years of experience with state of the art GenAI techniques (e.g., LLMs, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) or with GenAI\-related concepts (language modeling, computer vision).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technical direction.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex, matrixed organization involving cross\-functional,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - QBO Shared Experiences - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbdd6e3a81271bb3</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California **Job ID** 19494
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Senior Data Scientist. Our mission is to deliver delightful “Done for you” (DFY) customer experiences and accelerate GBSG user growth and retention through a data\-driven, platform\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies.
As a Senior Data Scientist, you will partner closely </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Business - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c6625ad62ed33d83</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

The Business Data Science team uses data and analytics to optimize business performance, drive growth, and foster meaningful partnerships, with the goal of ensuring the sustained and impactful expansion of OpenAI's initiatives to maximize the benefits of AGI for all of humanity. We partner with Sales (GTM), Marketing, Partnerships, Support, Finance, Product, and Growth.
  
  

About the Role
  
  

As a member of our Business Data Science team, you will help build a data\-driven culture around insight generation, decision making, and strategy at OpenAI. This role is focused on driving customer success within our business products (ChatGPT Team, ChatGPT Enterprise, and API). You will work on projects such as identifying opportunities for interventions within a customer lifecycle to drive activation \&amp; onboarding, identifying target audiences for new feature launches, and measuring the efficacy of emails, events, and other interventions to drive ongoing engagement w</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA)Staff, Data Scientist - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f8712b5cef69991</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**About the Role** We’re looking for a Staff Data Scientist to design and build advanced forecasting models to ensure accurate financial planning and analysis (FP\&amp;A) that power critical business decisions. You’ll build and deploy state\-of\-the\-art time series models (classical \+ ML \+ deep learning), drive explainability and trust (XAI), and explore next\-generation approaches such as graph neural networks for spatiotemporal and relational forecasting problems. You’ll partner closely with engineering, product, and stakeholders to deliver measurable impact at scale. **What You’ll Do**
* **Design and deploy** statistically and ML models to address high\-impact financial forecasting needs, ensuring alignment with Walmart’s business objectives.
* **Perform statistical analysis** across large data sets and within defined segments to empower data driven decisions.
* **Own E2E forecasting lifecyc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Analyst - Recidiviz</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d368f2584ef3ef10</link>
        <description>**Location:** Remote, New York City, or Oakland, CA


* Travel is encouraged approximately once every 6 months to state partners within the continental USA, and occasionally required. We expect these trips to include visits to prisons and parole offices.


**Role Type:** Full\-time


**Compensation**: $120,000


**Visa sponsorship:** Not available


**Hires remotely in:** United States


**Experience:** 5\+ years of full\-time, professional work experience



Recidiviz is thrilled to be hiring a Senior Data Analyst to join our team! We're a small, fast\-moving group that works with complex criminal justice data from our state partners and develops analyses that target the drivers of incarceration in specific systems. That's where you come in. We're looking for people who have an attention to detail to provide rigor to our analysis, creativity and inquisitiveness to identify and solve open\-ended problems, clarity to think through complex and variable data, flexibility to adjust in a ra</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; Machine Learning Intern – Operations - Matson</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ee0b7324dc8db4c5</link>
        <description>**About Us**


Matson has been the leading ocean shipping and logistics provider throughout the Pacific since 1882\. We are the supply chain lifeline for Hawaii, Alaska, Guam, and islands of the South Pacific. We also offer the top two ocean shipping services in the world’s largest trade lane \- Asia to the U.S. West Coast. With our subsidiaries Matson Terminals and Matson Logistics, our business focus is exceeding customer expectations with quality, reliability, and integrity.


We strive to operate in an environmentally sustainable manner and promote land\-based environmental programs in Hawaii, Guam, and Alaska. We help improve the communities in which we work and live through our community giving program that annually supports hundreds of local organizations.


Matson is honored to be certified as a Great Place to Work. Our team of dedicated and talented employees consistently deliver exceptional results for our customers and the communities in which we serve.


Learn more at matso</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior GTM Data Scientist New - Intercom</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=321b9d7d7adb85f1</link>
        <description>Intercom is the AI Customer Service company on a mission to help businesses provide incredible customer experiences.



Our AI agent Fin, the most advanced customer service AI agent on the market, lets businesses deliver always\-on, impeccable customer service and ultimately transform their customer experiences for the better. Fin can also be combined with our Helpdesk to become a complete solution called the Intercom Customer Service Suite, which provides AI enhanced support for the more complex or high touch queries that require a human agent.



Founded in 2011 and trusted by nearly 30,000 global businesses, Intercom is setting the new standard for customer service. Driven by our core values, we push boundaries, build with speed and intensity, and consistently deliver incredible value to our customers.

**What's the opportunity?**
---------------------------



Intercom is building a **GTM Data Products** team to embed machine learning and AI directly into our Sales and Marketing wo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Intern, Bixby Edge AI, Language (Summer) - Samsung Research America</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8e77ec814edded0d</link>
        <description>**Lab Summary:**



Advanced Intelligence Lab at Samsung Research America is working towards a vision of a world\-class voice assistant that provides a unified AI experience across multiple devices (Galaxy Smartphones, Galaxy Watch \&amp; Smart home appliances like TVs, Family Hub, IoT devices etc.) with deep integration and building AI assisted services intelligent solutions.



We work on applied research, innovative products, services, and experiences to delight our users by promoting new technologies to make best user experience with Bixby on devices to be intuitive, faster, seamless, more powerful, and multi\-dimensional across different product domains/categories. Our goal is to improve user's lifestyles through technology advancement and experience enrichment.


**Position Summary:**



Bixby is an intelligent personal assistant which is only available as a built\-in application on Samsung flagship devices and wearables. This application uses Natural Language Understanding to perfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Intern, Memory and Personalization (Summer) - Samsung Research America</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=038e06c5fa27ee8e</link>
        <description>**Lab Summary:**



Advanced Intelligence Lab at Samsung Research America is working towards a vision of a world\-class voice assistant that provides a unified AI experience across multiple devices (Galaxy Smartphones, Galaxy Watch \&amp; Smart home appliances like TVs, Family Hub, IoT devices etc.) with deep integration and building AI assisted services intelligent solutions.



We work on applied research, innovative products, services, and experiences to delight our users by promoting new technologies to make best user experience with Bixby on devices to be intuitive, faster, seamless, more powerful, and multi\-dimensional across different product domains/categories. Our goal is to improve user's lifestyles through technology advancement and experience enrichment.


**Position Summary:**



Bixby is an intelligent personal assistant which is only available as a built\-in application on Samsung flagship devices and wearables. This application uses Natural Language Understanding to perfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied AI Engineer - WorkOS</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b1b1d0796510f0e4</link>
        <description>**About WorkOS**


WorkOS builds tools and services for developers to help them implement authentication, identity, authorization, and overall enterprise readiness. We’re a fully distributed team with employees across North American time zones. We’re well\-funded, having raised $100m in funding from top investors including Greenoaks Capital, Lachy Groom, and Lightspeed Ventures. Our fast\-growing customer base includes rapidly growing SaaS companies like OpenAI, Cursor, Perplexity, Vercel, Plaid, and hundreds of others.

**About the Role**
------------------


We’re building an Applied AI function to dramatically increase productivity across Engineering, Sales, Support, and Operations.


As an Applied AI Engineer, you’ll design and ship production AI systems that change how WorkOS builds, sells, and supports software. Your focus is internal: building durable tools and workflows that teammates rely on every day.


You’ll work on a small, high‑ownership team that:

* Chooses problems bas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Machine Learning Engineer, Technical Lead, Evaluation - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f23b4d235cec13e</link>
        <description>Do you want to play a part in building a groundbreaking technology for large scale systems, generative AI experiences and shipping next generation of Apple products?  

  

You will improve and enrich lives of Apple users across the globe.  

  

Join the Evaluation team at Apple AIML.  

  

**Description**  

  

You will play a critical role in scaling up global evaluation of Apple AIML products, with the primary focus on next generation Siri and Apple Intelligence features.  

  

You will drive and scale our evaluation work to enable high\-velocity development and shipping of Generative AI features globally, in every country and language where Apple AIML features are available.  

  

You will drive LLM\-based evaluation as a product, delivering simulation\-based evaluation of personalized user experiences, reflective of cultural and language diversity of our customers.  

  

The focus of this technical lead role is strategy and execution of high quality evaluation datasets groun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Home Modeling - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81b718c5458f23d5</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5803
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning engineers who thrive on solving complex challenges and designi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytical Data Product - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a687a75e4c295db</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5202
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Content Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=279fa0acdf16465e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5885
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**Why Content Safety?**
-----------------------



As a **Principal Machine Learning Engineer** for Content Safety, you will define the future of proactive moderation</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Avatar - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3de71cfb924c3f12</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5891
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The **Avatar Team** is at the heart of the Roblox experience. The Roblox Avatar defines the identity of every player and is a core pillar of the metaverse. Our team </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Embodied AI and Smart NPCs - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f99abbc2884b814c</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5898
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Principal Machine Learning Engineer within the Creator Services Machine Intelligence team, you will focus on the research and development of Embodied AI and Beh</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Safety Core Data - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4fa7369cec471d81</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5759
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

#### **Why Safety?**



At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization’s mission is to become the leader in </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Ads - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b6a46f94f385e069</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5477
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning engineers who thrive on solving complex challenges and designi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Machine Learning Infrastructure Engineer, Content Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6e78cd0c47e72b17</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5749
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**Why Content Safety?**



Safety and civility are Roblox’s top priorities. Our mission is to protect our community by ensuring that all user\-generated content on th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Dynamic Economics - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9812bc1ecb5f1b0d</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5819
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a **Senior Machine Learning Engineer** on the **Economy ML** team, you will build models that power ranking, personalization, pricing, and optimization across Rob</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Creator Ecosystem - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=86126cb9407992f9</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5915
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior/Principal Data Scientist, you will be a strategic thought partner to our product and engineering leadership, specifically aligning with th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Machine Learning Engineer - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=30c093a2b8a15716</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 4733
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Distinguished Machine Learning Engineer/Technical Director in the Safety organization at Roblox, you will drive the overall technical vision and execution for a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Analytical Data Product (Temporary) - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7551d101967e86c9</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5392
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS (DSA)?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization’s mission is to increase the speed, frequency, and acumen of dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytical Data Product - Engine - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=baa3bcaf9d537827</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5748
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Generative AI - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c7741e88c36a750e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5610
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency, and acumen in making de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Risk Data Analyst - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6fddc9936f689654</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5720
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior Risk Data Analyst in our Payments organization, you will play a critical role in defending Roblox from various types of payment fraud across the platform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - App Performance - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=49eee3b459fce011</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5887
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making decisions at scale by instilling a data\</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal/Senior Machine Learning Scientist - Search and Discovery - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9c0a5d5df1e3455</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5927
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning researchers who thrive on solving complex challenges and desig</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Director - Data Science (Discovery) - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=559bb4df8e70354b</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5526
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, People Science - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2bc01ba9eb5d6b8b</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5460
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The People Science team at Roblox supports our Talent Acquisition organization and broader People, Places, \&amp; Systems group with applied statistics an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Ecosystem and Learning Platform - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fe68bb659770aec8</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5633
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency, and acumen in making de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Growth Measurement - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b59b60244b1feafd</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5694
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Machine Learning Engineer - Safety Experience - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7d89b400e85c1207</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5408
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The **Rights Manager** team and the **Content Suitability** team that are part of our **Safety Experience** are looking to hire a Sr Machine Learning Engineer for th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Safety Experience - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d0097f0dd9bd5aef</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5384
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The Safety Experience organization builds the tools and systems that give Roblox Users and Creators control over their experience and empower moderators to enforce o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, People Analytics - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d50df090864d3144</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5245
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The People Science \&amp; Analytics team at Roblox partners with our People, Places, \&amp; Systems organization to apply data science, applied statistics, an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=179e018a3941598e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5600
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

#### **WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of makin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Alt Defense - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0fe68b9e9cda8e1c</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5804
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY SAFETY?**



At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization’s mission is to become the leader in civil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Tooling &amp; Analytics Intern New - Nimble Robotics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b7937e2716900392</link>
        <description>**About Nimble**

Nimble is an AI robotics company building the autonomous supply chain to enable fast, efficient, and sustainable commerce. We’re developing a general\-purpose robot AI and a warehouse generalist superhumanoid robot, the first robot in the world capable of performing all core warehouse functions. We recently closed a $106M Series C at a $1B valuation,and we are continuing to grow our world\-class team.

Mission: to empower and inspire mankind to accomplish legendary feats by inventing robots that liberate us from the menial.

Vision: invent the Autonomous Supply Chain – everything from the inside of factories and warehouses to your front door – powered by industry\-generalist superhumanoids to deliver faster, more efficient, and more sustainable commerce.

Our founding team comes from the AI labs at Stanford and Carnegie Mellon and our board of directors include famed robotics and AI legends including Marc Raibert (founder of Boston Dynamics), Sebastian Thrun (founder </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Keywordless Search Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ac5224630ed4fa22</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), multimodal Machine Learning, ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging), or specialization in another ML field.
* Experience with experiment analysis.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience leading and optimizing industry\-scale machine learning infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Research Data Scientist, AI Data Intelligence - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=24b2d7dbd3bf3db6</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 10 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 8 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 12 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 10 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

**About the job**
-----------------


As a Senior Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a key innovation driver within our AI data organization. You will leverage your expertise in the full life\-cycle of data for large\-scale AI models (specifically Large Language Models (LLMs) from collection and distillation to precision curation and refinement.
In this</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Data Scientist, Statistics, Platform Analytics, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9255bcdd267e436b</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience in a data science role using data for business or product decisions.
* Experience analyzing data from various sources such as product instrumentation, customer support systems, and internal operational tools.
* Experience with SQL, Python or R programming including advanced data analysis, statistical modeling, and data visualization.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in a relevant quantitati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Data Scientist, Statistics, Platform Analytics, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0b1e6679a2ebae48</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience in a data science role using data for business or product decisions.
* Experience analyzing data from various sources such as product instrumentation, customer support systems, and internal operational tools.
* Experience with SQL, Python or R programming including advanced data analysis, statistical modeling, and data visualization.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in a relevant quantitati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Intuit Customer Success - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0f6148143645cc2a</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Intuit Customer Success data science team as a Staff Data Scientist to shape the strategy to enable best\-in\-class customer experiences for QuickBook customers.The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most important customer and business challenges.

 **Responsibilities**


We are seeking a Staff Data Scientist to deliver impactful insights into business performance and growth opportunities, build predictive models and insights, and drive measurable outcomes. This role requires a strong background in quantitative analysis, data\-driven decision\-making, and expertise in working with large data sets.
* Conceptualize business problems or opportunities, formulate hypotheses and goals, define key metrics, and make actionable recommendati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, App SW - Wayve</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc190c129d35caea</link>
        <description>At Wayve we're committed to creating a diverse, fair and respectful culture that is inclusive of everyone based on their unique skills and perspectives, and regardless of sex, race, religion or belief, ethnic or national origin, disability, age, citizenship, marital, domestic or civil partnership status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, pregnancy or related condition (including breastfeeding) or any other basis as protected by applicable law.


**About us**
------------

Founded in 2017, Wayve is the leading developer of Embodied AI technology. Our advanced AI software and foundation models enable vehicles to perceive, understand, and navigate any complex environment, enhancing the usability and safety of automated driving systems.



Our vision is to create autonomy that propels the world forward. Our intelligent, mapless, and hardware\-agnostic AI products are designed for automakers, accelerating the transition from assisted to automated driving.
  

  

In our f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Agentic Platform - Micron Technology</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fb60204ae54a34bf</link>
        <description>**Our vision is to transform how the world uses information to enrich life for** ***all*** **.**

Micron Technology is a world leader in innovating memory and storage solutions that accelerate the transformation of information into intelligence, inspiring the world to learn, communicate and advance faster than ever.


Micron’s Data Science team builds AI and data‑driven capabilities that power breakthroughs in semiconductor process technology, product engineering, and manufacturing. We work hands\-on with massive datasets, advanced modeling tools, and cross\-disciplinary engineering teams to push the boundaries of intelligent automation and decision\-making.
In this role, you’ll design and deploy AI systems that directly accelerate semiconductor design, verification, validation, and manufacturing. You’ll shape how agentic AI, LLMs, and automated decision systems integrate into Micron’s workflows, improving speed, accuracy, and scalability across the company.
**Responsibilities:*** Buil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Model Design Staff - Language Engineer - Microsoft</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d545902eea1b2ce</link>
        <description>**Overview**  


Microsoft AI is pushing the boundaries of technology. We are creating unique, beautiful and powerful products that will change lives. As a small, friendly, fast\-moving team, we support each other to do the best work of our lives, always looking to break new ground, fast. We are proud of what we build, how we build it and that our products will define the AI era. We run lean, obsess about users, and always make our decisions based on the evidence. We ship regularly, so your work will have real and immediate impact. It’s a time of huge change in the AI landscape, and this role will put you right in the heart of it.

We’re on the lookout for a detail\-oriented **Language Engineer** to help build the next wave of capabilities of our personal AI, Copilot. Language is an increasingly important modality for how we interact with computers. As a Language Engineer on the Copilot team, you will be responsible for how Copilot wields language. You will collaboratively work with da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
