<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Manager, Data for Applied AI Models - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0bd3eea7627490f6</link>
        <description>Join us at the forefront of redefining how people interact with their devices. On the Siri team, we’re solving the challenge of building and shipping powerful LLMs that shape the way millions of Apple customers get things done every day. As our Data lead, you will help craft the future of on\-device AI by developing powerful yet compact LLMs that bring personalized, private, and low\-latency experiences to users. This is a high\-impact role for a hands\-on technical leader who thrives at the intersection of cutting\-edge AI development and product delivery.  

  

**Description**  

  

We are seeking a deeply technical manager to lead our Data team. You will be responsible for understanding and drafting requirements, developing annotation tools and workflows, and managing the delivery and quality of data. The Data team is an immediate partner to our applied ML team, jointly responsible for developing and shipping production models at Apple scale. The huge importance of data on product</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Forward Deployed Product Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc4d79d08da1b73f</link>
        <description>TypeSafe is a frontier model lab. We build reliable and general AI systems to power economically valuable automation. Our mission is to usher in a new era of Transformative Artificial Intelligence (TAI): technology with the power to drive a societal shift on the scale of the agricultural and industrial revolutions.


While others chase benchmarks and academic puzzles, we’ve been quietly rethinking the LLM stack from first principles — building a new kind of general frontier model designed for real\-world reliability, decision\-making, and autonomy in production.


We’re a small, fast\-moving team from OpenAI, Google Brain, and Meta/FAIR, backed by top\-tier investors. Since mid\-2024, we’ve been engineering the foundation for what comes after the current “state\-of\-the\-art” — a model that actually gets things done.

**About the Role**
==================


Our tech stack is primarily Python. We also use TypeScript, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS for frontend, with Kubernetes for orchestrat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Borglet Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=70c56a7bbc4e571f</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience programming in C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products.
* 5 years of experience building and developing large\-scale infrastructure, distributed systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage, or hardware architecture.
* 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience with system software, distributed systems, and complex multi\-component software systems.
* Experience in reliability, efficiency, and scale, as well as in developing and releasing system software products and C/C\+\+ programming.
* Familiarity with the Linux kernel interface and containers.
* Understanding of key concepts of performance analysis and tuning.
* Excellent data analysis and SQL skills.

**Ab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=32291f54ab06a427</link>
        <description>NVIDIA's data centers host ground\-breaking products across high\-performance computing to machine learning applications for autonomous vehicles and healthcare! At the heart of our data centers is the ability to engineer integrated system designs in close coupling to NVIDIA's industry\-leading GPU products. We are seeking a Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer to accelerate next\-generation solutions.
The Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer is responsible for working with industry partners to align the strategic design, deployment, and optimization of high\-capacity pathways—terrestrial long\-haul and subsea—that interconnect AI Factories. You will act as the bridge between physical fiber infrastructure and global\-scale AI deployments.
What you’ll be doing:* Participate with partners on diverse long\-haul terrestrial routes to ensure network resilience and high\-capacity data flow between regional AI hubs.
* Participate in subsea and terrestrial consortiums to enable capa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8fcf7fff04f1f9c3</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has been transforming computer graphics, PC gaming, and accelerated computing for more than 30 years. Today, we're at the forefront of AI innovation powering breakthroughs in research, autonomous vehicles, robotics, and more. The DGX Cloud team builds and operates the AI infrastructure that fuels this progress.
We’re looking for a Senior Full\-Stack Software Engineer to join the AI Hub team within the DGX Cloud AI Infrastructure organization. The AI Hub team accelerates AI research by ensuring NVIDIA’s AI infrastructure is used efficiently, transparently, and at scale. Our primary goal is to build a unified, self\-service “single pane of glass” portal that enables AI researchers to efficiently manage, monitor, and optimize their use of Managed AI research Superclusters.
What You’ll Be Doing:* Lead the architecture and delivery of high\-scale web products across frontend, backend services, and data layers, with clear availability and latency targets (SLOs/SLAs).
* Own multi\-team</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI/ML Engineer-5 - Realign</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2b37a599430fcece</link>
        <description>San Francisco, California 94016 Posted February 25th, 2026
 Looking for more job opportunities? Click here!


  
Job Type: Contract


Job Category: IT


Job Description


**Role: Sr. AI/ML Engineer**

* **Experience** – 10\+ Years
* **Location** \- San Francisco, CA – LOCALS Only

**Required Qualifications**  

* Deep expertise in Machine Learning, Generative AI, LLMs, RAG, and AI orchestration.
* Strong understanding of Azure OpenAI, AWS Bedrock, or similar platforms.
* Experience deploying AI in regulated environments.
* Hands\-on architectural and engineering leadership capabilities.
* Strong communication skills with VP/Senior Director stakeholders.


 Preferred Qualifications  

* 12\+ years in AI/ML, data engineering, or digital transformation.
* Prior experience leading enterprise AI programs.
* Utility domain experience (wildfire, grid, operations).
* Knowledge of Responsible AI frameworks (NIST AI RMF, ISO 42001\).

  

**Roles \&amp; Responsibilities**  

**Role Overview**  

Uti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Early Stage Supply Chain Project - X Development</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=04f88456ad2297c4</link>
        <description>Software EngineeringMountain View, CA (HQ)



**About the Company:**



X is Alphabet’s moonshot factory. We are a diverse group of inventors and entrepreneurs who build and launch technologies that aim to improve the lives of millions, even billions, of people. Our goal: 10x impact on the world’s most intractable problems, not just 10% improvement. We approach projects that have the aspiration and riskiness of research with the speed and ambition of a startup.





**About the Team:**



We’re X’s moonshot for the global supply chain, applying AI to reduce waste, fragility, and inefficiency. We’re an agile team of experienced AI researchers, software engineers, and entrepreneurs working with visionary partners and customers around the world to make sure everyone has sustainable and reliable access to the food, medicine, clothing, and other goods and services they need.



We’re looking for people who are passionate about revolutionizing the global supply chain to join us at this criti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>COMPILER ENGINEER - DEBUG INFO, TOOLS - AMD</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94a15b3da6268bde</link>
        <description>Overview:
**WHAT YOU DO AT AMD CHANGES EVERYTHING**
At AMD, our mission is to build great products that accelerate next\-generation computing experiences—from AI and data centers, to PCs, gaming and embedded systems. Grounded in a culture of innovation and collaboration, we believe real progress comes from bold ideas, human ingenuity and a shared passion to create something extraordinary. When you join AMD, you’ll discover the real differentiator is our culture. We push the limits of innovation to solve the world’s most important challenges—striving for execution excellence, while being direct, humble, collaborative, and inclusive of diverse perspectives. Join us as we shape the future of AI and beyond. **Together, we advance your career.**
Responsibilities:
**THE ROLE:**
We are building first\-class compilation technology for HIP, OpenCL, OpenMP, and Python. In addition to HPC applications, our compilers are used in the development of AMD machine learning frameworks and libraries. We </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer AI/ML Ops - BlackLine</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=224560f3c02165ca</link>
        <description>Make Your Mark::

In new product design roles: develops and programs integrated software algorithms to structure, analyze and leverage data in product and systems applications in both structured and unstructured environments. Develops and communicates descriptive, diagnostic, predictive and prescriptive insights/algorithms. In product/systems improvement projects: uses machine language and statistical modeling techniques such as decision trees, logistic regression, Bayesian analysis and others to develop and evaluate algorithms to improve product/system performance, quality, data management and accuracy. In both theoretical development environments and specific product design, implementation and improvement environments, uses current programming language and technologies to translate algorithms and technical specifications into code. Completes programming and implements efficiencies, performs testing and debugging. Completes documentation and procedures for installation and maintenance</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=56d9c60e41101257</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6a5a28e369753401</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - PayPal</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3e2114b4a6b01f47</link>
        <description>**The Company**


PayPal has been revolutionizing commerce globally for more than 25 years. Creating innovative experiences that make moving money, selling, and shopping simple, personalized, and secure, PayPal empowers consumers and businesses in approximately 200 markets to join and thrive in the global economy.


We operate a global, two\-sided network at scale that connects hundreds of millions of merchants and consumers. We help merchants and consumers connect, transact, and complete payments, whether they are online or in person. PayPal is more than a connection to third\-party payment networks. We provide proprietary payment solutions accepted by merchants that enable the completion of payments on our platform on behalf of our customers.


We offer our customers the flexibility to use their accounts to purchase and receive payments for goods and services, as well as the ability to transfer and withdraw funds. We enable consumers to exchange funds more safely with merchants using</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Identity - Block</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=976d1456b7a1a13f</link>
        <description>Block is one company built from many blocks, all united by the same purpose of economic empowerment. The blocks that form our foundational teams — People, Finance, Counsel, Hardware, Information Security, Platform Infrastructure Engineering, and more — provide support and guidance at the corporate level. They work across business groups and around the globe, spanning time zones and disciplines to develop inclusive People policies, forecast finances, give legal counsel, safeguard systems, nurture new initiatives, and more. Every challenge creates possibilities, and we need different perspectives to see them all. Bring yours to Block.


**The Role**



The Identity Lifecycle team at Cash App ensures that our understanding of "who a customer is" stays accurate, compliant, and useful long after day one. In this role, you'll be embedded within the Trust: Identity \&amp; Controls organization and work closely with engineering, machine learning, risk, compliance, tax, and product partners to desi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal AI/ML Engineer - Palo Alto Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=55bf9fa35801743b</link>
        <description>Santa Clara, California, United States Product Engineering Ref ID: JR\-015095  

**Our Mission**


At Palo Alto Networks®, we’re united by a shared mission—to protect our digital way of life. We thrive at the intersection of innovation and impact, solving real\-world problems with cutting\-edge technology and bold thinking. Here, everyone has a voice, and every idea counts. If you’re ready to do the most meaningful work of your career alongside people who are just as passionate as you are, you’re in the right place.

**Who We Are**


In order to be the cybersecurity partner of choice, we must trailblaze the path and shape the future of our industry. This is something our employees work at each day and is defined by our values: Disruption, Collaboration, Execution, Integrity, and Inclusion. We weave AI into the fabric of everything we do and use it to augment the impact every individual can have. If you are passionate about solving real\-world problems and ideating beside the best and t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Group Product Manager, YouTube Shorts Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e5d4af9e36c63acb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **San Bruno, CA, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience in product management, shipping consumer products or features.
* 10 years of experience working cross\-functionally with engineering, data science, and UX/UI stakeholders.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning (ML) experimentation methodologies or recommendation systems.
* Experience in data analysis and leveraging product metrics to optimize algorithms and define product roadmaps.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* Experience delivering technical presentations to senior leadership and securing buy\-in for ML\-driven product ideas.
* Experience with discovery or adapting existing recommendation technology to a 0\-1 product surface</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Group Product Manager, YouTube Shorts Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2968647b8043eca9</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **San Bruno, CA, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience in product management, shipping consumer products or features.
* 10 years of experience working cross\-functionally with engineering, data science, and UX/UI stakeholders.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning (ML) experimentation methodologies or recommendation systems.
* Experience in data analysis and leveraging product metrics to optimize algorithms and define product roadmaps.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* Experience delivering technical presentations to senior leadership and securing buy\-in for ML\-driven product ideas.
* Experience with discovery or adapting existing recommendation technology to a 0\-1 product surface</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2ae7e83b4129de9b</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=937ccc2166fc35f0</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=482d8ed4498bc892</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>CAD Engineer - New College Grad 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9a62b1f91d5b9e0</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 fueled the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI \- the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to solve, that only we can seek, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human creativity and intelligence. Make the choice to join us today.
Join NVIDIA’s Advanced Technology Group—a fast paced team that crafts the next generation of process technologies for AI, HPC, automotive, and graphics. In this role, you will help contribute to flows and manage systems dealing with a range of data from packaging to VLSI library views to help streamline and improve productivity.
What you'll be doing:* Collaborate across internal library, packaging and design teams to implement flows t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - VSCO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fcb8a030781599dc</link>
        <description>**About VSCO**



VSCO (pronounced vis–co) is a platform that equips photographers with the tools, community, and exposure they need to expand creatively and professionally. VSCO maintains a rich and authentic creative environment that serves photographers at all levels – preserving a home for creative opportunity, inspiration, and connection. Our mission is to champion photographers so they can make it. We empower photographers to connect with other creatives and businesses with our suite of creative tools that spans from mobile to desktop and across our global community.



We are looking for people who are driven and demonstrate initiative in taking our company mission to the next level. Employees here have the opportunity to make a big impact, and believe that when we build together, we achieve stronger outcomes than we could alone.



Our values are critical pillars to our team culture and shape the way we hire. Read more about what you can expect when working at VSCO on our Caree</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship - On Product Performance Engineer - ASML</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=014e269116e47791</link>
        <description>**Introduction**


ASML US, including its affiliates and subsidiaries, bring together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop lithography machines that are key to producing faster, cheaper, more energy\-efficient microchips. We design, develop, integrate, market and service these advanced machines, which enable our customers \- the world’s leading chipmakers \- to reduce the size and increase the functionality of their microchips, which in turn leads to smaller, more powerful consumer electronics. Our headquarters are in Veldhoven, Netherlands and we have 18 office locations around the United States including main offices in Chandler, Arizona, San Jose and San Diego, California, Wilton, Connecticut, and Hillsboro, Oregon.

**Your Assignment**


This position is within the D\&amp;E Department, which is responsible is for the specification, design, implementation, integration, testing and optimizing of the ASML HMI’s E\-beam inspection and metrology products. ASML\-HMI H</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Site Reliability Engineer (SRE) - infinite choice</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=05beb20a88b8d487</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
------------------


We're seeking an exceptional Principal Site Reliability Engineer to architect, design, and build our SRE foundation from the ground up at InfiniteChoice. This is a rare greenfield opportunity to establish SRE practices, develop custom tooling, and create the reliability culture that will support our platform serving millions of users and billions in transaction volume.


As our Principal SRE, you'll combine deep technical expertise with strategic vision to build world\-class monitoring, observability, and automation systems. You'll have the autonomy to define our SRE processes, select technologies, and create the framework that ensures our systems are reliable, scalable, and performant.

**Location:** Remote \- US based**What You Will Do**
--------------------

### **SRE Foundation \&amp; Process Development**

* **Build SRE practices from scratch** \- define SLIs, SLOs, error budgets, and reliability metrics
* Establish incident response procedures,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Research Scientist II (Intern) United States - Cisco</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1456ae41917c00db</link>
        <description>Please note this posting is to advertise potential job opportunities. This exact role may not be open today but could open in the near future. When you apply, a Cisco representative may contact you directly if a relevant position opens.
  
  

Applications are accepted until further notice.
  
  

Meet the Team
  
  

Join a collaborative team of researchers and engineers dedicated to unlocking insights from substantial volumes of structured, unstructured, transactional, and real\-time data. Together, we analyze diverse data sources to understand customer usage patterns and deliver actionable, impactful insights using advanced metrics, algorithms, and statistical techniques.
  
  

Your Impact
  
  

As an AI Research Intern, you will drive innovation by contributing to sophisticated research in large language models (LLMs), natural language processing (NLP), and multimodal deep learning. You will work alongside senior researchers and cross\-functional teams to bridge the gap between t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google ADK AI Engineer - Infosys</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b3f03e22d717f43a</link>
        <description>Infosys is seeking **Google ADK AI Engineer.** In this role, you will interface with key stakeholders and apply your technical proficiency across different stages of the Software Development Life Cycle including Requirements Elicitation, Application Architecture definition and Design. You will play an important role in creating the high\-level design artifacts. You will also deliver high quality code deliverables for a module, lead validation for all types of testing and support activities related to implementation, transition, and warranty. You will be part of a learning culture, where teamwork and collaboration are encouraged, excellence is rewarded, and diversity is respected and valued.  

  

**Required Qualifications:*** Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education.
* Candidate must be located within commuting distance of **Cupertino, CA</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google ADK AI Engineer - Infosys</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=759dbdae4d524e89</link>
        <description>Infosys is seeking **Google ADK AI Engineer.** In this role, you will interface with key stakeholders and apply your technical proficiency across different stages of the Software Development Life Cycle including Requirements Elicitation, Application Architecture definition and Design. You will play an important role in creating the high\-level design artifacts. You will also deliver high quality code deliverables for a module, lead validation for all types of testing and support activities related to implementation, transition, and warranty. You will be part of a learning culture, where teamwork and collaboration are encouraged, excellence is rewarded, and diversity is respected and valued.  

  

**Required Qualifications:*** Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education.
* Candidate must be located within commuting distance of **Cupertino, CA</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - Software Developer - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e3d55e2faf39a9b0</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position Title: SAP iXp Intern \- Software Developer


Expected Start Date: April 2026


Duration: 6 months (potential extension for another 6 months)


Working Hours: 40/week (</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0270ac4b349b6312</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you\`ll do:**


Summary:


At SAP, we amplify the strength of AI technology, fusing it with our robust industry\-focused data and profound process knowledge. Our vision is to infuse every SAP application with sophisticated AI capabilities, revolutionizing the way businesses operate. Large Language Models (LLMs) hold immense potential to change the way we work and develop products. They are reshaping the landscape of Machine Learning across various domains. Our goal is to combine </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=75b1040dc0689b71</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you\`ll do:**


Summary:


At SAP, we amplify the strength of AI technology, fusing it with our robust industry\-focused data and profound process knowledge. Our vision is to infuse every SAP application with sophisticated AI capabilities, revolutionizing the way businesses operate. Large Language Models (LLMs) hold immense potential to change the way we work and develop products. They are reshaping the landscape of Machine Learning across various domains. Our goal is to combine </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Product Manager - Enterprise AI - AMD</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0c252514aca1d37f</link>
        <description>Overview:
**WHAT YOU DO AT AMD CHANGES EVERYTHING**
At AMD, our mission is to build great products that accelerate next\-generation computing experiences—from AI and data centers, to PCs, gaming and embedded systems. Grounded in a culture of innovation and collaboration, we believe real progress comes from bold ideas, human ingenuity and a shared passion to create something extraordinary. When you join AMD, you’ll discover the real differentiator is our culture. We push the limits of innovation to solve the world’s most important challenges—striving for execution excellence, while being direct, humble, collaborative, and inclusive of diverse perspectives. Join us as we shape the future of AI and beyond. **Together, we advance your career.**
Responsibilities:
**THE ROLE:**


This role sits within AMD’s Enterprise AI product organization, working at the intersection of AI software, infrastructure, and platform strategy. The team is responsible for shaping and delivering enterprise\-grade</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Intel and AI Intern - NetApp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6db7384c8151e55b</link>
        <description>**Own Every Moment at NetApp**


At NetApp, your ideas power innovation. We lead in intelligent data infrastructure—delivering unified storage, integrated data services, and solutions that help organizations unlock the full potential of their data, from AI to multicloud.


Ready to innovate and contribute to our path to $10B? Here, you'll collaborate with passionate teams, tackle real\-world challenges, and see your impact in how customers transform and grow. If you're ready to bring curiosity, creativity, and drive to every moment, NetApp is where your journey begins.


  
**Job Summary**
---------------


Organization Overview


NetApp storage systems hold 70 Exabytes of enterprise data. The Data Intelligence and AI Business Unit builds vision is to bring AI to data. We build platforms and services that enable enterprises to operationalize this data and AI at scale within the compliance boundaries of data. AIDE (AI Data Engine) is a core data platform product within the BU, focused o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ML Ops Intern - Mercedes-Benz Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d57da6647a38babb</link>
        <description>At Mercedes\-Benz Research \&amp; Development North America (MBRDNA), we are committed to delivering world\-class automotive technologies that push the boundaries of what is possible. Our teams of highly skilled engineers and designers use cutting\-edge software and technology, to enhance the driving experience and reduce environmental impact.  

The Mercedes\-Benz AI Experiences team is seeking a Machine Learning Engineering Intern to join our ML Product Development Team for Summer 2026\. In this role, you will help enhance our MLOps platform to support a diverse range of use cases powering AI projects that shape the future of Mercedes\-Benz vehicles. You will contribute to the development of ML pipelines, tools, and platform capabilities that enable experimentation, CI/CD, deployment, verification, validation, and monitoring of production models, while upholding strong data privacy standards and responsible AI principles. Working closely with cross\-functional development teams, you will</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Data for Perception Machine Learning - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=65a3faa19fa4d8ee</link>
        <description>We are seeking an experienced and highly skilled data scientist to join the Perception Data and Labeling team.. The team is responsible for training and evaluation data powering the perception (vision, lidar, and other modalities) ML models at Zoox. The candidate will work alongside data ops partners, ML engineers, software developers, and data engineers to improve model performance through high quality human\- and auto\-labeled data.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Define and implement scalable data quality measures across complex, multimodal data labeling pipelines
* Drive data\-centric ML model improvements to achieve critical Zoox milestones
* Support an org\-wide data ontology and class structure for perception models
* Determine trade\-offs and integrations between human\-labeled, human\-in\-the\-loop, and zero\-shot autolabeled data
* Build metrics to quantify labeling throughput, capacity, and annotator/vendor quality

### **Qualifications:**

* Master's or PhD degree in a f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Earner Growth), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e10955047184df03</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Earner Growth team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

Have you ever ordered a car service on Uber, and when the ride arrives, wondered how it got to you so fast? Ever ordered food on UberEats and wondered where the driver was before receiving your order and how long it took to get to the restaurant or if your order was ready when the courier arrived? Ever wondered why your grocery delivery from Uber always has the best apple picked? If so, Uber is for you. In our Sciences division, we strive to make magic within Uber's marketplace. This requires judgment to make difficult trade\-offs, blending algorith</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (Ads &amp; Offer), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=725e0d3e0220dcf1</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Ads \&amp; Offer team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of a Scientist, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross functional partners.
  

  

**About the Role**  

  

Have you ever ordered a car service on Uber, and when the ride arrives, wondered how it got to you so fast? Ever ordered food on UberEats and wondered where the driver was before receiving your order and how long it took to get to the restaurant or if your order was ready when the courier arrived? Ever wondered why your grocery delivery from Uber always has the best apple picked? If so, Uber is for you. In our Sciences division, we strive to make magic within Uber's marketplace. This requires judgment to make difficult trade\-offs, blending algorithms with human resourceful</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Scientist Intern (UberEats Courier Pricing), US - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e04bd1b2b7801fb6</link>
        <description>We're looking for PhD candidates to work with the Uber Eats Marketplace team as a Scientist intern during summer 2026 (12 weeks). As an intern, you will be embedded in a product team working on solving real\-world Uber problems under the supervision of an analyst on that team, and will have the opportunity to partner closely with Scientists, Software Engineers, Product Managers, and other cross\-functional partners.
  

  

**About the Team**  

  

The Uber Eats Marketplace team is the heart of the Uber Eats business. We build the platform and products that power the magical experience of connecting eaters, couriers, and restaurants. As a critical component of this ecosystem, the Courier Pricing team is responsible for the complex systems that determine courier payouts on every Uber Eats delivery worldwide.
  

  

Our mission is to build and refine a fully automated pricing system that optimizes our three\-sided marketplace for consumers, couriers, and merchants. We leverage sophisti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - VSCO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=da095374fa32049c</link>
        <description>**About VSCO**



VSCO (pronounced vis–co) is a platform that equips photographers with the tools, community, and exposure they need to expand creatively and professionally. VSCO maintains a rich and authentic creative environment that serves photographers at all levels – preserving a home for creative opportunity, inspiration, and connection. Our mission is to champion photographers so they can make it. We empower photographers to connect with other creatives and businesses with our suite of creative tools that spans from mobile to desktop and across our global community.



We are looking for people who are driven and demonstrate initiative in taking our company mission to the next level. Employees here have the opportunity to make a big impact, and believe that when we build together, we achieve stronger outcomes than we could alone.



Our values are critical pillars to our team culture and shape the way we hire. Read more about what you can expect when working at VSCO on our Caree</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship, AI Performance Engineer, Performance Optimization (Summer 2026) - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8ce700aa5d8b6518</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
Consider before submitting an application:


This position is expected to start May 2026 and continue through summer term (ending approximately August 2026 or later, if available). We ask for a minimum of 12 weeks, full\-time (40 hours/week) and on\-site, for most internships. Our internship program is for students who are actively enrolled in an academic program. Recent graduates seeking employment after graduation and not returning to school should apply for full\-time positions, not internships.


International Students: If your work authorization is through CPT, please consult your school on your ability to work 40 hours per week before applying. You must be able to work 40 hours per week on\-site. Many students will be limited to part\-time during the academic year.  

  



The Performance Optimization team takes research models and makes them run efficiently on Tesla's AI\-ASICs, powering Autopilot and Optimus. This role sits at the intersection of AI research</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML Services- Data Platform Engineer - GSK</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a25ec63d2a45d72c</link>
        <description>**Site Name:** South San Francisco 611 Gateway Blvd, Cambridge 300 Technology Square, Seattle Sixth Ave  

**Posted Date:** Feb 24 2026  

At GSK we see a world in which advanced applications of Machine Learning and AI will allow us to develop transformational medicines using the power of genetics, functional genomics, and machine learning. AI will also play a role in how we diagnose and use medicines to enable everyone to do more feel better and live longer. It is an ambitious vision that will require the development of products at the cutting edge of Machine Learning and AI.

  

We're looking for a highly skilled individual contributor who can consistently take a poorly defined business or technical problem, work it to a well\-defined problem/specification, and execute on it at a high level. They have a strong focus on metrics, both in the domains of system health/performance and the impact of their work. They are a model for the team on best practices for software development in ge</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr ML Ops Engineer - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=daf4a4241dc4709a</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Forward Deployed Robotics Engineer - Medra</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=347e6c832898b756</link>
        <description>**What We're Building:**
We have been quietly building the foundational layers of our Physical AI Scientist platform:  

 Physical AI that can operate scientific instruments with human\-level dexterity.  

 Scientific AI that can analyze results, reason about next steps, and close the loop autonomously.


This is an incredibly ambitious mission, but we believe that a team of ambitious people with high ownership can accomplish incredible things.

**The Team:**

* We’re a team of passionate, mission\-driven engineers from companies like Tesla, Amazon, SpaceX, and Neuralink. We’re collaborative and love moving fast, both with our product and on team trips skiing or go\-karting!
* As a team, we love nerding out about engineering and robotics — plus other topics like race cars or cooking. We like learning new things and then sharing our new knowledge with each other.
* Our team is opinionated and straightforward. We don’t mind intense discussions about design tradeoffs. If we have arguments</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Full Stack Software Engineer - Summer 2026 Internship - Medra</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ec13e877ffe52786</link>
        <description>**About the Role:**Paid Summer 2026 Internship (Jun. \- Aug., dates flexible). Candidates must work full\-time, in\-person at our San Francisco office located in the Mission.


**What We're Building:**


We have been quietly building the foundational layers of our Physical AI Scientist platform:  

 Physical AI that can operate scientific instruments with human\-level dexterity.  

 Scientific AI that can analyze results, reason about next steps, and close the loop autonomously.


This is an incredibly ambitious mission, but we believe that a team of ambitious people with high ownership can accomplish incredible things.

**The Team:**

* We’re a team of passionate, mission\-driven engineers from companies like Tesla, Amazon, SpaceX, and Neuralink. We’re collaborative and love moving fast, both with our product and on team trips skiing or go\-karting!
* As a team, we love nerding out about engineering and robotics — plus other topics like race cars or cooking. We like learning new thing</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, GPU Performance - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1cb81fad4b35b3e8</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Process Engineering Intern - Summer 2026 - Lam Research</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a21df53bf7ee40f1</link>
        <description>Requisition ID**194776**
Date posted**02/24/2026**
Work Location Model**On\-site**
Work Location**Fremont\-CA**
Work Country**United States****The group you’ll be a part of**
---------------------------------

  

The Office of the CTO is where innovation takes center stage. We inspire our global technical community to take on grand challenges, understand emerging trends, identify the critical inflections, and drive our sustainability, Environment, Social, and Governance (ESG) practices that will define the next generation of semiconductors and continued impact.

**The impact you’ll make**
--------------------------



In this role you will directly contribute to Lam Research’s Aether product group and process development efforts. You will work directly with experienced process and product development engineers developing the Aether products and process. Your work will lead to improvements in the equipment and systems that Lam provides to semiconductor manufacturers worldwide.

**What </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Machine Learning - Syntiant Corp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=342cdf5b1f51abde</link>
        <description>Syntiant Corp., a leader in the high\-growth AI software and semiconductor solutions space, is looking for an experienced and talented **Senior Software Engineer** to take on a critical role with expansive responsibilities in the Machine Learning team.


As a **Senior Software Engineer**, you will own and train computer vision models to run on edge devices. You will be responsible for ensuring the models run to spec and meet the customer needs. Ultimately, you will get the opportunity to apply machine learning in real world applications and see your work driving the latest edge AI devices.


**Requirements**
----------------

**Qualifications, Education, and Experience Required:**

* Masters in Computer Science/Engineering or related field.
* 5\+ years of experience developing and deploying ML models for vision applications.
* Strong C\+\+ and Python experience.
* Experience with ML frameworks (e.g. TensorFlow, PyTorch).
* Experience working in large, complex codebases.
* Experience wi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Machine Learning - Syntiant Corp</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=845178e882aff603</link>
        <description>**Summary Description****:**


Syntiant Corp., a leader in the high\-growth AI software and semiconductor solutions space, is looking for an experienced and talented **Senior Software Engineer** to take on a critical role with expansive responsibilities in the Machine Learning team.


As a **Senior Software Engineer**, you will own and train computer vision models to run on edge devices. You will be responsible for ensuring the models run to spec and meet the customer needs. Ultimately, you will get the opportunity to apply machine learning in real world applications and see your work driving the latest edge AI devices.


**Requirements**

**Qualifications, Education, and Experience Required:**

* Masters in Computer Science/Engineering or related field.
* 5\+ years of experience developing and deploying ML models for vision applications.
* Strong C\+\+ and Python experience.
* Experience with ML frameworks (e.g. TensorFlow, PyTorch).
* Experience working in large, complex codebases.
*</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II - MERCOR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c17d2525f9bdab9a</link>
        <description>A prestigious tech company is seeking a Software Engineer II to join their Safe Ads Experiences (SAE) team. This team is building the next\-generation data collection platform SPECTRA, which will shape the future of how human\-labeled data is collected and used in the company's systems. The role offers the opportunity to impact responsible advertising, user data privacy, and public trust through data\-driven insights.

**Responsibilities**

* Drive technical implementation and testing of complex data pipeline features within the SPECTRA platform, ensuring robust end\-to\-end functionality and meeting project release timelines
* Design and develop data processing pipelines using SQL and Python to handle large\-scale data collection, transformation, and quality monitoring workflows
* Build and maintain dashboards and visualization tools to provide visibility into data quality, rater performance, and platform metrics for stakeholders across multiple teams
* Create comprehensive end\-to\-e</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 PhD Resident - AI for Lab Automation (Early Stage Biology Project) - X Development</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=982b329352397df7</link>
        <description>InternshipMountain View, CA



**About us:**



X is Alphabet’s moonshot factory. We are a diverse group of inventors and entrepreneurs who build and launch technologies that aim to improve the lives of millions, even billions, of people. Our goal: 10x impact on the world’s most intractable problems, not just 10% improvement. We approach projects that have the aspiration and riskiness of research with the speed and ambition of a startup.


**About the team:**



The Bio Design Kitchen (BioDK) is X’s state\-of\-the\-art biology and chemistry lab that empowers Xers to tackle unique challenges to launch moonshots in biology and chemistry. Our team of resident scientists and engineers are experts at turning concepts into reality, whether it's rapid prototyping, in\-house development, or brainstorming novel solutions.


**About the role:**



We are looking for an exceptional PhD student who has experience in applied ML and a high\-level proficiency in programming to join our team for 6 mon</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer, Cash Line - Upstart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e2c28785b5b8428</link>
        <description>**About Upstart**



At Upstart, we're united by a mission that matters: to radically reduce the cost and complexity of borrowing for all Americans. Every day, we bring creativity, experimentation, and advanced AI to reshape access to credit, helping millions move forward financially with clarity and confidence.



As the leading AI lending marketplace, we partner with banks and credit unions to expand access to affordable credit through technology that's both radically intelligent and deeply human. Our platform runs over one million predictions per borrower using more than 1,800 signals, powering smarter, fairer decisions for millions of customers. But the numbers only hint at the impact. Every idea, every voice, and every contribution moves us closer to a world where credit never stands between people and their financial progress.



We're proudly digital\-first, giving most Upstarters the flexibility to do their best work from wherever they thrive, alongside teammates across 80\+ ci</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager III, Storage Systems and NPI, Cloud AI - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d0038faa55cb6382</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in program management.
* Experience in storage systems or infrastructure systems.
* Experience with new product introduction (NPI) across software or hardware products (architecture, development, launch).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of experience managing cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.
* Experience with NPI development, firmware, driving software quality and process transformation.
* Experience in software engineering as a developer or development manager, with an understanding of software development processes, tools, software test/qualification, release methodologies.
* Excellent investigative, problem\-solving, negotiation and organizational skills.
* Excellent program management skills, with the ability to successfully drive and land software programs.
* Excellent verbal and written communication and presentation sk</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Search, Speech Translation - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0011dcb0b2641eec</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in Python, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience developing and evaluating Machine Translation (MT) models and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience developing, deploying, and maintaining Machine Learning (ML) infrastructure.
* 1 year of experience conducting quantitative and qualitative evaluations of systems.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience with full stack development, including back\-end (Kotlin / C\+\+) and front\-end Android UI toolkits.
* Experience with speech recognition, translation or test to speech processing.
* Experience implementing and optimizing automated evaluation pipelines for data and models.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**Ab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Engineer, Machine Learning Accelerators - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c755f557a39c7937</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in manufacturing.
* Experience in PCBA (Printed Circuit Board Assembly) and related system assembly.
* Experience in design for manufacturability and serviceability.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Electrical, Mechanical, Industrial, Materials, or a related engineering field.
* 10 years of experience at a company developing supply chains in manufacturing and testing.
* Experience working with Original Device Manufacturers (ODMs), contract manufacturers and component suppliers for data center server accelerator products (GPU, FPGA or ASIC).
* Experience working with contract manufacturers and suppliers to drive root cause analysis, corrective actions and continuous process improvements.
* Experience of bring\-up or bench testing hardware in a lab environment.
* Knowledge of SQL queries and scripting in Python or Bash.

**Abou</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, GenAI, Device Portal - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7ce02c09d41216a1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products, and 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 5 years of experience leading ML design and optimizing ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 2 years of experience with GenAI techniques (e.g., LLMs, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) or with GenAI\-related concepts (e.g., language modeling, computer vision).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technical direction.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex organization involving cross\-functional, or cross\-busi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a5aabc4ae0be9156</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Intuit is looking for innovative and hands\-on Senior AI Scientist to join the Intuit AI team.


This team embeds artificial intelligence and machine learning into our product portfolio and business


to create smarter products, improve anti\-fraud and security and enhance customer care. Come join our


collaborative and creative group of AI scientists and machine learning engineers and build models that


directly affect hundreds of thousands of our customers. In this role you will be building and deploying


machine learning models using both analytical algorithms and deep learning approaches.

 **Responsibilities**

  

Perform hands\-on data analysis and modeling with huge data sets


Apply data mining, NLP , and machine learning (both supervised and unsupervised) to improve


relevance and personalization algorithms


Work side\-by\-side with product managers, software engineers, and designers in designing


experiments and minimum viable products


Dis</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ASIC Verification Engineer - Hewlett Packard Enterprise | HPE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c79443728843b2e</link>
        <description>ASIC Verification Engineer  



This role has been designed as ‘Hybrid’ with an expectation that you will work on average 2 days per week from an HPE office.**Who We Are:**


Hewlett Packard Enterprise is the global edge\-to\-cloud company advancing the way people live and work. We help companies connect, protect, analyze, and act on their data and applications wherever they live, from edge to cloud, so they can turn insights into outcomes at the speed required to thrive in today’s complex world. Our culture thrives on finding new and better ways to accelerate what’s next. We know varied backgrounds are valued and succeed here. We have the flexibility to manage our work and personal needs. We make bold moves, together, and are a force for good. If you are looking to stretch and grow your career our culture will embrace you. Open up opportunities with HPE.

**Job Description:**

  



  

HPE Networking is a leading provider of advanced routers and switches for the internet. We keep the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer, Trainium Manufacturing, Quality &amp; Reliability - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41c11ba9ebf8e96d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability (MQR) Team is part of AWS Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider. As a Senior Reliability Engineer you will engage with an experienced cross\-disciplinary staff to conceive and design infrastructure technologies. You will work closely with an internal inter\-disciplinary team, and outside partners to drive key aspects of product definition, execution and test in manufacturing. A successful candidate will be responsive, flexible and able to succeed within an open collaborative peer environment. You will:  

  

* Be responsible for the test validation of future technologies.
* Drive manufacturing process improvements to address reliability issues and concerns.
* You will have a fundamental understanding of Reliability statistics/Reliability tests and/or solid understanding of computer systems to influence des</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=16557617cc705e31</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Expedia Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f6610ed807a1c6f6</link>
        <description>Expedia Group brands power global travel for everyone, everywhere. We design cutting\-edge tech to make travel smoother and more memorable, and we create groundbreaking solutions for our partners. Our diverse, vibrant, and welcoming community is essential in driving our success.

**Why Join Us?**


To shape the future of travel, people must come first. Guided by our Values and Leadership Agreements, we foster an open culture where everyone belongs, differences are celebrated and know that when one of us wins, we all win.


We provide a full benefits package, including exciting travel perks, generous time\-off, parental leave, a flexible work model (with some pretty cool offices), and career development resources, all to fuel our employees' passion for travel and ensure a rewarding career journey. We’re building a more open world. Join us.

**Software Development Engineer III**

**Introduction to Team:**

Expedia Platform Technology teams partner with our Product teams to create innovat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist Lead - TikTok Integrity and Safety (San Jose) - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92430fc213a8ff8</link>
        <description>Data analysis
  
  

Data Scientist Lead \- TikTok Integrity and Safety (San Jose)
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A128353B
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About the Team
  
Join our team and leverage the power of data science to directly safeguard content, users, and privacy on TikTok. You will provide critical data\-driven insights for platform responsibility and safety initiatives, including video content safety, live content safety, account security, privacy compliance, and moderation platforms, ultimately enhancing the safety experience for millions of users worldwide.
  
  

Responsibilities \- What You'II Do
  
1\. Design, build, and maintain core metrics systems related to platform content safety and risk, including but not limited to content violation, user report, and account risk identification. Develop comprehensive monitoring and anomaly detection systems to quickly identify and analyze security inc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5d961e58f0e90588</link>
        <description>Category Data


Location Mountain View, California


Job ID 16372


  
Company Overview


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


Job Overview


We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team. This role is focused on driving Intuit Mid Market penetration through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Data Scientist &amp; AI/ML, Marketing - Proofpoint</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e07073af5d3d0b74</link>
        <description>About Us:  

Proofpoint is a global leader in human\- and agent\-centric cybersecurity. We protect how people, data, and AI agents connect across email, cloud, and collaboration tools. Over 80 of the Fortune 100, 10,000 large enterprises, and millions of smaller organizations trust Proofpoint to stop threats, prevent data loss, and build resilience across their people and AI workflows. Our mission is simple: safeguard the digital world and empower people to work securely and confidently. Join us in our pursuit to defend data and protect people.
How We Work:
At Proofpoint you’ll be part of a global team that breaks barriers to redefine cybersecurity guided by our BRAVE core values:
Bold in how we dream and innovate
Responsive to feedback, challenges and opportunities
Accountable for results and best in class outcomes
Visionary in future focused problem\-solving
Exceptional in execution and impact
The Role
We are seeking a highly analytical and commercially minded Senior Manager of Marke</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Hinge Health</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=04cf425808556719</link>
        <description>Overview:
**About the Role**


Hinge Health is on a mission to create a new healthcare system built around the user. To achieve this, we must demonstrate that our digital clinic not only improves clinical outcomes but also drives significant financial savings for our clients—primarily large employers and health plans.


As a Senior Data Scientist in the ROI Identification \&amp; Measurement Pod, you will join a high\-impact, cross\-functional team of Product, Data Science, Health Economics, and Engineering. Your work sits at the heart of our commercial value proposition: using massive healthcare claims datasets to prove and predict the economic impact of our programs.


In this role, you will solve complex technical challenges such as building propensity score matching models to establish causal impact and developing predictive models that identify high\-risk members for targeted clinical interventions. You will be a key architect of our automated claims analysis engine, leveraging a moder</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied AI Engineer (Mid-Level to Staff+) - Squint</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2ce72bcf8af47df</link>
        <description>**About Us**
------------


At Squint, we're building technology that matters. While many tech companies focus on digital\-first industries, we've set our sights on empowering the 80% of the global workforce that keeps our world running: frontline manufacturing operators. From soda cans to tires, toothpaste to chocolate bars, chips to napkin holders, these are the people who build the things you touch and see every single day. Our platform transforms manufacturing operations by putting AI and AR capabilities directly at workers' fingertips, creating what we call "agentic manufacturing" – where every team member has the power to make informed decisions in real\-time using practical, applied artificial intelligence tools.

**Proven Impact with Industry Leaders**
---------------------------------------


Our technology serves Fortune 500 leaders across Automotive, Consumer Packaged Goods, and Life Sciences industries. These companies trust Squint to capture and activate their essential op</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Decision Analytics Associate Consultant (Customer Models &amp; Motivation) - ZS Associates</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7300e9433f82a0fd</link>
        <description>:
**ZS** is a place where passion changes lives. As a management consulting and technology firm focused on improving life and how we live it, we transform ideas into impact by **bringing together data, science, technology** and **human ingenuity** to deliver better outcomes for all. Here you’ll work side\-by\-side with a powerful collective of thinkers and experts shaping life\-changing solutions for patients, caregivers and consumers, worldwide. ZSers drive impact by bringing a **client\-first mentality** to each and every engagement. We partner collaboratively with our clients to develop custom solutions and technology products that create value and deliver company results across critical areas of their business. Bring your curiosity for learning, bold ideas, courage and passion to drive life\-changing impact to ZS.  


 :
**Insights \&amp; Analytics**

**ZS's** **Insights \&amp; Analytics** **group** partners with clients to design and deliver solutions to help them tackle a broad range of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytics - Ads Product - Discord</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2cf53595ac1b9091</link>
        <description>Discord is used by over 200 million people every month for many different reasons, but there’s one thing that nearly everyone does on our platform: play video games. Over 90% of our users play games, spending a combined 1\.5 billion hours playing thousands of unique titles on Discord each month. Discord plays a uniquely important role in the future of gaming. We are focused on making it easier and more fun for people to talk and hang out before, during, and after playing games.At Discord, we're building something special \- a place where hundreds of millions of people connect, play, and belong. Our ads business is entering an exciting growth phase, and we're looking for a Senior Data Scientist who's passionate about building advertising technology that respects our users while delivering real value to brands. We are establishing the groundwork for advanced advertising capabilities that uphold user privacy and simultaneously achieve outstanding results for advertisers \- now that’s true</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist II - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b28f976f3803100f</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
Overall Purpose  

  

This position serves as a data science team member in the Model Validation and Monitoring Team delivering leading edge machine learning models to our clients. This includes providing effective challenges to model development, conduct model monitoring and </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Data Scientist - Recommendations - Scribd</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2eb5a157e509e5b</link>
        <description>**About The Company:**
----------------------


At Scribd Inc. (pronounced “scribbed”), our mission is to spark human curiosity. Join our team as we create a world of stories and knowledge, democratize the exchange of ideas and information, and empower collective expertise through our four products: Everand, Scribd, Slideshare, and Fable.


This posting reflects an approved, open position within the organization.


We support a culture where our employees can be real and be bold; where we debate and commit as we embrace plot twists; and where every employee is empowered to take action as we prioritize the customer.


When it comes to workplace structure, we believe in balancing individual flexibility and community connections. It’s through our flexible work benefit, Scribd Flex, that employees – in partnership with their manager – can choose the daily work\-style that best suits their individual needs. A key tenet of Scribd Flex is our prioritization of intentional in\-person moments t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist III - MERCOR</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ea02c074e8a62455</link>
        <description>We are seeking a highly experienced Data Science Contractor to join our team and provide essential support for strategic initiatives across a major social media platform's ecosystem. This position is ideally suited for a data scientist possessing robust analytical capabilities, substantial experience within large\-scale data environments, and a commitment to generating significant impact through data\-driven insights.

**Responsibilities**

* Conduct rigorous analysis of complex datasets to identify trends, patterns, and actionable insights pertinent to the ecosystem (products, partners, platforms, and user interactions).
* Design, implement, and meticulously maintain critical metrics to accurately measure ecosystem health, growth, and engagement.
* Develop and execute structured experiments to rigorously evaluate new features, strategic partnerships, and ecosystem strategies.
* Engage closely with cross\-functional teams (Product, Engineering) to formally define requirements, deliver </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Data Scientist, New College Grad - 2026 - Visa</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=45d3814a2a03d341</link>
        <description>**Company Description**  

Visa is a world leader in digital payments, facilitating more than 215 billion payments transactions between consumers, merchants, financial institutions and government entities across more than 200 countries and territories each year. Our mission is to connect the world through the most innovative, convenient, reliable and secure payments network, enabling individuals, businesses and economies to thrive.


When you join Visa, you join a culture of purpose and belonging – where your growth is priority, your identity is embraced, and the work you do matters. We believe that economies that include everyone everywhere, uplift everyone everywhere. Your work will have a direct impact on billions of people around the world – helping unlock financial access to enable the future of money movement.

**Join Visa: A Network Working for Everyone.**

 **Job Description**  

The Global Data Science team at Visa leverages our rich data \- spanning over 3 billion card accoun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied AI/ML Business Analytics Lead - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41829f0bf21c6a9a</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Mathematics, Statistics, Economics, Computer Science, or a related quantitative field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 6 years of experience in data analysis, statistical modeling, or a similar role.
* Experience in applying machine learning techniques and economic analysis in a business context such as simulations, statistical analysis, and nonlinear regression models.
* Experience in SQL (BigQuery, PostgreSQL, SQL Server, or MySQL).
* Experience in Python or R.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Data Science, Machine Learning, Statistics, Economics, or a related field.
* Experience with data visualization tools such as Tableau, Power BI, or similar.
* Experience in the consumer electronics industry, with a focus on promotional analytics and consumer offer management.
* Experience building and deploying statistical and machine learning models using Python.
* Knowledge of cloud\-based AI plat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Engineer, AI.x - Charles Schwab</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=925b48f9ccab421f</link>
        <description>**Your opportunity**
--------------------

  

At Schwab, your career is more than a job—it's an opportunity to impact the lives of millions. Innovation and creative problem solving thrive here, as we challenge conventional approaches and prioritize collaboration. We value in\-person teamwork, so this role is based on\-site at our San Francisco office.  

As part of Schwab’s AI Strategy \&amp; Transformation team (AI.x), you’ll join the central hub for Artificial Intelligence across the company. AI.x brings together product, engineering, strategy, and risk specialists to set enterprise AI vision, invest in transformative opportunities, and accelerate delivery organization\-wide. Our team builds the scalable core platform for AI and explores next\-generation GenAI initiatives that redefine client experiences.  

We’re seeking a Senior AI Engineer who will design and deliver cutting\-edge GenAI applications, enhancing the client journey and driving tangible business value. You’ll collaborate</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Quickbooks Workforce Solutions - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1a58af106a5dec8b</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


We are seeking a Senior Data Scientist to join our Quickbooks Workforce Solutions Data Science Team. This role is focused on growth across Intuit’s Payroll and Human Capital Management products and services. The team uses advanced analytics and artificial intelligence to deliver exceptional customer experiences and help businesses manage finances and employees more effectively.

  



As a Senior Data Scientist on the Product Data Science team, you will explore data to generate insights that influence the strategic direction of Workforce Solutions. Your work will directly shape product development, customer experience, and go\-to\-market decisions.

 **Responsibilities**

  

* Define KPIs and Success Metrics: Establish key business indicators for projects, ensuring alignment with company objectives and clear measures of success.
* Data Visualization: Translate complex data into clear, accessible dashboards and other visualizations that help stakeholders und</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Scientist - Personalization - Expedia Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d6e2187ca23ecc09</link>
        <description>Expedia Group brands power global travel for everyone, everywhere. We design cutting\-edge tech to make travel smoother and more memorable, and we create groundbreaking solutions for our partners. Our diverse, vibrant, and welcoming community is essential in driving our success.

**Why Join Us?**


To shape the future of travel, people must come first. Guided by our Values and Leadership Agreements, we foster an open culture where everyone belongs, differences are celebrated and know that when one of us wins, we all win.


We provide a full benefits package, including exciting travel perks, generous time\-off, parental leave, a flexible work model (with some pretty cool offices), and career development resources, all to fuel our employees' passion for travel and ensure a rewarding career journey. We’re building a more open world. Join us.


Expedia Product \&amp; Technology builds innovative products, services, and tools to deliver high\-quality experiences for travelers, partners, and our</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products and Brands-Agent - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ccc63935b30031a7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

About the team  

The SPB\-Agent is the central agent that interfaces with advertisers in Ads </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Developer 4 - Redwood City, CA (in-office role) - Oracle</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=701b0e63a9a8e050</link>
        <description>**\*Please note, this is an in\-office role in Oracle's Redwood City, CA office.**

AI/ML Engineer with hands\-on experience to build production\-grade multi\-agent AI applications, Agentic RAG knowledge assistants, and scalable ML pipelines. candidate should have strong applied AI background in distributed reasoning, retrieval\-augmented architectures, and cloud\-native deployment (Kubernetes, Docker, FastAPI), plus data science experience with large\-scale consumer data modeling. good to have experience experience with impact improving reliability, latency, and model quality (e.g., reduced hallucinations, faster inference, higher multi\-hop accuracy)


  
As part of Oracle Applied AI team, you will work on below list of technologies


* LLM \&amp; Agentic Systems: Multi\-agent orchestration, tool use, routing, verification/refinement loops; ReAct/CoT prompting and synthetic data generation; self\-consistency distillation
* RAG / Knowledge Automation: GraphRAG, vector DBs (Qdrant, Chroma)</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:37:41 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
