<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Cloud/Backend - SCP (Hybrid) - CrowdStrike</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9101165c057c709</link>
        <description>As a global leader in cybersecurity, CrowdStrike protects the people, processes and technologies that drive modern organizations. Since 2011, our mission hasn’t changed — we’re here to stop breaches, and we’ve redefined modern security with the world’s most advanced AI\-native platform. We work on large scale distributed systems, processing almost 3 trillion events per day and this traffic is growing daily. Our customers span all industries, and they count on CrowdStrike to keep their businesses running, their communities safe and their lives moving forward. We’re also a mission\-driven company. We cultivate a culture that gives every CrowdStriker both the flexibility and autonomy to own their careers. We’re always looking to add talented CrowdStrikers to the team who have limitless passion, a relentless focus on innovation and a fanatical commitment to our customers, our community and each other. Ready to join a mission that matters? The future of cybersecurity starts with you.
About </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (Scala) - Quantifind</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b2f69574da81c80</link>
        <description>### **Who You Are**



Quantifind is seeking a Software Engineer for our Platform team to help define and deliver data services and machine learning infrastructure. The Platform team owns all the infrastructure that powers the SaaS products we build for our customers. We process terabytes of data each day on our own dedicated Hadoop clusters. We use real\-time data services to enable interactive investigations in our web applications. We use Kubernetes and Docker for our container ecosystem, and we develop standalone services in Scala and Python and use Spark for MapReduce jobs.



You care deeply about your work and its impact on the work your team does. You hold yourself to a high standard when it comes to writing clean, performant, and maintainable code that powers well\-designed microservices and enhances Quantifind's distributed data platform. You work well with cross\-functional teams that include Data Scientists, DevOps Engineers, Front\-end Engineers and Product Managers. You a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Information Technology (IT) Systems Administrator (Systems Application Analyst 3) - HII</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0bb8f79e831189f8</link>
        <description>**Date:** Feb 25, 2026


**Location:** Mountain View, CA, California, United States


**Company:** HII's Mission Technologies division


Requisition Number: 27302



Required Travel: 0 \- 10%



Employment Type: Full Time/Salaried/Exempt



Anticipated Salary Range: $96,278\.00 \- $125,000\.00



Security Clearance: Secret


Level of Experience: Mid

  


**Meet HII’s Mission Technologies Division**  

Our team of more than 7,000 professionals worldwide delivers all\-domain expertise and advanced technologies in service of mission partners across the globe. Mission Technologies is leading the next evolution of national defense – the data evolution \- by accelerating a breadth of national security solutions for government and commercial customers. Our capabilities range from C5ISR, AI and Big Data, cyber operations and synthetic training environments to fleet sustainment, environmental remediation and the largest family of unmanned underwater vehicles in every class. Find the role that’</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II - Embedded Systems - Hewlett Packard Enterprise | HPE</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f7d643ae0057cd3d</link>
        <description>Software Engineer II \- Embedded Systems  



This role has been designed as ‘’Onsite’ with an expectation that you will primarily work from an HPE office.**Who We Are:**


Hewlett Packard Enterprise is the global edge\-to\-cloud company advancing the way people live and work. We help companies connect, protect, analyze, and act on their data and applications wherever they live, from edge to cloud, so they can turn insights into outcomes at the speed required to thrive in today’s complex world. Our culture thrives on finding new and better ways to accelerate what’s next. We know varied backgrounds are valued and succeed here. We have the flexibility to manage our work and personal needs. We make bold moves, together, and are a force for good. If you are looking to stretch and grow your career our culture will embrace you. Open up opportunities with HPE.

**Job Description:**

  



We’re looking for people who are excited about building infrastructure that global businesses rely on \- </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, AI - Okta</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=836f642fc92a044b</link>
        <description>**Get to know Okta**  

  

Okta is The World’s Identity Company. We free everyone to safely use any technology, anywhere, on any device or app. Our flexible and neutral products, Okta Platform and Auth0 Platform, provide secure access, authentication, and automation, placing identity at the core of business security and growth.  

  

At Okta, we celebrate a variety of perspectives and experiences. We are not looking for someone who checks every single box \- we’re looking for lifelong learners and people who can make us better with their unique experiences.  

  

Join our team! We’re building a world where Identity belongs to you.

**The Global AI Engineering Team**
----------------------------------



At Okta, you’ll be part of a **unified global AI engineering team** that spans the US and India. You’ll work on cutting\-edge applied AI projects while shaping the **platform foundations** that make secure, scalable AI possible at enterprise scale. If you’re passionate about building</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Engineer - Automation Anywhere</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=73fc1a9a504ab369</link>
        <description>About Us:
Automation Anywhere is the leader in Agentic Process Automation (APA), transforming how work gets done with AI\-powered automation. Its APA system, built on the industry’s first Process Reasoning Engine (PRE) and specialized AI agents, combines process discovery, RPA, end\-to\-end orchestration, document processing, and analytics—all delivered with enterprise\-grade security and governance. Guided by its vision to fuel the future of work, Automation Anywhere helps organizations worldwide boost productivity, accelerate growth, and unleash human potential.
Our opportunity:
Automation Anywhere, the leader in Agentic Process Automation (APA), is seeking a Staff Machine Learning Engineer to help power the next generation of AI\-driven digital agents transforming enterprise operations.
In this role, you will design, build, and deploy cutting\-edge machine learning systems that operate at real\-world scale—advancing Generative AI, Natural Language Processing, and Computer Vision cap</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Research Scientist, Applied AI, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=50c8d2c7d0406c6c</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Computer Science, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience leading a research agenda.
* 2 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools, or Applied ML (e.g., LLM's, Generative AI, NLP, Recommendations).
* Experience coding in Python, JavaScript, R, Java, or C\+\+.
* One of more scientific publication submission(s) for conferences, journals, or public repositories (such as CVPR, ICCV, NeurIPS, ICML, ICLR, etc.).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 2 years of experience in coding and leading multiple research efforts and influencing research direction.
* 2 years of coding experience in Python, JavaScript, R, Java, or C\+\+.
* Experience developing and deploying AI solutions to solve large\-scale problems.
* Ability to articulate technical concepts and influence technical directions.
* Excellent communication skills.

**About the job**
-----------------


As an organization, Google </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Machine Learning, Shopping Targeting - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c6d972f514e010d1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: information retrieval, reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML Modeling, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience with LLMs and Generative AI modeling (e.g., prompt engineering, reinforcement learning, model fine tuning).
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with informa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, Production Engineering, Google Distributed Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d70d7958016e708d</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related field.
* 15 years of experience in software development for technical infrastructure.
* Experie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, AI/ML Recommendations, Rankings, Predictions, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f3b7778b66baa90</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 7 years of experience leading technical project strategy, ML design, and working with industry\-scale ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience with design and architecture; and testing/launching software products.
* 5 years of experience building and deploying recommendation systems models (retrieval, prediction, ranking, embedding) in production and experience building architecture in different modeling domains.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of industry experience working on Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning (AI/ML) recommendations.
* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 5 years of experience in a technical leadership role le</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Generative AI and LLMs, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a092eeb18e110586</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products, and 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning algorithms and tools (e.g. TensorFlow), artificial intelligence, deep learning, or natural language processing.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience designing and implementing complex context retrieval systems (context scaffolding) for large language models in production.
* Experience leading technical strategy for large\-scale projects and mentoring executive engineers.
* Proficiency in SQL.
* Understanding of vector space models, semantic search, and experience evaluating embedding techniques (e.g., dense versus sparse retrieval, re\-ranking strategies).
* Ability to independently query massive data</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Mechanical Engineering, Instruments Intern - Pleasanton, CA - Calyxo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0295aa9a8490d503</link>
        <description>Calyxo, Inc. is a medical device company headquartered in Pleasanton, California, USA. The company was founded in 2016 to address the profound need for improved kidney stone treatment. Kidney stone disease is a common, painful condition that consumes vast amounts of healthcare resources each year. Our team is led by executives and investors with a proven track record of commercializing paradigm\-shifting devices to meet unmet needs within urology.



Are you ready to change the future of kidney stone treatment? We are seeking high achievers who want to be part of a dynamic team working in a fun, diverse atmosphere.


The Instruments Engineering team is a highly energetic and actively growing team that is responsible for developing and ultimately driving Calyxo's instruments and accessories through to launch. As a Mechanical Engineering Intern on the Instruments team, you will support the design and development of new solutions for both released and next\-generation critical components </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Intern - Pleasanton, CA - Calyxo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b41d53c045908438</link>
        <description>Calyxo, Inc. is a medical device company headquartered in Pleasanton, California, USA. The company was founded in 2016 to address the profound need for improved kidney stone treatment. Kidney stone disease is a common, painful condition that consumes vast amounts of healthcare resources each year. Our team is led by executives and investors with a proven track record of commercializing paradigm\-shifting devices to meet unmet needs within urology.



Are you ready to change the future of kidney stone treatment? We are seeking high achievers who want to be part of a dynamic team working in a fun, diverse atmosphere.


The Software Engineering Internship is aimed at providing hands\-on insight into the day\-to\-day activities of a medical device software department that produces solutions to improve the lives of our patients and support medical professionals who treat their conditions. Our interns will work within the Software Engineering Group and collaborate with Electrical Engineering</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II - Ripple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6988d9d372dc66d3</link>
        <description>At Ripple, we're building a world where value moves like information does today. It's big, it's bold, and we're already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs.



If you're ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.

**The work:**
-------------



In this role, As a Software Engineer II, you will be one of the core engineers within Ripple's central Data Engineering. This team implements the data ingestion and transformation for analytics, machine learning and powering various business functions at Ripple. You are curious about the bottlenecks and failure modes of a system and look for opportuniti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Research Scientist, Perception - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e36e68b8141386cd</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| SAN FRANCISCO, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4389


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Perception team builds the system which learns the spatial\-temporal representation and their semantic meanings of the sur</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>(USA) Senior, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=173d001bc4af220b</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**Position Summary**  

 We are looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join our team and build the Search backend services processing billions of queries for millions of products on Walmart sites and apps worldwide.  

**About Team:**  

 The Search team at Walmart processes billions of queries across millions of products on our global websites and apps. Whether a customer is searching for a specific item or browsing through categories, our platform powers the intelligence behind product discovery. We leverage structured and semi\-structured data at massive scale \- drawing from catalogs, transaction logs, social data, and more. By combining cutting\-edge information retrieval, machine learning, and ranking algorithms, we build low\-latency, high\-availability systems that directly impact customer experience and business metrics. Immigration support is not available for this role.  

  

**</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Signal Integrity Engineer - Amphenol</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2ff821f054a2af27</link>
        <description>**Position: Signal Integrity Engineer**

**Location: Santa Clara, CA**


Amphenol Cable Backplane System group is the market leader for high speed, high bandwidth integrated cable and connector systems for the AI/Machine Learning market not excluding (Mobile Networks, Storage, Servers, Routers, Switches, etc.). Our products help to enable the electronics revolution and remain a key enabler for all the major Tier 1 OEMs globally. Our global headquarters are located in Nashua, NH and we have design, sales and manufacturing locations globally. We are currently seeking a Signal Integrity Engineer with our CBS Team. The position will be located in Santa Clara, CA.

**RESPONSIBILITIES:**

* Contribute to dedicated teams responsible for customer system development and support from concept to production.
* Develop integration and test strategies in support of new product introduction.
* Assist with providing solutions to customers across a wide range of sectors with their high speed data trans</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI/ML Engineer (AI Automation) - Spanidea Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=030013dc9d5218c7</link>
        <description>**No C2C or vendor involvement. No sponsorship provided.**

**Role: Senior AI / ML Engineer (Automation \&amp; Agentic AI)**

**Experience:** 10\+ years  
**Location:** Santa Clara, CA (Hybrid)

**Role Overview**

We are looking for a highly experienced **AI / ML Engineer** with a strong **data engineering and applied AI background** to lead automation initiatives across **code generation and test automation**. This role will work closely with core engineering teams to design, build, and scale **AI\-driven and agentic automation solutions** that improve developer productivity and software quality.

**Key Responsibilities**

* Lead and drive **AI\-powered automation** initiatives for **code generation, refactoring, and test automation**
* Design and implement **Agentic AI systems** using modern LLM frameworks and orchestration tools
* Collaborate with engineering teams to embed AI/ML solutions into existing development and CI/CD workflows
* Build, train, fine\-tune, and evaluate ML and LLM </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Signal Integrity Engineer - Amphenol</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=67d5769687669d5a</link>
        <description>**Location:**

Santa Clara, California
  

**Posted:**

2/25/2026
  

**Location Name:**

Santa Clara
  

**Wage Max:**

214,500\.00
  

**Wage Min:**

80,750\.00
  

**Position Type:**

Full Time  

  

  

Amphenol Communications Solutions (ACS), a division of Amphenol Corporation, is a world leader in interconnect solutions for Communications, Mobile, RF, Optics, and Commercial electronics markets. Amphenol Corporation is one of the world’s largest designers and manufacturers of electrical, electronic and fiber optic connectors and interconnect systems, antennas, sensors and sensor\-based products and coaxial and high\-speed specialty cable. ACS has an expansive global presence in research and development, manufacturing, and sales. We design and manufacture a wide range of innovative connectors as well as cable assemblies for diverse applications including server, storage, data center, mobile, RF, networking, industrial, business equipment, and automotive.


**Position: Signal Integ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI/ML Lead (Agentic AI) - Spanidea Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a98fce0b0b1eaf47</link>
        <description>**No C2C or vendor involvement. No sponsorship provided.**

**Role: Senior AI / ML Engineer (Automation \&amp; Agentic AI)**

**Experience:** 10\+ years  
**Location:** Santa Clara, CA (Hybrid)

**Role Overview**

We are looking for a highly experienced **AI / ML Engineer** with a strong **data engineering and applied AI background** to lead automation initiatives across **code generation and test automation**. This role will work closely with core engineering teams to design, build, and scale **AI\-driven and agentic automation solutions** that improve developer productivity and software quality.

**Key Responsibilities**

* Lead and drive **AI\-powered automation** initiatives for **code generation, refactoring, and test automation**
* Design and implement **Agentic AI systems** using modern LLM frameworks and orchestration tools
* Collaborate with engineering teams to embed AI/ML solutions into existing development and CI/CD workflows
* Build, train, fine\-tune, and evaluate ML and LLM </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager, ML Fleet Planning and Operations - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c04fc8e45e5234ed</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year
  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the follo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager, ML Fleet Planning and Operations - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd0db9793748b750</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year
  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the follo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Computer Vision, Map Geometry - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=beb79b7e6c11b09b</link>
        <description>The application window will be open until at least March 4, 2026\. This opportunity will remain online based on business needs which may be before or after the specified date.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Boulder, CO, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* 1 year of experience with Computer Vision (e.g., image classification and processing, object detection, visual search), video generation, or signal processing.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or a related technical field.
* 2 years of exp</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Rust - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f3c2b991579da048</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Seattle, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, Machine Learning, Information Systems, a similar research\-related field, or equivalent practical experien</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Research Data Scientist, Network and Machines Optimization, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=69aafedde169a79e</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 3 years of work experience with a PhD degree.
* 4 years of experience in data analysis or related fields as a Statistician, Data Scientist, etc.
* Experience with statistical software (e.g., R, Python, MATLAB, pandas) and database languages (e.g., SQL).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in Data Science, Operations Research, Industrial Engineering, Statistics, or related quantitative field.
* 4 years of relevant work experience (e.g., as a data scientist), including experience applying advanced analytics to planning and infrastructure problems.
* Experience working on technical infrastructure for cloud computing with designing and b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Manager I, XR Apps - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b2300ef626946503</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 3 years of experience in product management or a related technical role.
* 1 year of experience taking technical products from conception to launch (e.g., ideation to execution, end\-to\-end, 0 to 1, etc.).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Experience developing completely new apps, features, and interfaces.
* Experience building products with machine\-learning, computer vision, and AI features.
* Experience delivering zero\-to\-one products and technologies (i.e., new technology introduction), and developing consumer electronics hardware products.
* Knowledge of product craft, with the ability to develop seamless and magical experiences in XR.
* Ability to initiate, develop and build support for ideas.
* Passion for human\-centric design and wants to build technology that feels natural, invisible, and deeply integrated into daily life.

**About the job**
-----------------


At Google, we</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, AI Data, Multimodal - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=377205d26437c592</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 5 years of experience testing and launching software products, and 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.
* 5 years of experience with ML design and ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience with full\-stack development across the back end, such as Java, Python, Golang, or C\+\+ codebases, and the front end.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* 8 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 3 years of experience working in an organization involving cross\-functional or cross\-business projects.
* Experience with innovation of technology at scale and passion for development and the use of cross\-platform shared code.
* Understanding of ML</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Program Manager II, Data Center Networking, Cloud Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f647e08357955e22</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Atlanta, GA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience in program management.
* Experience with networking technologies.
* Experience with data center infrastructure (e.g., power, storage, cooling systems, servers, racks, etc.).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 2 years of experience managing cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.
* Experience with data center technologies, network architecture, NPI, and deployment planning.
* Experience with network capacity planning.
* Ability to grow technically and become a subject matter expert.
* Excellent problem\-solving, communication, and influencing skills.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products tha</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, Infrastructure, Core - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=885d3a4b2419705d</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms in either an academic or industry setting.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience building and developing infrastructure, distributed systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage, or hardware architecture.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.
* Experience with large\-scale distributed systems.
* Experience with Deep Learning, Machine Learning.
* Experience with infrastructure, developer platform.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, YouTube Live Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=28c5f9db463cff38</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages (e.g., Python, C, C\+\+, Java, JavaScript).
* 3 years of experience in a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 3 years of experience working in a complex, matrixed organization.
* 3 years of experience with ML classification systems, ranking and recommendation systems or similar.
* Experience in computer vision/NLP/ML/data mining areas.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all areas, including info</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Fullstack Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b9a978c504533869</link>
        <description>**About Hamilton AI**
---------------------


Hamilton AI is creating the operating system for business aviation. Unlike commercial aviation, business aviation lives in the dark ages, think emails, phone and spreadsheets that run most of the operations of operators from 2 aircraft to 1,000 aircraft.


Hamilton is here to change that. We offer a fully vertically integrated platform that runs business operations at our customers. Our AI agents are the first point of contact for quote requests and we run these quote requests from A to Z. Think quoting, flight scheduling and optimization, route planning, aircraft tracking, payment processing, and back\-office invoicing and payroll.

**Team**
--------


Hamilton AI is founded by Wouter Witvoet, who previously founded Secfi.com ($1\.5bn AUM) and went on to take his second business public called DeFi Technologies, listed on the NASDAQ under DEFT with a market cap of $1\.2bn. Other members are ex\-Dropbox, Square, Airlabs, PagerDuty, Playbook,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Manager, Data for Applied AI Models - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0bd3eea7627490f6</link>
        <description>Join us at the forefront of redefining how people interact with their devices. On the Siri team, we’re solving the challenge of building and shipping powerful LLMs that shape the way millions of Apple customers get things done every day. As our Data lead, you will help craft the future of on\-device AI by developing powerful yet compact LLMs that bring personalized, private, and low\-latency experiences to users. This is a high\-impact role for a hands\-on technical leader who thrives at the intersection of cutting\-edge AI development and product delivery.  

  

**Description**  

  

We are seeking a deeply technical manager to lead our Data team. You will be responsible for understanding and drafting requirements, developing annotation tools and workflows, and managing the delivery and quality of data. The Data team is an immediate partner to our applied ML team, jointly responsible for developing and shipping production models at Apple scale. The huge importance of data on product</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Forward Deployed Product Engineer - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc4d79d08da1b73f</link>
        <description>TypeSafe is a frontier model lab. We build reliable and general AI systems to power economically valuable automation. Our mission is to usher in a new era of Transformative Artificial Intelligence (TAI): technology with the power to drive a societal shift on the scale of the agricultural and industrial revolutions.


While others chase benchmarks and academic puzzles, we’ve been quietly rethinking the LLM stack from first principles — building a new kind of general frontier model designed for real\-world reliability, decision\-making, and autonomy in production.


We’re a small, fast\-moving team from OpenAI, Google Brain, and Meta/FAIR, backed by top\-tier investors. Since mid\-2024, we’ve been engineering the foundation for what comes after the current “state\-of\-the\-art” — a model that actually gets things done.

**About the Role**
==================


Our tech stack is primarily Python. We also use TypeScript, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS for frontend, with Kubernetes for orchestrat</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Borglet Infrastructure - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=70c56a7bbc4e571f</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience programming in C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience testing, and launching software products.
* 5 years of experience building and developing large\-scale infrastructure, distributed systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage, or hardware architecture.
* 3 years of experience with software design and architecture.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Engineering, Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience with system software, distributed systems, and complex multi\-component software systems.
* Experience in reliability, efficiency, and scale, as well as in developing and releasing system software products and C/C\+\+ programming.
* Familiarity with the Linux kernel interface and containers.
* Understanding of key concepts of performance analysis and tuning.
* Excellent data analysis and SQL skills.

**Ab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=32291f54ab06a427</link>
        <description>NVIDIA's data centers host ground\-breaking products across high\-performance computing to machine learning applications for autonomous vehicles and healthcare! At the heart of our data centers is the ability to engineer integrated system designs in close coupling to NVIDIA's industry\-leading GPU products. We are seeking a Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer to accelerate next\-generation solutions.
The Global Connectivity Distinguished Engineer is responsible for working with industry partners to align the strategic design, deployment, and optimization of high\-capacity pathways—terrestrial long\-haul and subsea—that interconnect AI Factories. You will act as the bridge between physical fiber infrastructure and global\-scale AI deployments.
What you’ll be doing:* Participate with partners on diverse long\-haul terrestrial routes to ensure network resilience and high\-capacity data flow between regional AI hubs.
* Participate in subsea and terrestrial consortiums to enable capa</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Full-Stack Software Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8fcf7fff04f1f9c3</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has been transforming computer graphics, PC gaming, and accelerated computing for more than 30 years. Today, we're at the forefront of AI innovation powering breakthroughs in research, autonomous vehicles, robotics, and more. The DGX Cloud team builds and operates the AI infrastructure that fuels this progress.
We’re looking for a Senior Full\-Stack Software Engineer to join the AI Hub team within the DGX Cloud AI Infrastructure organization. The AI Hub team accelerates AI research by ensuring NVIDIA’s AI infrastructure is used efficiently, transparently, and at scale. Our primary goal is to build a unified, self\-service “single pane of glass” portal that enables AI researchers to efficiently manage, monitor, and optimize their use of Managed AI research Superclusters.
What You’ll Be Doing:* Lead the architecture and delivery of high\-scale web products across frontend, backend services, and data layers, with clear availability and latency targets (SLOs/SLAs).
* Own multi\-team</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Lead Network Architect - Synopsys</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=93433922ed167ee4</link>
        <description>**We Are:**
At Synopsys, we drive the innovations that shape the way we live and connect. Our technology is central to the Era of Pervasive Intelligence, from self\-driving cars to learning machines. We lead in chip design, verification, and IP integration, empowering the creation of high\-performance silicon chips and software content. Join us to transform the future through continuous technological innovation. **You Are:**
You are a visionary and hands\-on network engineering leader who thrives on architecting robust, scalable, and future\-ready network solutions across both data center and cloud environments. With over a decade of deep technical expertise, you bring an expert\-level understanding of complex protocols and architectures, including BGP, MPLS, Segment Routing, EVPN, and VXLAN, and excel in leveraging Cisco ACI to its fullest potential. You have a proven track record of program\-managing and driving cross\-functional projects, ensuring seamless collaboration between dive</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Manager - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9e12221b08a8af2a</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Enhancing your leadership style, you motivate, develop and inspire others to deliver quality. You are responsible for coaching, leveraging team member’s uniq</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Manager - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8a3dcab0d472d1f4</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Enhancing your leadership style, you motivate, develop and inspire others to deliver quality. You are responsible for coaching, leveraging team member’s uniq</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6aefe58f5368dbe6</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Senior Associate - PwC</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9835877a10c98aee</link>
        <description>At PwC, our people in business application consulting specialise in consulting services for a variety of business applications, helping clients optimise operational efficiency. These individuals analyse client needs, implement software solutions, and provide training and support for seamless integration and utilisation of business applications, enabling clients to achieve their strategic objectives. In Oracle data and analytics at PwC, you will utilise Oracle's suite of tools and technologies to work with data and derive insights from it. You will be responsible for tasks such as data collection, data cleansing, data transformation, data modelling, data visualisation, and data analysis using Oracle tools like Oracle Database, Oracle Analytics Cloud, Oracle Data Integrator, Oracle Data Visualization, and Oracle Machine Learning.  

Focused on relationships, you are building meaningful client connections, and learning how to manage and inspire others. Navigating increasingly complex situ</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>COMPILER ENGINEER - DEBUG INFO, TOOLS - AMD</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94a15b3da6268bde</link>
        <description>Overview:
**WHAT YOU DO AT AMD CHANGES EVERYTHING**
At AMD, our mission is to build great products that accelerate next\-generation computing experiences—from AI and data centers, to PCs, gaming and embedded systems. Grounded in a culture of innovation and collaboration, we believe real progress comes from bold ideas, human ingenuity and a shared passion to create something extraordinary. When you join AMD, you’ll discover the real differentiator is our culture. We push the limits of innovation to solve the world’s most important challenges—striving for execution excellence, while being direct, humble, collaborative, and inclusive of diverse perspectives. Join us as we shape the future of AI and beyond. **Together, we advance your career.**
Responsibilities:
**THE ROLE:**
We are building first\-class compilation technology for HIP, OpenCL, OpenMP, and Python. In addition to HPC applications, our compilers are used in the development of AMD machine learning frameworks and libraries. We </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer AI/ML Ops - BlackLine</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=224560f3c02165ca</link>
        <description>Make Your Mark::

In new product design roles: develops and programs integrated software algorithms to structure, analyze and leverage data in product and systems applications in both structured and unstructured environments. Develops and communicates descriptive, diagnostic, predictive and prescriptive insights/algorithms. In product/systems improvement projects: uses machine language and statistical modeling techniques such as decision trees, logistic regression, Bayesian analysis and others to develop and evaluate algorithms to improve product/system performance, quality, data management and accuracy. In both theoretical development environments and specific product design, implementation and improvement environments, uses current programming language and technologies to translate algorithms and technical specifications into code. Completes programming and implements efficiencies, performs testing and debugging. Completes documentation and procedures for installation and maintenance</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=56d9c60e41101257</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6a5a28e369753401</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - PayPal</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3e2114b4a6b01f47</link>
        <description>**The Company**


PayPal has been revolutionizing commerce globally for more than 25 years. Creating innovative experiences that make moving money, selling, and shopping simple, personalized, and secure, PayPal empowers consumers and businesses in approximately 200 markets to join and thrive in the global economy.


We operate a global, two\-sided network at scale that connects hundreds of millions of merchants and consumers. We help merchants and consumers connect, transact, and complete payments, whether they are online or in person. PayPal is more than a connection to third\-party payment networks. We provide proprietary payment solutions accepted by merchants that enable the completion of payments on our platform on behalf of our customers.


We offer our customers the flexibility to use their accounts to purchase and receive payments for goods and services, as well as the ability to transfer and withdraw funds. We enable consumers to exchange funds more safely with merchants using</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Identity - Block</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=976d1456b7a1a13f</link>
        <description>Block is one company built from many blocks, all united by the same purpose of economic empowerment. The blocks that form our foundational teams — People, Finance, Counsel, Hardware, Information Security, Platform Infrastructure Engineering, and more — provide support and guidance at the corporate level. They work across business groups and around the globe, spanning time zones and disciplines to develop inclusive People policies, forecast finances, give legal counsel, safeguard systems, nurture new initiatives, and more. Every challenge creates possibilities, and we need different perspectives to see them all. Bring yours to Block.


**The Role**



The Identity Lifecycle team at Cash App ensures that our understanding of "who a customer is" stays accurate, compliant, and useful long after day one. In this role, you'll be embedded within the Trust: Identity \&amp; Controls organization and work closely with engineering, machine learning, risk, compliance, tax, and product partners to desi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal AI/ML Engineer - Palo Alto Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=55bf9fa35801743b</link>
        <description>Santa Clara, California, United States Product Engineering Ref ID: JR\-015095  

**Our Mission**


At Palo Alto Networks®, we’re united by a shared mission—to protect our digital way of life. We thrive at the intersection of innovation and impact, solving real\-world problems with cutting\-edge technology and bold thinking. Here, everyone has a voice, and every idea counts. If you’re ready to do the most meaningful work of your career alongside people who are just as passionate as you are, you’re in the right place.

**Who We Are**


In order to be the cybersecurity partner of choice, we must trailblaze the path and shape the future of our industry. This is something our employees work at each day and is defined by our values: Disruption, Collaboration, Execution, Integrity, and Inclusion. We weave AI into the fabric of everything we do and use it to augment the impact every individual can have. If you are passionate about solving real\-world problems and ideating beside the best and t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Group Product Manager, YouTube Shorts Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e5d4af9e36c63acb</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **San Bruno, CA, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience in product management, shipping consumer products or features.
* 10 years of experience working cross\-functionally with engineering, data science, and UX/UI stakeholders.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning (ML) experimentation methodologies or recommendation systems.
* Experience in data analysis and leveraging product metrics to optimize algorithms and define product roadmaps.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* Experience delivering technical presentations to senior leadership and securing buy\-in for ML\-driven product ideas.
* Experience with discovery or adapting existing recommendation technology to a 0\-1 product surface</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Group Product Manager, YouTube Shorts Discovery - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2968647b8043eca9</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **San Bruno, CA, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience in product management, shipping consumer products or features.
* 10 years of experience working cross\-functionally with engineering, data science, and UX/UI stakeholders.
* 5 years of experience with machine learning (ML) experimentation methodologies or recommendation systems.
* Experience in data analysis and leveraging product metrics to optimize algorithms and define product roadmaps.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* Experience delivering technical presentations to senior leadership and securing buy\-in for ML\-driven product ideas.
* Experience with discovery or adapting existing recommendation technology to a 0\-1 product surface</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2ae7e83b4129de9b</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=937ccc2166fc35f0</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Google (AGBG) Mid Market Delivery Architect - Accenture</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=482d8ed4498bc892</link>
        <description>**We Are:**


A leading partner to the world’s major cloud providers, including AWS, Azure, and Google. The formation of Accenture Cloud First, with a $3 billion investment over three years, demonstrates our commitment to deliver greater value to our clients when they need it most and offers huge growth opportunities for you! Our Cloud First group of more than 70,000 cloud professionals delivers a full stack of integrated cloud capabilities across data, edge, integrated infrastructure and applications, deep ecosystem skills, culture of change along with a deep industry expertise to shape, move, build and operate our clients’ businesses in the cloud. To accelerate our customers transformation leveraging cloud, we combine world\-class learning and talent development expertise; deep experience in cloud change management; and cloud\-ready operating models with a commitment to responsible business by design — with security, data privacy, responsible use of artificial intelligence, sustainab</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Summer Intern – Software Engineer, Autonomous Robot (PhD) - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=23951275af4d1a25</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**To help** **facilitate** **administration of relocation benefits if you are selected, please apply using the permanent address you would move from.**

**Work Arrangement:**  

Hybrid: This internship is categorized as hybrid . The selected intern is expected to report to the office up to three times per week or as determined by the team.  



**Locations:**

Mountain View, California


Sunnyvale, California


We are seeking highly motivated interns to research, explore, and evaluate cutting\-edge AI\-driven approaches for robot localization/map construction, perception , motion planning, scenario simulation, and data engineering. The role will involve hands\-on experimentation, algorithm development, and integration of multi\-modal sensor data to advance autonomous robotic systems.  



**About the Team:**

The Robotics Software team is developing the next generation of autonomous robotic systems, focusing on autonomous mobile robots (AMRs) and intelligent roboti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Manager, Logging - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ae5754e425f1ab81</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**Hybrid** **:** This role is categorized as hybrid . The successful candidate is expected to report to GMs office in Mountain View, CA or the office in Warren, MI as needed .  



  

**Why join us?**  

General Motors pioneers the innovations that move and connect people to what matters. We see a world with zero crashes, zero emissions, and zero congestion. As we move toward this vision, software plays an integral role as it becomes more prominent in our vehicles.  



At General Motors, our product teams are redefining mobility. Through a human\-centered design process, we create vehicles and experiences that are designed not just to be seen, but to be felt. We’re turning today’s impossible into tomorrow’s standard —from breakthrough hardware and battery systems to intuitive design, intelligent software, and next\-generation safety and entertainment features.


Every day, our products move millions of people as we aim to make driving safer, smarter, and more con</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer - Vehicle AI - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=740454acacc50185</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**The Role**
============

As a Principal Software Engineer in the Vehicle AI division, you will be the technical cornerstone of our smart cabin initiatives. You will architect, design, and deploy low\-latency, high\-performance AI software that runs directly on edge hardware within the vehicle.


You won't just be writing code; you will define the technical roadmap, mentor senior engineers, and collaborate across hardware, UI/UX, and vehicle software teams to bring intelligent features—like natural language voice assistants, driver monitoring systems (DMS), and predictive cabin personalization—to life.


**Key Responsibilities**
========================

* **Architectural Leadership:** Design scalable, secure, and real\-time software architectures for AI\-driven features running on automotive\-grade compute platforms (e.g., Qualcomm Snapdragon Digital Chassis, NVIDIA DRIVE).
* **Edge AI Optimization:** Lead the deployment and optimization of machine learning model</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>CAD Engineer - New College Grad 2026 - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9a62b1f91d5b9e0</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 fueled the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI \- the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to solve, that only we can seek, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human creativity and intelligence. Make the choice to join us today.
Join NVIDIA’s Advanced Technology Group—a fast paced team that crafts the next generation of process technologies for AI, HPC, automotive, and graphics. In this role, you will help contribute to flows and manage systems dealing with a range of data from packaging to VLSI library views to help streamline and improve productivity.
What you'll be doing:* Collaborate across internal library, packaging and design teams to implement flows t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - VSCO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fcb8a030781599dc</link>
        <description>**About VSCO**



VSCO (pronounced vis–co) is a platform that equips photographers with the tools, community, and exposure they need to expand creatively and professionally. VSCO maintains a rich and authentic creative environment that serves photographers at all levels – preserving a home for creative opportunity, inspiration, and connection. Our mission is to champion photographers so they can make it. We empower photographers to connect with other creatives and businesses with our suite of creative tools that spans from mobile to desktop and across our global community.



We are looking for people who are driven and demonstrate initiative in taking our company mission to the next level. Employees here have the opportunity to make a big impact, and believe that when we build together, we achieve stronger outcomes than we could alone.



Our values are critical pillars to our team culture and shape the way we hire. Read more about what you can expect when working at VSCO on our Caree</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Internship - On Product Performance Engineer - ASML</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=014e269116e47791</link>
        <description>**Introduction**


ASML US, including its affiliates and subsidiaries, bring together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop lithography machines that are key to producing faster, cheaper, more energy\-efficient microchips. We design, develop, integrate, market and service these advanced machines, which enable our customers \- the world’s leading chipmakers \- to reduce the size and increase the functionality of their microchips, which in turn leads to smaller, more powerful consumer electronics. Our headquarters are in Veldhoven, Netherlands and we have 18 office locations around the United States including main offices in Chandler, Arizona, San Jose and San Diego, California, Wilton, Connecticut, and Hillsboro, Oregon.

**Your Assignment**


This position is within the D\&amp;E Department, which is responsible is for the specification, design, implementation, integration, testing and optimizing of the ASML HMI’s E\-beam inspection and metrology products. ASML\-HMI H</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Site Reliability Engineer (SRE) - infinite choice</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=05beb20a88b8d487</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
------------------


We're seeking an exceptional Principal Site Reliability Engineer to architect, design, and build our SRE foundation from the ground up at InfiniteChoice. This is a rare greenfield opportunity to establish SRE practices, develop custom tooling, and create the reliability culture that will support our platform serving millions of users and billions in transaction volume.


As our Principal SRE, you'll combine deep technical expertise with strategic vision to build world\-class monitoring, observability, and automation systems. You'll have the autonomy to define our SRE processes, select technologies, and create the framework that ensures our systems are reliable, scalable, and performant.

**Location:** Remote \- US based**What You Will Do**
--------------------

### **SRE Foundation \&amp; Process Development**

* **Build SRE practices from scratch** \- define SLIs, SLOs, error budgets, and reliability metrics
* Establish incident response procedures,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Forward Deployed AI Engineer - turing</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2f067230dc25ca0b</link>
        <description>**About Turing**



Based in San Francisco, California, Turing is the world's leading research accelerator for frontier AI labs and a trusted partner for global enterprises looking to deploy advanced AI systems. Turing accelerates frontier research with high\-quality data, specialized talent, and training pipelines that advance thinking, reasoning, coding, multimodality, and STEM. For enterprises, Turing builds proprietary intelligence systems that integrate AI into mission\-critical workflows, unlock transformative outcomes, and drive lasting competitive advantage.



Recognized by Forbes, The Information, and Fast Company among the world's top innovators, Turing's leadership team includes AI technologists from Meta, Google, Microsoft, Apple, Amazon, McKinsey, Bain, Stanford, Caltech, and MIT. Learn more at www.turing.com

**The Role**



We are looking for an elite engineer who builds like a hacker and communicates like a consultant. You will not just be building models in a notebook</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Creator Ecosystem - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=146772f8fa5737b5</link>
        <description>Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.



At Roblox, we're building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We're on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.



A career at Roblox means you'll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior/Principal Data Scientist, you will be a strategic thought partner to our product and engineering leadership, specifically aligning with the Ecosystem team to help shape the future of the Roblox Creator </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist – AI &amp; Machine Learning Systems (Dublin, CA) - SavvyMoney</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e01821abea23411c</link>
        <description>**Data Scientist – AI \&amp; Machine Learning Systems** (Dublin, CA)

  

\*\*In order to have your application considered, you must complete every question on this application

  

SavvyMoney is a leading San Francisco East Bay fintech company. We provide integrated credit score and personal finance solutions to 1,600 \+ bank and credit union partners nationally. The SavvyMoney solutions integrate with more than 43 digital banking platforms.

 **SavvyMoney was recently recognized by the San Francisco Business Times and the Silicon Valley Journal as one of the "Top 25 Places to Work in the San Francisco Bay Area" and is an Inc. 5000 Fastest Growing Company.**

  

We’re headquartered in Dublin, CA, and offer a flexible hybrid work environment that blends in\-office collaboration with the freedom of remote work.

  

We are seeking a **Data Scientist with strong Machine Learning Engineering capabilities** to lead initiatives in predictive modeling, personalization, and AI\-driven financial </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software AI Engineer - US - Jade Global</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b7fe9dbaa9a91c42</link>
        <description>**Job Title: Software AI Engineer/Architect**

**Location: Santa Clara, CA (onsite preferred but remote candidates can be considered)**

**Experience: 8\- 10 yrs**

**Job Type: Contract/ FTE**

This role requires deep, end\-to\-end understanding of how Large Language Models are built, trained, optimized, deployed, and operated.  



Candidates must demonstrate hands\-on experience beyond consuming hosted LLM APIs, with a strong grasp of the underlying ML theory, system trade\-offs, and production realities of AI/ML solutions.  



**Mandatory Competency Areas (Non\-Negotiable)**

**1\. Foundations of LLMs (How They Actually Work)**

Candidate must demonstrate first\-principles understanding, including:


* Transformer architectures (attention, embeddings, positional encoding)
* Tokenization strategies and their impact on cost \&amp; performance
* Training vs inference behavior
* Loss functions, pre\-training objectives, and alignment techniques (SFT, RLHF)
* Limitations: hallucinations, bi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist Manager, Product, Home - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e4895c78d6141910</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field or equivalent practical experience.
* 13 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), or 10 years of work experience with an advanced degree.
* 5 years of experience working as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 15 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL).
* 6 years of experience working as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

**About the job**
-----------------


Help serve Google's worldwide user base of more than a billion people. </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer, Agent Systems - Salesforce</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=27a11923c9d60175</link>
        <description>*To get the best candidate experience, please consider applying for a maximum of 3 roles within 12 months to ensure you are not duplicating efforts.*

Job Category


Software Engineering
Job Details


**About Salesforce**

Salesforce is the \#1 AI CRM, where humans with agents drive customer success together. Here, ambition meets action. Tech meets trust. And innovation isn’t a buzzword — it’s a way of life. The world of work as we know it is changing and we're looking for Trailblazers who are passionate about bettering business and the world through AI, driving innovation, and keeping Salesforce's core values at the heart of it all.


Ready to level\-up your career at the company leading workforce transformation in the agentic era? You’re in the right place! Agentforce is the future of AI, and you are the future of Salesforce.


We are seeking a Lead AI Engineer, Agent Systems to join the Salesforce AI Research Incubation Team.
  

In this role, you will design and build production\-g</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer, ML Systems - Salesforce</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ded5878ed549bb8b</link>
        <description>*To get the best candidate experience, please consider applying for a maximum of 3 roles within 12 months to ensure you are not duplicating efforts.*

Job Category


Software Engineering
Job Details


**About Salesforce**

Salesforce is the \#1 AI CRM, where humans with agents drive customer success together. Here, ambition meets action. Tech meets trust. And innovation isn’t a buzzword — it’s a way of life. The world of work as we know it is changing and we're looking for Trailblazers who are passionate about bettering business and the world through AI, driving innovation, and keeping Salesforce's core values at the heart of it all.


Ready to level\-up your career at the company leading workforce transformation in the agentic era? You’re in the right place! Agentforce is the future of AI, and you are the future of Salesforce.


We are seeking a Lead AI Engineer, ML Systems to join the Salesforce AI Research Incubation Team.
  

In this role, you will own the engineering systems that </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Analyst, Advanced Analytics - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2291d9ca101a00a7</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------


We’re seeking an intellectually curious, analytical, and detail\-oriented self\-starter to join our team as Senior Analyst. This role is an individual contributor position central to the continued growth, efficiency, and success of the Walmart Connect team. You’ll work alongside Analytics, Sales, and Campaign Management teams and oversee unlocking insights, building analytic solutions and models, and telling the story that helps move media decisions forward. The ideal candidate will have a strong background in analytics with a deep understanding of the retail/media industry.**What you'll do...**
---------------------


* Collaborate with the Walmart Connect cross\-functional teams for the development, execution and delivery of short and long\-term analytic projects that influence media investment strategies and business growth opportunities
* Ensure delivery of assigned insights analyses with end\-to\-end ownership, clear communication,</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director, Data Standards &amp; Statistical Programming - IDEAYA Biosciences</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fb054c59fd68d0a6</link>
        <description>**Non\-Solicitation Policy and Notice to Agencies and Recruiters:**
===================================================================

**IDEAYA's Non\-Solicitation Policy strictly prohibits agencies and recruiters from any contact and communication with IDEAYA employees, managers, and leaders to submit unsolicited candidate resumes and/or to solicit business partnerships** . Submission of unsolicited candidate resumes by agencies or recruiters with or without a contract in place with IDEAYA Biosciences Inc. will not create any implied obligation. Failure to comply with this policy will result in disqualification from current and future business opportunities with IDEAYA Biosciences. All recruiting and talent agency decisions are strictly managed by the internal IDEAYA Human Resources function. All communication by external agencies and recruiters must be directed to humanresources@ideayabio.com. We ask that you only email your interest once.


Job Summary


About IDEAYA Biosciences:
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Data Scientist, Pixel - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c149e0ea0d9973c</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Chicago, IL, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 5 years of experience with analysis applications (e.g., extracting insights, performing statistical analysis, or solving business problems), and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL) or 2 years of experience with a Master's degree.
* Experience analyzing device telemetry to triage issues; distinguishing between software regressions and hardware limitations (i.e., power, performance, connectivity, or stability domains).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* Experience analyzing time\-series data or telemetry from hardware devices.
* Experie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist Manager, Product, Health - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d9808ed843f289f0</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 13 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL) (or 10 years of experience with a Master's degree).
* 5 years of experience as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 15 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, performing statistical analysis, and coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL).
* 6 years of experience as a people manager within a technical leadership role.

**About the job**
-----------------


Help serve Google's worldwide user base of more than a billion people. Data Scientists provide quantitative support, market und</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, YouTube Shopping and Horizontal - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=981fe57c11e663e9</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 8 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 6 years of experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 8 years of experience with a PhD degree.
* Experience with classifiers.

**About the job**
-----------------


At YouTube, we believe that everyone deserves to have a voice, and that the world is a better place when we listen, share, and build community through our stories. We work together to give everyone the power to share their story, explore what they love, and connect with one another in the process. Working at the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=301105ee76fbeeda</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Data Science team as a Staff Data Scientist. The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most important customer and business challenges.
We are seeking a Staff Data Scientist to deliver impactful models and insights, and drive measurable outcomes for the Workforce Solutions segment within QuickBooks. **Responsibilities**

* Drive Business Strategy through Data \- Translate business problems into analytical frameworks. Provides guidance and support leadership on how best to harness available data in support of critical business needs and goals
* Build \&amp; Operationalize Advanced Models \- Develop and deploy machine learning models and statistical frameworks to forecast growth, uncover pattern</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=84dfcf6f124a3c30</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team. This role is focused on driving Intuit Mid Market penetration through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refine innovative growth strategies. Your expertise—especially in causal inference and advanced analytics—will be instrumental in surfacing critical insights and translating them into actionable hypotheses that fuel sustained customer and revenue growth.

 **Responsibilities**

* Set Technical Vision and Strategy:
	+ Contribute to and help refine a data science roadmap aimed at driving product funnel optimization and scalable growth initiatives.
	+ Apply rig</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Early Stage Supply Chain Project - X Development</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=04f88456ad2297c4</link>
        <description>Software EngineeringMountain View, CA (HQ)



**About the Company:**



X is Alphabet’s moonshot factory. We are a diverse group of inventors and entrepreneurs who build and launch technologies that aim to improve the lives of millions, even billions, of people. Our goal: 10x impact on the world’s most intractable problems, not just 10% improvement. We approach projects that have the aspiration and riskiness of research with the speed and ambition of a startup.





**About the Team:**



We’re X’s moonshot for the global supply chain, applying AI to reduce waste, fragility, and inefficiency. We’re an agile team of experienced AI researchers, software engineers, and entrepreneurs working with visionary partners and customers around the world to make sure everyone has sustainable and reliable access to the food, medicine, clothing, and other goods and services they need.



We’re looking for people who are passionate about revolutionizing the global supply chain to join us at this criti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-25</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist Lead - TikTok Integrity and Safety (San Jose) - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92430fc213a8ff8</link>
        <description>Data analysis
  
  

Data Scientist Lead \- TikTok Integrity and Safety (San Jose)
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A128353B
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About the Team
  
Join our team and leverage the power of data science to directly safeguard content, users, and privacy on TikTok. You will provide critical data\-driven insights for platform responsibility and safety initiatives, including video content safety, live content safety, account security, privacy compliance, and moderation platforms, ultimately enhancing the safety experience for millions of users worldwide.
  
  

Responsibilities \- What You'II Do
  
1\. Design, build, and maintain core metrics systems related to platform content safety and risk, including but not limited to content violation, user report, and account risk identification. Develop comprehensive monitoring and anomaly detection systems to quickly identify and analyze security inc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5d961e58f0e90588</link>
        <description>Category Data


Location Mountain View, California


Job ID 16372


  
Company Overview


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


Job Overview


We are seeking an experienced Staff Data Scientist to join our Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team. This role is focused on driving Intuit Mid Market penetration through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. This is a high\-impact role where your work will directly influence product, marketing, and business model strategies. As a Staff Data Scientist, you will operate as a senior individual contributor, partnering closely with peers and leaders to identify, validate, and refi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Scientist - Personalization - Expedia Group</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d6e2187ca23ecc09</link>
        <description>Expedia Group brands power global travel for everyone, everywhere. We design cutting\-edge tech to make travel smoother and more memorable, and we create groundbreaking solutions for our partners. Our diverse, vibrant, and welcoming community is essential in driving our success.

**Why Join Us?**


To shape the future of travel, people must come first. Guided by our Values and Leadership Agreements, we foster an open culture where everyone belongs, differences are celebrated and know that when one of us wins, we all win.


We provide a full benefits package, including exciting travel perks, generous time\-off, parental leave, a flexible work model (with some pretty cool offices), and career development resources, all to fuel our employees' passion for travel and ensure a rewarding career journey. We’re building a more open world. Join us.


Expedia Product \&amp; Technology builds innovative products, services, and tools to deliver high\-quality experiences for travelers, partners, and our</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 01:06:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
