<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>Scraped jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Engineer, Global E-commerce - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d5da820e8618ee64</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Research Engineer, Global E\-commerce
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A177957
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

The e\-commerce industry has seen tremendous growth in recent years and has become a hotly contested space amongst leading internet companies. With millions of loyal users globally, we believe TikTok is an ideal platform to deliver a brand new and better e\-commerce experience to our users.
  
  

Our AI Innovation team is dedicated to building next\-generation e\-commerce experiences powered by AIGC and agentic shopping systems. We explore how AI\-generated content and intelligent agents can meaningfully enhance user experiences and reshape the way people discover, evaluate, and purchase products.
  
  

**Responsibilities:**  

* Develop and optimize AIGC video generation models, with a focus on multimodal post\-training for e\-commerce short\-video scenarios.
* Design and implement p</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Infrastructure Engineer – Distributed AI Systems - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e7a1b91b42fe800</link>
        <description>Job Description

We are seeking a highly experienced infrastructure engineer (**phD Only**) to design and maintain large\-scale distributed systems that support machine learning workloads, high\-throughput data pipelines, and real\-time model serving.

This role involves building robust backend services, optimizing GPU resource orchestration, and implementing advanced system monitoring to ensure low\-latency and highly reliable AI infrastructure.

The ideal candidate is comfortable working at the intersection of **distributed systems, ML infrastructure, and performance engineering**, and has strong experience with large\-scale production environments.

Responsibilities

* Design and implement high\-performance backend services supporting AI model training and inference pipelines
* Develop distributed systems capable of handling multi\-petabyte datasets and high\-throughput data processing
* Optimize GPU cluster scheduling, memory utilization, and workload orchestration
* Build internal</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - AI Machine Learning - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=90785d4b0ecee872</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position title: SAP iXp Intern \- AI Machine Learning


Location: Palo Alto, CA (in\-person)


Expected start date: June 2026


Contract Duration: 6 months (extendable)


Workin</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - LLM - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e88d7644687e863d</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, new ideas have a way of becoming extraordinary products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there's no telling what you could accomplish. The people here at Apple don’t just create products \- they create the kind of wonder that’s revolutionized entire industries. It’s the diversity of those people and their ideas that inspires the innovation that runs through everything we do, from amazing technology to industry\-leading environmental efforts.  

  

Join Apple, and help us leave the world better than we found it.  

  

**Description**  

  

We are seeking a highly capable and dynamic Machine Learning Engineer to work cross\-functional in building out a GenAI system in support of Beats and Apple Audio products. The ideal candidate thrives in ambiguity, is exceptionally organized, relentlessly detail\-oriented, and an exceptional communicator at all levels of the organization.  

  

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Staff ML Engineer, Apple Cloud AI Platform - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=95e091c5b2ce2077</link>
        <description>Apple Cloud AI Platform powers the machine learning, AI, and data systems that enable intelligent experiences across Apple consumer products. We are looking for a Software Engineer who is excited to work directly with Apple product teams and translate real\-world AI needs into production\-ready solutions. You will operate at the intersection of full\-stack engineering, data and ML platforms, backend systems and applied AI, using customer requirements to build end\-to\-end solutions and workflows as part of our platform offerings. This role is ideal for engineers who are highly collaborative, proactive, adaptable, and capable of turning ambiguous customer requests into working AI\-powered solutions at scale.  

  

**Description**  

  

In this role you will partner directly with internal customers to understand their use cases, evaluate technical requirements, and build AI\-driven systems and solutions that leverage Apple Cloud AI Platform capabilities. You will work across the stack,</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Applied Sensing &amp; Health - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2db726006e6e44d7</link>
        <description>Are you a seasoned engineer passionate about transforming cutting\-edge ML researchinto production systems that improve lives? The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team is revolutionizing health and fitness technology, empowering millions to live healthier, more active lives. We develop sophisticated machine learning algorithms and sensor fusion systems that track human motion, turning raw data into meaningful, actionable insights for Apple users worldwide.  

  

Join a team of world\-class experts dedicated to applied ML in human movement and health. Here, you'll bridge the gap between research and production\-translating novel ML approaches into robust, high\-performance systems that delight and inspire millions of Apple customers every day. This is a unique opportunity to blend ML expertise withsystems engineering in service of a mission that truly matters.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team delivers critical Health and Fitness features for Apple Watch, iPhon</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Battery - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=14fcb3a9e5027ef1</link>
        <description>Do you have a passion for invention and self\-challenge? Do you thrive on pushing the  

  

limits of what’s considered feasible? As part of our Battery Engineering group, you’ll  

  

help craft creative battery solutions that deliver more energy in smaller spaces than  

  

ever before! We work across subject areas to transform improved hardware elements  

  

into a single, integrated design. Join us, and you’ll help us innovate new battery  

  

technologies that continually outperform the previous iterations. By collaborating with  

  

other product development groups across Apple, we push the industry boundaries of  

  

what batteries can do and improve the product experience for our customers across the  

  

world! This position works within a multi\-functional team supporting the entire Battery  

  

Department to identify trends, mine data, and help the battery team improve  

  

performance.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Battery Analytics team transforms data</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Embedded Software Manager - CommScope</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a1fd18f839a38be</link>
        <description>In our ‘always on’ world, we believe it’s essential to have a genuine connection with the work you do.

  

RUCKUS Networks, a CommScope BU, specializes in delivering high\-performance networking solutions while focusing on creating purpose\-driven networks that perform exceptionally well in challenging environments. RUCKUS Networks leverages advanced technologies like Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) to enhance network performance and reduce total cost of ownership.

  

The Embedded Software Engineering Manager will lead and mentor a team of engineers in the development of next\-generation WiFi Access Point solutions. This position requires a strong background in embedded systems, wireless and wired networking, and a proven track record of managing and delivering complex software projects. An experienced leader with a strong technical background in embedded systems, 802\.11 wireless networking, and SoC platforms who thrives in a fast\-paced, collaborative enviro</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - AI/ML Platform - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8b919e29e9ec8294</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO AI platform and Infrastructure team is seeking an exceptional Senior ML Platform Engineer to build and scale our machine learning infrastructure with a focus on Large Language Models (LLMs) and AI applications. This role combines deep technical expertise in cloud platforms, container orchestration, and ML operations with strong leadership and mentoring capabilities. You will be responsible for designing, implem</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Researcher - kiddom</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6d7006cf9ed1f5c5</link>
        <description>**About Kiddom**  

Kiddom is a groundbreaking educational platform that promotes student equity and growth by uniting high\-quality instructional materials with dynamic digital learning. Through unparalleled curriculum management functionality, Kiddom empowers schools and districts to take ownership of their curriculum – resulting in learning experiences tailored to meet the unique needs and goals of local communities. Kiddom’s high\-quality curriculum is layered with robust teacher and leader data insights to drive the continuous improvement of instructional decisions, school/district programming, and professional learning.  

Join our mission to revolutionize K\-12 education at the intersection of cutting\-edge AI and impactful learning outcomes. As a **Machine Learning Researcher**, you will play a pivotal role in pushing the boundaries of what’s possible with AI in education. Your work will assist teachers by personalizing their teaching experience and improving student outcomes. </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=77beaf29cf135608</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d58b4d5ca2a71718</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist, Biosensing - Vivalnk, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=edc2b088d4f16363</link>
        <description>**POSITION: Principal Data Scientist, Biosensing**

PURPOSE OF JOB

The Principal Data Scientist will oversee development of novel algorithms and AI/ML methods to bridge densely collected digital measures from wearable sensor devices to multimodal systems. This role will focus on creating edge\- and cloud\-based algorithmic pipelines for biomedical signal processing and translating research findings into practical, production\-ready solutions to empower users of the Vivalink platform.

Projects will involve establishing methodologies for building and implementing machine learning models using multi\-modal data sets, and extracting the features from raw data that correlate to measures of interest. In addition to modeling, development will include software tools and scripts at scale to support data analysis and interpretation.

MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES

The principal data scientist will apply biomedical knowledge and data science to develop new algorithm\-based products and feat</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - AI Machine Learning - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=90785d4b0ecee872</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position title: SAP iXp Intern \- AI Machine Learning


Location: Palo Alto, CA (in\-person)


Expected start date: June 2026


Contract Duration: 6 months (extendable)


Workin</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - LLM - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e88d7644687e863d</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, new ideas have a way of becoming extraordinary products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there's no telling what you could accomplish. The people here at Apple don’t just create products \- they create the kind of wonder that’s revolutionized entire industries. It’s the diversity of those people and their ideas that inspires the innovation that runs through everything we do, from amazing technology to industry\-leading environmental efforts.  

  

Join Apple, and help us leave the world better than we found it.  

  

**Description**  

  

We are seeking a highly capable and dynamic Machine Learning Engineer to work cross\-functional in building out a GenAI system in support of Beats and Apple Audio products. The ideal candidate thrives in ambiguity, is exceptionally organized, relentlessly detail\-oriented, and an exceptional communicator at all levels of the organization.  

  

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Staff ML Engineer, Apple Cloud AI Platform - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=95e091c5b2ce2077</link>
        <description>Apple Cloud AI Platform powers the machine learning, AI, and data systems that enable intelligent experiences across Apple consumer products. We are looking for a Software Engineer who is excited to work directly with Apple product teams and translate real\-world AI needs into production\-ready solutions. You will operate at the intersection of full\-stack engineering, data and ML platforms, backend systems and applied AI, using customer requirements to build end\-to\-end solutions and workflows as part of our platform offerings. This role is ideal for engineers who are highly collaborative, proactive, adaptable, and capable of turning ambiguous customer requests into working AI\-powered solutions at scale.  

  

**Description**  

  

In this role you will partner directly with internal customers to understand their use cases, evaluate technical requirements, and build AI\-driven systems and solutions that leverage Apple Cloud AI Platform capabilities. You will work across the stack,</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Applied Sensing &amp; Health - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2db726006e6e44d7</link>
        <description>Are you a seasoned engineer passionate about transforming cutting\-edge ML researchinto production systems that improve lives? The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team is revolutionizing health and fitness technology, empowering millions to live healthier, more active lives. We develop sophisticated machine learning algorithms and sensor fusion systems that track human motion, turning raw data into meaningful, actionable insights for Apple users worldwide.  

  

Join a team of world\-class experts dedicated to applied ML in human movement and health. Here, you'll bridge the gap between research and production\-translating novel ML approaches into robust, high\-performance systems that delight and inspire millions of Apple customers every day. This is a unique opportunity to blend ML expertise withsystems engineering in service of a mission that truly matters.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team delivers critical Health and Fitness features for Apple Watch, iPhon</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Battery - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=14fcb3a9e5027ef1</link>
        <description>Do you have a passion for invention and self\-challenge? Do you thrive on pushing the  

  

limits of what’s considered feasible? As part of our Battery Engineering group, you’ll  

  

help craft creative battery solutions that deliver more energy in smaller spaces than  

  

ever before! We work across subject areas to transform improved hardware elements  

  

into a single, integrated design. Join us, and you’ll help us innovate new battery  

  

technologies that continually outperform the previous iterations. By collaborating with  

  

other product development groups across Apple, we push the industry boundaries of  

  

what batteries can do and improve the product experience for our customers across the  

  

world! This position works within a multi\-functional team supporting the entire Battery  

  

Department to identify trends, mine data, and help the battery team improve  

  

performance.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Battery Analytics team transforms data</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - AI/ML Platform - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8b919e29e9ec8294</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO AI platform and Infrastructure team is seeking an exceptional Senior ML Platform Engineer to build and scale our machine learning infrastructure with a focus on Large Language Models (LLMs) and AI applications. This role combines deep technical expertise in cloud platforms, container orchestration, and ML operations with strong leadership and mentoring capabilities. You will be responsible for designing, implem</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Funding Data Analyst (0633U) - 84541 - University of California Berkeley</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=39f073e14c11d567</link>
        <description>Research Funding Data Analyst (0633U) \- 84541 About Berkeley
  
  

At the University of California, Berkeley, we are dedicated to fostering a community where everyone feels welcome and can thrive. Our culture of openness, freedom and belonging make it a special place for students, faculty and staff.
  
  

As a world\-leading institution, Berkeley is known for its academic and research excellence, public mission, diverse student body, and commitment to equity and social justice. Since our founding in 1868, we have driven innovation, creating global intellectual, economic and social value.
  
  

We are looking for applicants who reflect California's diversity and want to be part of an inclusive, equity\-focused community that views education as a matter of social justice. Please consider whether your values align with our Guiding Values and Principles , Principles of Community , and Strategic Plan .
  
  

At UC Berkeley, we believe that learning is a fundamental part of working, and</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Consultant - GenAI Full Stack Developer - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=589547b629f51343</link>
        <description>**GenAI Full Stack Developer \- Senior Consultant**  

  

Deloitte's Audit \&amp; Assurance professionals help organizations navigate business risks and opportunities\-across financial, operational, information technology (IT), business, and regulatory areas\-to build resilience and accelerate performance. In this role, you'll design and deliver end\-to\-end Generative AI (GenAI) solutions \- including Retrieval\-Augmented Generation (RAG) and agentic AI \- that are production\-ready, scalable, and aligned to enterprise risk and governance expectations.  

  

Recruiting for this role ends on  

  

**Work you'll do**  

* Lead business and technical requirements elicitation with client stakeholders; own end\-to\-end gap analysis; translate needs into solution architecture, detailed technical specifications, and delivery\-ready backlog artifacts.
* Drive design, build, test, and deployment of full\-stack Generative AI (GenAI) applications (web user interface (UI), backend services, and da</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Consultant - GenAI Full Stack Developer - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=678a91e6ce1e590b</link>
        <description>**GenAI Full Stack Developer \- Senior Consultant**  

  

Deloitte's Audit \&amp; Assurance professionals help organizations navigate business risks and opportunities\-across financial, operational, information technology (IT), business, and regulatory areas\-to build resilience and accelerate performance. In this role, you'll design and deliver end\-to\-end Generative AI (GenAI) solutions \- including Retrieval\-Augmented Generation (RAG) and agentic AI \- that are production\-ready, scalable, and aligned to enterprise risk and governance expectations.  

  

Recruiting for this role ends on  

  

**Work you'll do**  

* Lead business and technical requirements elicitation with client stakeholders; own end\-to\-end gap analysis; translate needs into solution architecture, detailed technical specifications, and delivery\-ready backlog artifacts.
* Drive design, build, test, and deployment of full\-stack Generative AI (GenAI) applications (web user interface (UI), backend services, and da</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=77beaf29cf135608</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d58b4d5ca2a71718</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:08:03 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
