<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Software Engineer - Matching ML Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fa75f948a6490ab7</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching ML Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
* Building a highly scalable ml systems \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Evolving the ML platform for matching \- enabling real\-time inference, model de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II, Matching Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2aafb69e9aa6afc2</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
  

* Building a highly scalable matching platform \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Designing extensible architectures \- creating a modular and flexible pl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Software Engineer - Matching ML Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=89146ec20f6cf6d6</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching ML Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
* Building a highly scalable ml systems \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Evolving the ML platform for matching \- enabling real\-time inference, model de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II, Matching Platform - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7fb43f34545fb472</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

Uber is looking for a Software Engineer to join our Matching Platform team. This team sits at the core of Uber's real\-time marketplace, ensuring that riders and drivers are matched efficiently, fairly, and at scale.
  

  

Matching is one of Uber's most complex and impactful engineering problems, requiring expertise in high\-scale distributed systems, real\-time decision\-making, and machine learning infrastructure. As a Senior Engineer, you'll play a key role in evolving our matching architecture, improving system efficiency, and enabling Uber's next\-generation ML\-powered matching capabilities. This is an opportunity to work on one of Uber's most business\-critical domains with massive global impact.
  

  

Some of the problems you'll be working on include:
  

* Building a highly scalable matching platform \- handling millions of ride requests per second with ultra\-low latency.
* Designing extensible architectures \- creating a modular and flexible pl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Controls Systems Engineer, Machine Learning, Platforms - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=df41500635df1342</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Science, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience designing and implementing controls systems and dynamic modeling.
* 5 years of experience with Machine Learning and construction of algorithms.
* Experience with programming in C, Python, MATLAB, or Shell.
* Experience with software development or prototyping within a business or enterprise setting.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD in Engineering, Science, or a related field.
* Experience with modeling/statistical software such as TensorFlow, Simulink, R, or MATLAB Machine Learning Toolbox.
* Experience with digital signal processing and time\-series analysis. Experience with optimization, Linear Programming, and Convex Optimization.
* Experience with dynamic system analysis, feedback control systems, and optimal control.
* Experience with developing AI/ML prototypes and conducting full\-cycle modeling experiments within</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6949073a57771923</link>
        <description>Category Data


Location Mountain View, California


Job ID 19909


  
Company Overview


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


Job Overview


Intuit is looking for innovative and hands\-on Senior AI Scientist to join the Intuit AI team.


This team embeds artificial intelligence and machine learning into our product portfolio and business


to create smarter products, improve anti\-fraud and security and enhance customer care. Come join our


collaborative and creative group of AI scientists and machine learning engineers and build models that


directly affect hundreds of thousands of our customers. In this role you will be building and deploying
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Reliability Engineer - EV Powertrain Systems - Zoox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94fa6b0d149c33e3</link>
        <description>At Zoox, we have set the goal to provide our customers with the highest level of safety and a best\-in\-class experience while using our fully autonomous vehicles. You will work with a team of world\-class engineers with diverse backgrounds, such as robotics, control, and vehicle engineering, to deliver vehicle performance using advanced virtual tools and methodologies. In taking on the virtual and physical durability development, you will predict where the vehicle is within its lifecycle and define maintenance, monitoring, and optimization strategies. Working in a startup environment gives you the chance to lead technically, influence system design, and make a meaningful impact on the final product.
### **In this role, you will:**

* Establish and refine system\- and component\-level reliability targets for the electric drive unit (EDU), high\-voltage battery (HVB), and HV to LV Power Distribution (DCDC and HV harnesses) in collaboration with Vehicle Systems Engineering and cross\-fun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Engineer - Cargomatic</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e4eebde6b6cf3dae</link>
        <description>Senior Data Architect – Data Engineering



Location: San Francisco, CA  

Reports To: VP of Engineering  

FLSA Status: Exempt  

Employment Type: Full\-Time  

Compensation: $140,000 – $160,000 annually (based on experience)



About Cargomatic



Cargomatic is transforming the local trucking industry with cutting\-edge technology that connects shippers and carriers in real time. Every product that humans build, grow, or sell has spent time on a truck. Local trucking is the lifeblood of every regional economy, yet this $82 billion industry still relies heavily on outdated systems. Cargomatic is bringing transparency, efficiency, and intelligence to local freight through modern technology and data\-driven solutions.



We are solving complex, real\-world logistics problems every day. If you thrive in a fast\-paced environment, enjoy building scalable systems, and want to help shape the future of AI\-powered logistics, we'd love to meet you.



Position Summary



Cargomatic is seeking</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Junior Software Engineer - Mechanize</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2bb70bb6f02595de</link>
        <description>Mechanize builds RL environments that teach AI models to perform real\-world work. Our goal is to enable the full automation of the economy. We sell to the leading AI labs. Learn more at mechanize.work.

Software engineers at Mechanize create RL environments to sell to the leading AI labs. You might be a good fit if you are about to graduate university, or have 0\-2 years of experience as a software engineer and can code in python.

**No prior machine learning or AI experience is required.**

Read about how our interview process works here: **https://www.mechanize.work/how\-our\-interview\-process\-works/**

Job Type: Full\-time

Pay: $300,000\.00 per year

Work Location: In person</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI/ML Engineer-4 - Realign</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=667798be4f135f84</link>
        <description>San Francisco, California 94016 Posted February 24th, 2026
 Looking for more job opportunities? Click here!


  
Job Type: Contract


Job Category: IT


Job Description


**Role: Sr. AI/ML Engineer**

* **Experience** – 10\+ Years
* **Location** \- San Francisco, CA – LOCALS Only

**Required Qualifications**  

* Deep expertise in Machine Learning, Generative AI, LLMs, RAG, and AI orchestration.
* Strong understanding of Azure OpenAI, AWS Bedrock, or similar platforms.
* Experience deploying AI in regulated environments.
* Hands\-on architectural and engineering leadership capabilities.
* Strong communication skills with VP/Senior Director stakeholders.


 Preferred Qualifications  

* 12\+ years in AI/ML, data engineering, or digital transformation.
* Prior experience leading enterprise AI programs.
* Utility domain experience (wildfire, grid, operations).
* Knowledge of Responsible AI frameworks (NIST AI RMF, ISO 42001\).

  

**Roles \&amp; Responsibilities**  

**Role Overview**  

Uti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Vehicle AI - General Motors (GM)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e8f6ef0a04cb5ae</link>
        <description>**Job Description**

**Work Arrangement:**  

This role is categorized as hybrid/Remote. This means the successful candidate is expected to report to Mountain View, CA three times per week at minimum or other frequency dictated by the business or Remote, Washington location.


**The Role**

GM is looking to hire highly skilled and experienced Staff Software Engineers to join our team focused on developing cutting\-edge AI agents. This role involves leading the design, development, and deployment of robust, scalable, and intelligent software agents that drive innovation across our products and services. The ideal candidate will have a deep understanding of AI/ML principles, distributed systems, and a track record of technical leadership.


**What You'll Do**

* Lead the architecture and implementation of next\-generation AI agents, from conceptualization to production deployment.
* Drive technical direction and strategy for the AI agent platform, ensuring scalability, reliability, and p</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e8b8f804f9021a3</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer, Trainium Manufacturing, Quality &amp; Reliability - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=23c00e90341e49c8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability (MQR) Team is part of AWS Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider. As a Senior Reliability Engineer you will engage with an experienced cross\-disciplinary staff to conceive and design infrastructure technologies. You will work closely with an internal inter\-disciplinary team, and outside partners to drive key aspects of product definition, execution and test in manufacturing. A successful candidate will be responsive, flexible and able to succeed within an open collaborative peer environment. You will:  

  

* Be responsible for the test validation of future technologies.
* Drive manufacturing process improvements to address reliability issues and concerns.
* You will have a fundamental understanding of Reliability statistics/Reliability tests and/or solid understanding of computer systems to influence des</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, DevOps - Moveworks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9aa0a68ebe3a9f9e</link>
        <description>DevOps Mountain View, CA Full Time


  
What You Will Do:



As a member of the DevOps team, you will be responsible for building and scaling the Moveworks AI cloud infrastructure and developer platform. As Moveworks grows fast, the infrastructure team is tasked with designing and operating reliable and resilient foundational services as well as frameworks that allow our product to scale seamlessly and our engineering teams to build customer facing features very rapidly.



We’re building a team that indexes on moving fast, solving challenging product/engineering problems and providing value to our customers. To be successful, you'll be partnering with machine learning, search, product, data, and full stack teams to identify, define and build elegant solutions. This is an opportunity to play an integral role at the fastest\-growing AI startup in its space.


* Closely work with platform, machine learning, search, data, and frontend teams, understand their DevOps and infrastructure need</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Zendesk</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b808411d8487a58f</link>
        <description>**Job Description**
-------------------

Role: Machine Learning Engineer


TBH\#:


Location: US  



  

Zendesk’s people have one goal in mind: to make Customer Experience better.  



  

The Enterprise Machine Learning team drives organizational value through scalable ML solutions and data\-driven insights, fundamentally changing how business decisions are made. We collaborate closely with stakeholders, applying the latest advances in machine learning, deep learning, and large language models (LLMs) to create highly impactful outcomes. Our commitment is to advance the state of AI, statistical modeling, and robust system design to enhance and expand our core business capabilities.


### **Role Overview**

As a Machine Learning Engineer, you will serve as a technical and strategic member within the team, driving the development and deployment of advanced data science and machine learning solutions—particularly those harnessing LLMs and deep learning. You will architect and scale ML s</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Infrastructure Software Engineer - KLA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=88aca83269910cc5</link>
        <description>Company Overview
KLA is a global leader in diversified electronics for the semiconductor manufacturing ecosystem. Virtually every electronic device in the world is produced using our technologies. No laptop, smartphone, wearable device, voice\-controlled gadget, flexible screen, VR device or smart car would have made it into your hands without us. KLA invents systems and solutions for the manufacturing of wafers and reticles, integrated circuits, packaging, printed circuit boards and flat panel displays. The innovative ideas and devices that are advancing humanity all begin with inspiration, research and development. KLA focuses more than average on innovation and we invest 15% of sales back into R\&amp;D. Our expert teams of physicists, engineers, data scientists and problem\-solvers work together with the world’s leading technology providers to accelerate the delivery of tomorrow’s electronic devices. Life here is exciting and our teams thrive on tackling really hard problems. There is n</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Hardware Validation Engineer, Servers, Compute, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3a9a43da681e3e10</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Physics, a related field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience working in board level design and testing, or 3 years of experience with an advanced degree.
* Experience with lab equipment like scopes, BERTs and analyzers.
* Experience with servers and compute platform architecture.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's or PhD degree in Electrical Engineering, Computer Engineering, Physics, or a related field.
* Experience managing teams and providing technical leadership for complex programs.
* Experience in collecting and organizing data to reproduce results and explain what happened.
* System\-level understanding of server products including physical, functional, logical, mechanical, electrical, software, thermal and cooling.
* Understanding of high speed transceiver interfaces like PCIe (physical, DLL and transaction layer), and memory interfaces </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer C++, Level 4 - Snap Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fe29ec411050d5c1</link>
        <description>Snap Inc is a technology company. We believe the camera presents the greatest opportunity to improve the way people live and communicate. Snap contributes to human progress by empowering people to express themselves, live in the moment, learn about the world, and have fun together. The Company’s three core products are Snapchat, a visual messaging app that enhances your relationships with friends, family, and the world; Lens Studio, an augmented reality platform that powers AR across Snapchat and other services; and its AR glasses, Spectacles.
Snap Engineering teams build fun and technically sophisticated products that reach hundreds of millions of Snapchatters around the world, every day. We’re deeply committed to the well\-being of everyone in our global community, which is why our values are at the root of everything we do. We move fast, with precision, and always execute with privacy at the forefront.
We’re looking for a C\+\+ Software Engineer to join our ML Infrastructure team!
W</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Full Stack Engineer, Content Engineering Tools - GeForce NOW - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d02f60d0ea1588bc</link>
        <description>We are seeking a Senior Full Stack Engineer to help build and enhance content engineering tools for GeForce NOW at NVIDIA. If you're experienced with various front\-end and backend technologies, are a fast learner, and have a get\-things\-done mentality, we'd love to hear from you!
You will play a significant role in crafting and guiding the future of GeForce NOW content engineering tools for our Cloud Gaming Business.
What you will be doing:* Collaborate with a world\-class team to design software platforms for content engineering tools at NVIDIA.
* Work closely with our Product and Design teams to define feature specifications and build the next generation of content engineering tools.
* Design and develop high\-performance, complex, and responsive full\-stack applications.
* Engineer brand\-new UX using JavaScript/TypeScript/HTML5, CSS; with a strong emphasis on React and similar frameworks.
* Architect and implement scalable backend services and RESTful APIs using Python and Java.
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer - Hardware - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cd9385e96a4da420</link>
        <description>We're now looking for a Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer! NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to solve, that only we can tackle, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human imagination and intelligence. Make the choice to join our diverse team today!
As a Senior Digital Design Verification Engineer at NVIDIA, you'll verify the design and implementation of our cutting edge SerDes IPs. This ground breaking technology will enable and accelerate gaming, artificial intelligence, deep learning, and autonomous driving. We have put together a best\-in\-class team that delivers IPs that will be consumed b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Neural Graphics Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=43ccee2279892053</link>
        <description>Computer graphics is experiencing its most exciting transformation in decades. Neural techniques are reshaping how we render, simulate, and create visual content in real time — and we're just getting started.
At NVIDIA, our Neural Graphics team builds technologies at the intersection of AI and real\-time rendering. We reach millions of developers and creators through products like Alpasim, open platforms like Slang, our shader language and compiler for portable GPU programming. We work on hard, meaningful problems with curiosity and collaboration — and we're looking for a Neural Graphics Engineer to grow with us. This is an opportunity to learn from some of the most accomplished people in graphics and AI, and to make a meaningful impact early in your career!
What You'll Be Doing:* Implement and optimize neural graphics techniques within real\-time rendering pipelines
* Prototype neural rendering, differentiable graphics, and generative 3D approaches
* Collaborate across teams to move i</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Recruiter, AI/ML Research - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8d6b77a5eacdd5ef</link>
        <description>About the Team
  
  

OpenAI’s mission is to build safe artificial general intelligence (AGI) that benefits all of humanity. Achieving this requires bringing the world’s most exceptional talent under one roof to push the boundaries of what’s possible.
  
  

Our Research Recruiting team plays a critical role in this effort. We are an embedded part of the research organization, working side by side with our research staff to deeply understand evolving priorities, build trust, and strategically shape the future of OpenAI’s talent.
  
  

About the Role
  
  

You will own and execute long\-term talent strategies to identify, engage, and recruit many of the world’s leading and emerging AI researchers, research engineers, and technical scientists working at the frontier of machine learning. This is not a traditional execution\-focused recruiting role.
  
  

You will operate as a strategic partner to OpenAI’s research staff, helping define hiring priorities, shape search strategy, influenc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer – VLM/LLM Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0df07204f739042b</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| NEW YORK CITY, NEW YORK, UNITED STATES \| KIRKLAND, WASHINGTON, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4608


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The mission of the Waymo AI Foundations team is to develop machine learning solutions add</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer (Full Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3e963f648194405d</link>
        <description>Hi! We’re Jerry.ai. We’re building the first AI\-powered **AllCar™ super app** to make car ownership affordable, seamless, and even magical. From insurance to repairs to road safety, we’re connecting the entire car ownership experience into one mobile\-first platform. Our revenue has grown 60x in the last 5 years, we’re profitable, and our goal is to scale from **5M 50M** users next.
We’re looking for a **Senior Software Engineer** to join our **Core Marketplace Automation Team**, building automation systems that let our users self\-serve, stay insured, and get the smoothest experience possible. This is a rare opportunity to **work on software that directly impacts millions of users**, **automate complex business processes**, and shape the future of insurance tech.

**Why you’ll love working here**

* **Real world impact:** Your code touches millions of end users every day. Our automation systems already handle complex tasks like document uploads/verification, policy changes, payment, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - AI Machine Learning - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=97577c68592f5b4a</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position title: SAP iXp Intern \- AI Machine Learning


Location: Palo Alto, CA (in\-person)


Expected start date: June 2026


Contract Duration: 6 months (extendable)


Workin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Designer - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6c6e4e534a104dac</link>
        <description>**You could work anywhere. Why join Jerry?**
Jerry is building the first **AI\-powered assistant for car ownership**, making it easy and affordable for the 80% of Americans who rely on their cars every day. From buying and insurance to financing, safety, and repairs, we’re reimagining the entire experience of owning a car.


It’s a $2T industry that’s fragmented, analog, and full of friction — and no one else is tackling it end\-to\-end. Since launching in 2019, **over 5 million people** have trusted Jerry to manage their car insurance, maintenance, and safety. We reached **profitability in 2024**, are backed by **$240M in funding**, and are on track to become a **$10B company by 2030**.


Customers love what we’ve built, and we’re just getting started. Now we’re ready to elevate our craft, define our brand, and design the next generation of products that make car ownership feel effortless. In other words: we have function. Now we need form.

**Why this role matters**


Millions of peo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II (Full Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ca14d0626b46d7b5</link>
        <description>Hi! We’re Jerry.ai. We’re building the first AI\-powered **AllCar™ super app** to make car ownership affordable, seamless, and even magical. From insurance to repairs to road safety, we’re connecting the entire car ownership experience into one mobile\-first platform. Our revenue has grown 60x in the last 5 years, we’re profitable, and our goal is to scale from **5M 50M** users next.
We’re looking for a **Software Engineer II** to join our **Core Marketplace Automation Team**, building automation systems that let our users self\-serve, stay insured, and get the smoothest experience possible. This is a rare opportunity to **work on software that directly impacts millions of users**, **automate complex business processes**, and shape the future of insurance tech.

**Why you’ll love working here**

* **Real world impact:** Your code touches millions of end users every day. Our automation systems already handle complex tasks like document uploads/verification, policy changes, payment, canc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, Consumer Products - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7955d57685cde83e</link>
        <description>**About** **Jerry.ai**  

Jerry.ai is building America’s first and only AI\-powered super app to radically simplify car ownership. We are redefining how people manage owning a car, one of their most expensive and time\-consuming assets. We are the \#1 rated and most downloaded app in our category with a 4\.7 star rating in the App Store. We have more than 5 million users, and have helped millions find better auto insurance — and we’re just getting started.**About The Opportunity:**

**Own how Jerry reimagines auto repair and maintenance — a space ready for a clearer, more trusted experience.**


Are you a curious and data\-driven Sr. Product Manager with deep customer empathy and strong UI/UX instincts, ready to **own a critical piece of our mission to radically simplify car ownership**? If so, you’ll be joining a company that’s already proven its momentum and is only just getting started. In 6 years, we’ve amassed 5M customers and are building toward a 10x expansion over the next few </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Product Designer - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b1f387e0d6176d6b</link>
        <description>**You could work anywhere. Why join Jerry?**
Jerry is building the first **AI\-powered assistant for car ownership**, making it easy and affordable for the 80% of Americans who rely on their cars every day. From buying and insurance to financing, safety, and repairs, we’re reimagining the entire experience of owning a car.


It’s a $2T industry that’s fragmented, analog, and full of friction — and no one else is tackling it end\-to\-end. Since launching in 2019, **over 5 million people** have trusted Jerry to manage their car insurance, maintenance, and safety. We reached **profitability in 2024**, are backed by **$240M in funding**, and are on track to become a **$10B company by 2030**.


Customers love what we’ve built, and we’re just getting started. Now we’re ready to elevate our craft, define our brand, and design the next generation of products that make car ownership feel effortless. In other words: we have function. Now we need form.

**Why this role matters**


Design is how w</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II (Full-Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ad78714c100e6ae4</link>
        <description>**Before we wrote this ad, we talked to our engineers and asked them what it’s really like working here. Here’s what they said.**
At most companies, engineers wait.


Wait for approvals. Wait for dependencies. Wait while real problems go unsolved.


At Jerry.ai, we don’t wait.


If you have an idea, you can explain it, build it, and ship it — sometimes in days, not months. One engineer told us: ***“At other companies I made very little difference. Here, if I have a good idea, I can go do it.”***


That sense of ownership is built into how we work. We move fast, and you’ll see your fingerprints on the product right away. Engineers here love being able to touch every layer of the stack, collaborate across teams, and see their work reflected in real customer behavior — sometimes the same week they ship. ***“Everything you do reflects immediately for the users,”*** said another. ***“And things move fast.”***


We don’t do bureaucracy. We don’t do politics. Everyone here — from our CTO to o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer II (Full Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=69c23a47c47f3de1</link>
        <description>Hi! We’re Jerry.ai. We’re building the first AI\-powered **AllCar™ super app** to make car ownership affordable, seamless, and even magical. From insurance to repairs to road safety, we’re connecting the entire car ownership experience into one mobile\-first platform. Our revenue has grown 60x in the last 5 years, we’re profitable, and our goal is to scale from **5M 50M** users next.
We’re looking for a **Software Engineer II** to join our **Core Marketplace Automation Team**, building automation systems that let our users self\-serve, stay insured, and get the smoothest experience possible. This is a rare opportunity to **work on software that directly impacts millions of users**, **automate complex business processes**, and shape the future of insurance tech.

**Why you’ll love working here**

* **Real world impact:** Your code touches millions of end users every day. Our automation systems already handle complex tasks like document uploads/verification, policy changes, payment, canc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, New Products - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=71c391efc2f88b16</link>
        <description>**About** **Jerry.ai**  

Jerry.ai is building America’s first and only AI\-powered super app to radically simplify car ownership. We are redefining how people manage owning a car, one of their most expensive and time\-consuming assets. We are the \#1 rated and most downloaded app in our category with a 4\.7 star rating in the App Store. We have more than 5 million users, and have helped millions find better auto insurance — and we’re just getting started.**About The Opportunity:**

**Own how Jerry reimagines auto repair and maintenance — a space ready for a clearer, more trusted experience.**


Are you a curious and data\-driven Sr. Product Manager with deep customer empathy and strong UI/UX instincts, ready to **own a critical piece of our mission to radically simplify car ownership**? If so, you’ll be joining a company that’s already proven its momentum and is only just getting started. In 6 years, we’ve amassed 5M customers and are building toward a 10x expansion over the next few </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Product Manager, Emerging Products - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=98829bde5a37350c</link>
        <description>**About** **Jerry.ai**  

Jerry.ai is building America’s first and only AI\-powered super app to radically simplify car ownership. We are redefining how people manage owning a car, one of their most expensive and time\-consuming assets. We are the \#1 rated and most downloaded app in our category with a 4\.7 star rating in the App Store. We have more than 5 million users, and have helped millions find better auto insurance — and we’re just getting started.**About The Opportunity:**

**Own how Jerry reimagines auto repair and maintenance — a space ready for a clearer, more trusted experience.**


Are you a curious and data\-driven Sr. Product Manager with deep customer empathy and strong UI/UX instincts, ready to **own a critical piece of our mission to radically simplify car ownership**? If so, you’ll be joining a company that’s already proven its momentum and is only just getting started. In 6 years, we’ve amassed 5M customers and are building toward a 10x expansion over the next few </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer (Full-Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=35fded17f6dfbee5</link>
        <description>**Before we wrote this ad, we talked to our engineers and asked them what it’s really like working here. Here’s what they said.**
At most companies, engineers wait.


Wait for approvals. Wait for dependencies. Wait while real problems go unsolved.


At Jerry.ai, we don’t wait.


If you have an idea, you can explain it, build it, and ship it — sometimes in days, not months. One engineer told us: ***“At other companies I made very little difference. Here, if I have a good idea, I can go do it.”***


That sense of ownership is built into how we work. We move fast, and you’ll see your fingerprints on the product right away. Engineers here love being able to touch every layer of the stack, collaborate across teams, and see their work reflected in real customer behavior — sometimes the same week they ship. ***“Everything you do reflects immediately for the users,”*** said another. ***“And things move fast.”***


We don’t do bureaucracy. We don’t do politics. Everyone here — from our CTO to o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer (Full-Stack, Backend-leaning) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3deb113f1c97ac9d</link>
        <description>**Before we wrote this ad, we talked to our engineers and asked them what it’s really like working here. Here’s what they said.**
At most companies, engineers wait.


Wait for approvals. Wait for dependencies. Wait while real problems go unsolved.


At Jerry.ai, we don’t wait.


If you have an idea, you can explain it, build it, and ship it — sometimes in days, not months. One engineer told us: ***“At other companies I made very little difference. Here, if I have a good idea, I can go do it.”***


That sense of ownership is built into how we work. We move fast, and you’ll see your fingerprints on the product right away. Engineers here love being able to touch every layer of the stack, collaborate across teams, and see their work reflected in real customer behavior — sometimes the same week they ship. ***“Everything you do reflects immediately for the users,”*** said another. ***“And things move fast.”***


We don’t do bureaucracy. We don’t do politics. Everyone here — from our CTO to o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Automated Driving Intern - Simulation at Scale for RL - Bosch</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d70f838b64860f16</link>
        <description>**Company Description**  

The Bosch Research and Technology Center North America with offices in Sunnyvale, California, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and Cambridge, Massachusetts is a part of the global Bosch Group (www.bosch.com), a company with over 80\-billion\-euro revenue, 400,000 employees worldwide, a very diverse product portfolio, and a history spanning over 125 years. The Research and Technology Center North America (RTC\-NA) is dedicated to providing technologies and system solutions for various Bosch business fields, primarily in the field of artificial intelligence (AI) (e.g., human\-assisted AI, natural language processing, robotics, 3D perception, and AI platform), energy technologies, internet technologies, circuit design, semiconductors and wireless, as well as advanced MEMS design.


As a part of the global research, our AI research in Silicon Valley (Bosch Center for AI) focuses on research topics such as Big Data Visual Analytics, Explainable AI (XAI), Natural Language </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, SOC Design - Samsung Semiconductor Inc (US)</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8e0a1874d82b5b9f</link>
        <description>**Please Note:**



To provide the best candidate experience amidst our high application volumes, each candidate is limited to 10 applications across all open jobs within a 6\-month period.


**Advancing the World's Technology Together**



Our technology solutions power the tools you use every day\-including smartphones, electric vehicles, hyperscale data centers, IoT devices, and so much more. Here, you'll have an opportunity to be part of a global leader whose innovative designs are pushing the boundaries of what's possible and powering the future.



We believe innovation and growth are driven by an inclusive culture and a diverse workforce. We're dedicated to empowering people to be their true selves. Together, we're building a better tomorrow for our employees, customers, partners, and communities.

**Principal Engineer, SOC Design**


**What You'll Do**



The DRAM Development Lab (DDL) is part of Samsung's Memory Business Unit, the industry's technology and volume leader in DRA</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer – VLM/LLM Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c0bc57b2bad8ac01</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The mission of the Waymo AI Foundations team is to develop machine learning solutions addressing open problems in autonomous driving, towards the goal of safely operating Waymo vehicles in dozens of cities and under all driving conditions. As part of our work, we also initiate and foster coll</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Mechanical Design Engineer, Automated Test Equipment, Optimus - Tesla</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2ee8e5a35727c4b</link>
        <description>**What to Expect**
We seek a highly motivated hands\-on Sr. Mechanical Engineer for a position in the Manufacturing Test Engineering group as part of the “machine that builds the machine”. The group is focused on creating robust, beautiful, data\-centric production testing equipment for Tesla’s power electronic components in vehicle, stationary storage, humanoid robot and charging products.


The ideal candidates take pride in their hands\-on work, analytical ability, organizational skills, and attention todetail, and appreciate an environment where superior work is encouraged, noticed, and rewarded. The candidates look forward to learning an incredible amount on the job, excited to share the knowledge and mentor Engineers, and do not shy away from tremendous levels of responsibility.  



  

**What You'll Do*** Architect automated test equipment, produce detailed\-level CAD models, pneumatic diagrams, and verify designs using structural and thermal FEA and CFD
* Conceptual equipment </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Pacific Community Ventures</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0447d34a5a96e2c3</link>
        <description>**About Us**  
PCV is a nonprofit community development investor that supports small business entrepreneurs and their communities to build economic mobility through the power of inclusive entrepreneurship and a good quality job. We work side\-by\-side with small business leaders through our unique integrated model: combining impact\-first Restorative Capital and Pro Bono Business Advising with our Good Jobs Innovation Lab that propels thriving communities with equitable jobs, climate outcomes, uplifts and amplifies their voices and needs through research and policy advocacy.

**The Role**  
Are you an experienced data scientist who is passionate about applying your data and technology development skills towards building a more equitable society? If so, please consider joining Pacific Community Ventures as a Data Scientist. As a mission\-driven lender, we invest in diverse small businesses across the state of California to help them grow and strengthen their practices. You’ll work to ta</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ML Ops Engineer II - Early Warning Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1bb70d7640bf48cc</link>
        <description>At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and protect transactions for hundreds of millions of consumers and small businesses.
Positions located in Scottsdale, San Francisco, Chicago, or New York follow a hybrid work model to allow for a more collaborative working environment.
Candidates responding to this posting must independently possess the eligibility to work in the United States, for any employer, at the date of hire. This position is ineligible for employment Visa sponsorship.
At Early Warning, we’ve powered and protected the U.S. financial system for over thirty years with cutting\-edge solutions like Zelle®, Paze℠, and so much more. As a trusted name in payments, we partner with thousands of institutions to increase access to financial services and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Applied AI - Okta</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=981ef83ee02535af</link>
        <description>**Get to know Okta**  

  

Okta is The World’s Identity Company. We free everyone to safely use any technology, anywhere, on any device or app. Our flexible and neutral products, Okta Platform and Auth0 Platform, provide secure access, authentication, and automation, placing identity at the core of business security and growth.  

  

At Okta, we celebrate a variety of perspectives and experiences. We are not looking for someone who checks every single box \- we’re looking for lifelong learners and people who can make us better with their unique experiences.  

  

Join our team! We’re building a world where Identity belongs to you.


Okta’s Business Technology organization builds secure and intelligent internal platforms that power our global workforce. Our **AI \&amp; Automation** team is delivering next\-generation tools and experiences by integrating GenAI and intelligent automation into workflows across IT, HR, Finance, Sales, Marketing and Customer Support.



We focus on real\-worl</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Researcher - Rivet Industries</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=756a548f7b63644b</link>
        <description>**About Rivet**


Rivet is an American company building integrated task systems — fusing hardened hardware with software, sensors, AI, and networking — for industrial workforces and defense personnel. We create capabilities that multiply the effectiveness of every individual and withstand the world’s toughest environments.

  

We serve the people who build, operate, maintain, and defend our way of life. From technicians and engineers to first responders and service members, they embody the hard work, ingenuity, and meritocratic values that drive Western prosperity. Yet too often they are forced to rely on outdated tools that fail under modern pressures. Rivet exists to reset that priority.

  

At Rivet, you’ll join a mission\-driven team that fuses disciplines to deliver decisive outcomes where they matter most. Whether shaping our technology, strengthening our partnerships, or building our culture, every role here contributes to equipping the front lines with the modern systems they</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Software Engineer - Jerry.AI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c5440def00fdecae</link>
        <description>Hi there! If you're looking to make a real\-world impact fast while leveling up your skills in a high\-growth startup, we might be the right place for you!

**Why join Jerry?**


We’re Jerry, and we’re building the first AI\-powered AllCar app to completely rethink what it means to own a car. Car insurance, maintenance, repairs, financing—we’re simplifying it all into one seamless mobile experience. Our users already save over $1,000/year with us, and we’ve grown revenue 60x in the last 5 years.


Now we’re scaling from 5M to 50M users, and we need sharp, curious engineers located in the SF area to help us get there.


**Here’s what you’ll get:**


Impact from Day One — you’ll be writing production code within your first few weeks.


Backed and booming — we’ve raised $240M\+ and are cash\-flow positive.


Modern tech stack — React, Node, Python, AWS, TypeScript, and more.


Mentorship \+ learning — work with top engineers from companies like Nvidia, TikTok, and Cepton.


Merit\-based g</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Mobile Ads Security and Fraud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0967b1e0d0f95e5e</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Mathematics, a related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience with software development in one or more general\-purpose programming languages.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products (e.g., security tools, mobile apps, or data pipelines).
* 1 year of experience focused on software design and architecture within distributed systems.
* Experience analyzing large\-scale datasets to identify anomalies or system vulnerabilities.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Computer Science, Cyber\-security, or a related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with advanced data structures, algorithms, and large\-scale system construction (e.g., MapReduce, Bigtable).
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role, guiding project roadmaps and mentoring engineering talent.
* Experience developing accessible technolo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, AI Storage, Google Distributed Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7cf4aa61d695718f</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Cambridge, MA, USA; Raleigh, NC, USA; Durham, NC, USA; Seattle, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or related technical field or equivale</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7a3aa92c6e02eecd</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Technical Program Manager II, Machine Learning, Google Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=820d54d8b1bf896d</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in a technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of machine learning work experience.
* 10 years of experience in program management.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 10 years of experience managing complex cross\-functional or cross\-team projects.

**About the job**
-----------------


A problem isn’t truly solved until it’s solved for all. That’s why Googlers build products that help create opportunities for everyone, whether down the street or across the globe. As a Technical Program Manager at Google, you’ll use your technical expertise to lead complex, multi\-disciplinary projects from start to finish. You’ll work with stakeholders to plan requirements, identify risks, manage project schedules, and communicate clearly with cross\-</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Engineer (1043) - DataSF - City and County of San Francisco</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=012bacb5fe848397</link>
        <description>**Company Description** **Department:** DataSF  

**Job class:** 1043 Senior Data Engineer  

**Salary range:** $153,686/year \- $193,388/year  

**Role type:** Permanent Exempt  

**Hours:** Full\-time. The department has a hybrid work schedule.

**About:**  

Permanent Exempt: This is an Exempt position excluded by the Charter from the competitive Civil Service examination process, pursuant to the City and County of San Francisco, Charter Section 10\.104\. It is considered "at will" and shall serve at the discretion of the Appointing Officer.  

  

Application Opening: **Monday, February 23, 2026**  

Application Closing: Interested candidates are encouraged to apply as soon as possible, as this job announcement will close at any time, but not earlier than **Sunday, March 2, 2026 at 11:59pm PST**

**As part of the application process, you must also complete a Supplemental Questionnaire using this link by the filing deadline:** **https://forms.office.com/g/PgvQyRjYdX**

**The Office </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Hardware Validation Engineer - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3531cd0c44ba562c</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to resolve, that only we can seek, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human inventiveness and intelligence.
NVIDIA’s System Co\-Design Group (SCG) team is seeking a versatile engineer to be part of a Silicon Hardware team. You will partner with silicon validation teams to capture, interpret, and refine bring‑up platform requirements, then drive alignment and reviews with the platform design team. In this role, you will shape validation platforms that support product lines spanning artificial intelligence, consumer graphics, self‑driving cars, and other cutting‑edge tec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Datacenter Resiliency Architect, RAS Features and Modeling - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dbab83c64b61ddf1</link>
        <description>We are now looking for a Principal Datacenter Resiliency Architect, RAS Features and Modeling! Today, NVIDIA is tapping into the unlimited potential of AI to define the next era of computing. An era in which our GPU acts as the brains of computers, robots, and self\-driving cars that can understand the world. Doing what’s never been done before takes vision, innovation, and the world’s best talent. As an NVIDIAN, you’ll be immersed in a diverse, encouraging environment where everyone is inspired to do their best work. Come join the team and see how we can make a lasting impact on the world.
We are now seeking a Resiliency Architect to support the development and validation of GPU (graphical processing unit) hardware and software resiliency features, including modeling reliability and availability from component to datacenter level. In this role, you will be a key member of a team of innovators, challenging the status quo and pushing beyond boundaries. You will have the opportunity to i</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Generative AI Engineer - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1a035421dad8e109</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **This is a hybrid role based out of Palo Alto, CA. Hybrid is 3 days a week on\-site, 2 days a week remote.**

 **Summary:**  

With over 3\.6 million connected companies, the SAP Business Network powers global commerce. We are moving beyond simple automation to build autonomous supply chain agents capable of reasoning, planning, and exception handling.

  

This is a high\-impact role for a technical leader to design the architecture that bridges unstructured data with structured busin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Engineer - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a672c4a0dc83d4a7</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **This is a hybrid role based out of Palo Alto, CA. Hybrid is 3 days a week on\-site, 2 days a week remote.**

 **Summary:**


With over 3\.6 million connected companies, the SAP Business Network powers global commerce. We are moving beyond simple automation to build autonomous supply chain agents capable of reasoning, planning, and exception handling.

  

This is a hands\-on role for a Senior AI Application Engineer to drive the design and implementation of intelligent agents that bri</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Associate Software Engineer - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ee2d17e6af7f1398</link>
        <description>Hi there! If you're looking to make a real\-world impact fast while leveling up your skills in a high\-growth startup, we might be the right place for you!**Why join Jerry?**


We’re Jerry, and we’re building the first AI\-powered AllCar™ app to completely rethink what it means to own a car. Car insurance, maintenance, repairs, financing—we’re simplifying it all into one seamless mobile experience. Our users already save over $1,000/year with us, and we’ve grown revenue 60x in the last 5 years.


Now we’re scaling from 5M to 50M users, and we need sharp, curious engineers located in the SF area to help us get there.


**Here’s what you’ll get:**


✅ Impact from Day One — you’ll be writing production code within your first few weeks.


✅ Backed and booming — we’ve raised $240M\+ and are cash\-flow positive.


✅ Modern tech stack — React, Node, Python, AWS, TypeScript, and more.


✅ Mentorship \+ learning — work with top engineers from companies like Nvidia, TikTok, and Cepton.


✅ Merit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (entry) - Jerry</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cd82e56ef354fee9</link>
        <description>Hi there! If you're looking to make a real\-world impact fast while leveling up your skills in a high\-growth startup, we might be the right place for you!**Why join Jerry?**


We’re Jerry, and we’re building the first AI\-powered AllCar™ app to completely rethink what it means to own a car. Car insurance, maintenance, repairs, financing—we’re simplifying it all into one seamless mobile experience. Our users already save over $1,000/year with us, and we’ve grown revenue 60x in the last 5 years.


Now we’re scaling from 5M to 50M users, and we need sharp, curious engineers located in the SF area to help us get there.


**Here’s what you’ll get:**


✅ Impact from Day One — you’ll be writing production code within your first few weeks.


✅ Backed and booming — we’ve raised $240M\+ and are cash\-flow positive.


✅ Modern tech stack — React, Node, Python, AWS, TypeScript, and more.


✅ Mentorship \+ learning — work with top engineers from companies like Nvidia, TikTok, and Cepton.


✅ Merit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=70305e4256b84960</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------


Personalization team at Walmart is dedicated to the mission of knowing our customers better and making it frictionless and faster for them to get what they want while building a trusted partnership with Walmart. We help bring a seamless experience to our customers irrespective of how and where they engage with us – while shopping online or picking groceries at stores. We thrive to provide each customer with a journey tailored to their individual needs, preferences and routines. We operate at the intersection of huge Walmart assortment, millions of customers, thousands of stores and Walmart associates \- a multi\-layer multi\-objective problem space which has a unique impact on Global customer base and powers assisted AI for our associates. The Personalization team consists of big data geeks, application engineers, scientists and product visionaries all working together to design, prototype an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer 50 - Adobe</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=652c1e250e125af4</link>
        <description>The Opportunity
  
Adobe Journey Optimizer B2B is redefining how enterprises engage buying groups through AI\-powered customer journey orchestration. We're building intelligent systems that understand complex B2B buyer behavior, predict intent signals across accounts, and deliver hyper\-personalized experiences at every touchpoint—from first awareness through closed revenue.
  
  

We are looking for a Machine Learning Engineer \&amp; Architect to join our AI and Agents team, define and own the ML architecture vision for our B2B journey orchestration platform. In this role, you'll shape how thousands of B2B enterprises leverage AI to transform pipeline generation, accelerate deal velocity, and drive measurable revenue impact. Your architecture decisions will power billions of personalized interactions annually, directly influencing how marketing and sales teams identify, engage, and convert buying committees.
  
  

What you'll do with us
  
  

You'll train and finetune ML models that sol</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Quality Assurance Engineer, Creative Imaging Apps - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=28e3471f024fdac7</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here! The people here at Apple don’t just build products \- we craft the kind of wonder that’s revolutionized entire industries. It’s the diversity of those people and their ideas that supports the innovation that runs through everything we do, from amazing technology to industry\-leading environmental efforts. The Creative Imaging Applications team is looking for a Software Quality Assurance Engineer that has experience in iPadOS \&amp; macOS apps, image/graphics design software, and advanced image editors. Ideally, we are searching for a highly motivated, enthusiastic, and experienced QA engineer with a passion and/or background in digital design to contribute to the production of innovative tools for creative professionals, visual storytellers, and the next generation of creators.  

  

**Description**  

  

As an Creative Imaging Apps Software QA Engineer, you will be responsible for testing both existing and newly developed features across all supported App</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Camera Embedded Software Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cf4f7c768be37082</link>
        <description>Apple's Camera Firmware team is looking for an extraordinary firmware engineer to drive groundbreaking technologies for Apple products! As part of the team you would work on core camera/ISP/Machine learning technologies, including Apple crafted Image signal processing pipeline and HW components, where you will have the chance to define the way that Apple develops, tests and manufactures all of its products. Our close\-knit team champions an environment of product innovation, rapid product iteration and collaboration at both team and multi\-functional levels with a liberating amount of autonomy!  

  

**Description**  

  

In this role you will implement, maintain and pursue problems in our firmware. This is a highly multi\-functional product development role and you will work closely with various teams, like Silicon Design, QA team and the Machine Learning algorithm team! The environment is multifaceted, fast\-paced and requires a self\-starter demeanor.","responsibilities":"Develop </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Ads Signals Intelligence and Information Retrieval - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8ff005053d5baae0</link>
        <description>At Apple, we focus deeply on our customers’ experience. Apple Ads brings this same approach to advertising, helping people find exactly what they’re looking for and helping advertisers grow their businesses.  

  

Our technology powers ads and sponsorships across Apple Services, including the App Store, Apple News, and MLS Season Pass. Everything we do is designed for trust, connection, and impact: We respect user privacy, integrate advertising thoughtfully into the experience, and deliver value for advertisers of all sizes\-from small app developers to big, global brands. Because when advertising is done right, it benefits everyone.  

  

**Description**  

  

Apple’s Ads Signals Intelligence team is seeking a hands\-on and experienced Machine Learning Engineer to develop the next generation of ML\-driven signal platforms that power retrieval, prediction, and relevance across Apple’s advertising ecosystem\-including the App Store and Apple News.  

  

This role focuses on building</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Siri Runtime Systems and Interaction - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=50939989a3b294ea</link>
        <description>We are a group of engineers working on making Siri more intelligent and intuitive to interact with. We focus on innovating multimodal machine learning solutions that improve the experience for our users. We adapt our technologies based on various sensors available on different hardware products and make them run efficiently. We collaborate with various teams at Apple to deploy these innovative solutions to our products.  

  

**Description**  

  

As a member of the team you will be responsible for researching and developing innovative ML solutions for challenging problems that will meaningfully affect how users interact with Siri on Apple products. You will be looking at the user experience we want to deliver, define the optimization metrics and propose solutions to achieve the goal. You will bring these innovations to life by working collaboratively with partner teams to take them all the way to production. You are self\-motivated, excellent problem solver with strong execution. Yo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Machine Learning Engineer - News, Books, &amp; Stocks Team - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ea46ebfa5b876df0</link>
        <description>In a time where the news and book media landscapes are changing by the day, Apple News and  

  

Apple Books stand as champions of quality content, expert curation, user privacy, and the  

  

judicious use of machine learning.  

  

Our lively and brilliant team consists of client and machine learning engineers who embody  

  

Apple's values. We inspire, teach, and otherwise enable each other to do the best work of our  

  

careers.  

  

Our team's outstanding retention rate speaks to our strong culture of respect for our teammates  

  

as both engineers and people.  

  

Would you like to work on such a team, solving hard problems in machine learning? Terrific!  

  

Please join us for the next generation of these apps!  

  

**Description**  

  

Our team is seeking a high\-energy and self\-driven machine learning engineer who will play a  

  

central role in the delivery of scalable services. The team uses machine learning to tackle  

  

difficult and complicated</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Senior ML Researcher in Foundation Models, Responsible AI - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0ae583941cf97bf0</link>
        <description>Join us as we build world\-class groundbreaking products for our customers! Apple's Responsible AI and Safety team is looking to hire a technical lead with a strong track record in Applied Research who is passionate about ML and foundation models with a focus on responsibility, fairness, and safety. In this role, you will lead the research and application of ML methods for technologies that power breakthrough user experiences while upholding Apple's values, privacy, and quality standards.  

  

**Description**  

  

This role will be highly multifunctional. You will collaborate closely with top machine learning researchers and engineers, software engineers, and design teams to develop and deliver groundbreaking solutions for Apple products. We believe that the most exciting problems in machine learning research arise at the intersection of emerging technologies and real\-world use cases. This is also where the most critical breakthroughs come from. As a researcher, you will:  

  

*</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Responsible AI and Safety - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d3793fcea00faf51</link>
        <description>Would you like to play a part in building the next generation of generative AI applications at Apple? We’re looking for Machine Learning Engineers to work on ambitious projects that will impact the future of Apple, our products, and the broader world. This role is directed at assessing, quantifying, and improving the safety and inclusivity of Apple’s Generative\-AI powered features and products. In this role you’ll have the opportunity to tackle innovative problems in machine learning, particularly focused on large language models for text generation, diffusion models for image generation, and mixed model systems for multimodal applications. As a member of Apple’s Responsible AI group you will be working on a wide array of new features and research in the generative AI space. Our team is currently interested in large generative models for vision and language, with particular interest on Responsible AI, safety, fairness, robustness, explainability, and uncertainty in models.  

  

**De</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Signal Processing Software Engineer - Applied Intuition</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=47a5927717184d5a</link>
        <description>**About Applied Intuition**
---------------------------


Applied Intuition, Inc. is powering the future of physical AI. Founded in 2017 and now valued at $15 billion, the Silicon Valley company is creating the digital infrastructure needed to bring intelligence to every moving machine on the planet. Applied Intuition services the automotive, defense, trucking, construction, mining and agriculture industries in three core areas: tools and infrastructure, operating systems, and autonomy. Eighteen of the top 20 global automakers, as well as the United States military and its allies, trust the company's solutions to deliver physical intelligence. Applied Intuition is headquartered in Sunnyvale, California, with offices in Washington, D.C.; San Diego; Ft. Walton Beach, Florida; Ann Arbor, Michigan; London; Stuttgart; Munich; Stockholm; Bangalore; Seoul; and Tokyo. Learn more at applied.co.
*We are an in\-office company, and our expectation is that employees primarily work from their Applie</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director, Digital Learning - Delinea</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4611c04e5ea16d9e</link>
        <description>**About Delinea:**  

Delinea is a pioneer in securing human and machine identities through intelligent, centralized authorization, empowering organizations to seamlessly govern their interactions across the modern enterprise. Leveraging AI\-powered intelligence, Delinea’s leading cloud\-native Identity Security Platform applies context throughout the entire identity lifecycle – across cloud and traditional infrastructure, data, SaaS applications, and AI. It is the only platform that enables you to discover all identities – including workforce, IT administrator, developers, and machines – assign appropriate access levels, detect irregularities, and respond to threats in real\-time. With deployment in weeks, not months, 90% fewer resources to manage than the nearest competitor, and a 99\.995% uptime, Delinea delivers robust security and operational efficiency without compromise. Learn more about Delinea on Delinea.com, LinkedIn, X, and YouTube.


Join our passionate, global team at Deli</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Agent - Pika</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a550f1035b38bdf3</link>
        <description>*Senior Software Engineer, Agent*  

  

*Department:* Engineering \| *Location:* Palo Alto HQ \| *Type:* Full\-time, On\-site  

  

*About the Role*  

We're looking for a Senior Agent Engineer to push the boundaries of what AI agents can do at Pika. You'll work on the systems that give AI agents their personality, memory, reasoning, multi\-modal capabilities, and ability to act autonomously across platforms. This is the core of what makes Pika's AI products feel alive.  

  

You'll design agent architectures, build tool\-use frameworks, optimize LLM interactions, and create the systems that allow agents to learn, remember, and evolve over time. If you're excited about building AI systems that feel genuinely intelligent — not just wrappers over chat APIs — this role is for you.  

  

*What You'll Do*  

* Design and evolve the agent runtime — the core loop that handles reasoning, tool use, memory retrieval, and response generation
* Build agent capabilities — image generation, voic</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Data Analyst - Super Micro Computer, Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4fcebd76e0743460</link>
        <description>Sr. Data Analyst

  

**Date:** Feb 24, 2026


**Location:** San Jose, California, United States


**Company:** Super Micro Computer


**Job Req ID: 28380**
**About Supermicro:**

Supermicro® is a Top Tier provider of advanced server, storage, and networking solutions for Data Center, Cloud Computing, Enterprise IT, Hadoop/ Big Data, Hyperscale, HPC and IoT/Embedded customers worldwide. We are the \#5 fastest growing company among the Silicon Valley Top 50 technology firms. Our unprecedented global expansion has provided us with the opportunity to offer a large number of new positions to the technology community. We seek talented, passionate, and committed engineers, technologists, and business leaders to join us.  

**Job Summary:**

Supermicro is seeking a Sr. Data Analyst to drive business process analysis, documentation, and optimization across various strategic initiatives. This role is ideal for a self\-starter who can work with limited structure, engages take holders, and develo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Marketing Innovation - OpenAI</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=50da1a7d4cd0e76a</link>
        <description>Careers
  
  

Data Scientist, Marketing Innovation
  
  

Data Science \- San Francisco
  
  

About the Role
  
  

We’re hiring a Data Scientist to support our Marketing Innovation pod, a cross\-functional team building the internal tools and agentic systems that fundamentally change how we do marketing and serve customers.
  
  

**We build product\-like systems that:**  

Deliver high\-touch, consultative experiences to millions of SMB customers through agentic lifecycle and sales experiences
  
  

Adapt messaging, creative, and outreach using real\-time behavioral signals
  
  

Power intelligent routing, targeting, and engagement decisions at scale, with minimal human\-in\-the\-loop
  
  

In this role, you’ll be embedded with Product and Engineering to ensure these systems drive measurable business outcomes.
  
  

What You’ll Do
  
  

Define success metrics for agentic marketing systems (e.g., incremental pipeline generated, conversion lift, rep hours saved), including leadi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-24</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist (Start-Up) - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=868be077d2a214f1</link>
        <description>### **Qualifications \&amp; Experience**


* Minimum of 4\+ years of hands\-on experience in data science within high\-performing product analytics environments, ideally supporting B2B software platforms.
* Advanced proficiency in **Python and SQL** , including strong working knowledge of pandas, NumPy, StatsModels or Scikit\-learn, and experience working within modern data warehouses such as BigQuery or Snowflake.
* Strong command of statistical sampling methodologies, including stratified sampling, bootstrapping techniques, and reliable extrapolation approaches.
* Proven track record of independently designing, building, and deploying analytics tools or frameworks that were successfully adopted by product, growth, or cross\-functional teams.
* Deep expertise in experimentation and causal measurement, including A/B testing, difference\-in\-differences analysis, propensity score matching, matched market testing, and statistical power calculations.
* Hands\-on experience working with large </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Global Product R&amp;D Center - San Francisco - Plaud</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=41d0957d2d36fcb4</link>
        <description>**About Plaud Inc.**


Plaud is building the world's most trusted AI work companion for professionals to elevate productivity and performance through note\-taking solutions, loved by over 1,500,000 users worldwide since 2023\. With a mission to amplify human intelligence, Plaud is building the next\-generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, and utilize what you say, hear, see, and think.

  

Plaud Inc. is a Delaware\-incorporated, San Francisco\-based company pushing the boundary of human–AI intelligence through a hardware–software combination. With ISO 27001, ISO 27701, GDPR, SOC 2, HIPAA, and EN 18031 compliance, Plaud is committed to the highest standards of data security and privacy protection.

  

To learn more about Plaud, please visit https://www.plaud.ai and follow along on Instagram, X, Facebook, LinkedIn, and YouTube

 **Why You Should Join Us**


Plaud is building the next generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, ex</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Analyst, Teams - San Francisco - Plaud</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4cbf72e080da509b</link>
        <description>**About Plaud Inc.**


Plaud is building the world's most trusted AI work companion for professionals to elevate productivity and performance through note\-taking solutions, loved by over 1,500,000 users worldwide since 2023\. With a mission to amplify human intelligence, Plaud is building the next\-generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, and utilize what you say, hear, see, and think.


Plaud Inc. is a Delaware\-incorporated, San Francisco\-based company pushing the boundary of human–AI intelligence through a hardware–software combination. With ISO 27001, ISO 27701, GDPR, SOC 2, HIPAA, and EN 18031 compliance, Plaud is committed to the highest standards of data security and privacy protection.


To learn more about Plaud, please visit https://www.plaud.ai and follow along on Instagram, X, Facebook, LinkedIn, and YouTube

**Why You Should Join Us**


Plaud is building the next generation intelligence infrastructure and interfaces to capture, extract, </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior AI Specialist - DocuSign</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=aeab1ee32b95dd3c</link>
        <description>**Company Overview**
--------------------

  

Docusign brings agreements to life. Over 1\.5 million customers and more than a billion people in over 180 countries use Docusign solutions to accelerate the process of doing business and simplify people’s lives. With intelligent agreement management, Docusign unleashes business\-critical data that is trapped inside of documents. Until now, these were disconnected from business systems of record, costing businesses time, money, and opportunity. Using Docusign’s Intelligent Agreement Management platform, companies can create, commit, and manage agreements with solutions created by the \#1 company in e\-signature and contract lifecycle management (CLM).  

  

**What You'll Do**
------------------

  

The Senior AI Specialist – Partner Digital Transformation \&amp; Success plays a pivotal role in empowering our global partner ecosystem to accelerate digital transformation and achieve measurable business outcomes through advanced AI technologies</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Cloud AI - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e2bc7e003c119e13</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Kirkland, WA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 7 years of experience leading technical</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Google Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=76e37f7d1610c50e</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; New York, NY, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 3 years of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structu</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer III, AI/ML GenAI, YouTube - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=391141c6ac856cb9</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience programming in Python and C\+\+.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).
* Experience with core GenAI concepts (LLM, Multi\-Modal, Large Vision Models) and experience with text, image, video, or audio generation.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Engineer - AI/LLM - Super Micro Computer, Inc.</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8147e3e533cff873</link>
        <description>Sr. Software Engineer \- AI/LLM

  

**Date:** Feb 23, 2026


**Location:** San Jose, California, United States


**Company:** Super Micro Computer


**Job Req ID: 28343**
**About Supermicro:**

Supermicro® is a Top Tier provider of advanced server, storage, and networking solutions for Data Center, Cloud Computing, Enterprise IT, Hadoop/ Big Data, Hyperscale, HPC and IoT/Embedded customers worldwide. We are the \#5 fastest growing company among the Silicon Valley Top 50 technology firms. Our unprecedented global expansion has provided us with the opportunity to offer a large number of new positions to the technology community. We seek talented, passionate, and committed engineers, technologists, and business leaders to join us.**Job Summary:**

Supermicro is seeking an experienced and exceptional Sr. Software Engineer to work on web\-based applications for business process automation. This is a key role that will give you the opportunity to expand your existing knowledge in programmin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Ad Measurement Products - Pinterest</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ab7a89414dbc28a7</link>
        <description>**About Pinterest:**



Millions of people around the world come to our platform to find creative ideas, dream about new possibilities and plan for memories that will last a lifetime. At Pinterest, we're on a mission to bring everyone the inspiration to create a life they love, and that starts with the people behind the product.



Discover a career where you ignite innovation for millions, transform passion into growth opportunities, celebrate each other's unique experiences and embrace the flexibility to do your best work. Creating a career you love? It's Possible.


We're looking for a Staff Data Scientist to lead the science behind how advertisers understand the impact of their investment on Pinterest through first and third party measurement products. You'll push the boundaries of ads measurement, advancing our approaches to causal inference and incrementality and partner closely with Product and Engineering, as well as represent Pinterest science externally with customers and par</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Data Analyst - Stanford University</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3f79eaf0fa99d3e8</link>
        <description>The Neuromuscular Division of Neurology is seeking a Research Data Analyst (RDA) with experience in clinical data management to oversee and analyze research data while assuring operational efficiency and regulatory compliance, The RDA will be responsible for data collection, compilation, statistical analysis, reporting, and overall data management support for research initiatives.


The division is pursuing novel approaches to quantify movement using wearables and video\-based technologies, as well as development of new analytical methods for MRI data to characterize disease health for individuals with neuromuscular disease. As disease\-modifying treatments become available, we work closely with experts in neurology, physiology, and engineering to advance current clinical practice with data\-driven tools.


The successful candidate will serve as a primary data manager for multiple clinical studies, ensuring data integrity, regulatory compliance, and efficient data flow from collection </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer - AI, Building Design - kp reddy</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=30cf3c854ab272eb</link>
        <description>**About the Job**
=================


Here, we partner with forward\-thinking organizations in the AEC (Architecture, Engineering, and Construction) industry to push the boundaries of how the built environment is designed and delivered. As the premier full\-service management advisory firm exclusively focused on the built world, we combine domain expertise with leading\-edge technology strategy to solve real problems at scale.


We are seeking a Senior AI Engineer to lead the development of automated building design systems and advance the state\-of\-the\-art in AI/ML applications for the built environment. You'll architect and implement generative design algorithms, computer vision systems, and optimization models that fundamentally transform how buildings are


conceived, designed, and validated. This role sits at the intersection of deep learning, computational geometry, and architectural design, creating AI systems that augment human creativity while respecting engineering constrai</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer - AI, Building Design - kp reddy</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e50a761ac02df3ba</link>
        <description>**About the Job**
=================


Here, we partner with forward\-thinking organizations in the AEC (Architecture, Engineering, and Construction) industry to push the boundaries of how the built environment is designed and delivered. As the premier full\-service management advisory firm exclusively focused on the built world, we combine domain expertise with leading\-edge technology strategy to solve real problems at scale.


We are seeking a Senior AI Engineer to lead the development of automated building design systems and advance the state\-of\-the\-art in AI/ML applications for the built environment. You'll architect and implement generative design algorithms, computer vision systems, and optimization models that fundamentally transform how buildings are


conceived, designed, and validated. This role sits at the intersection of deep learning, computational geometry, and architectural design, creating AI systems that augment human creativity while respecting engineering constrai</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, Research, gTrade - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8dcf03b919570a88</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 3 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a PhD degree.
* 1 year of experience managing investigative projects.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 5 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or a PhD degree.

**About the job**
-----------------


Our team is responsible for real\-time bidding on behalf of Google Ads advertisers (i.e. GDA and AC). Our optimization modules oversee the transaction of \~20B ARR of ad inventory across web and app display publishers. We optimize bidding across web and app on several exchanges running different types of auctions.


As a Data Scien</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Applied AI - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9568bd1760d0d86f</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year
  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Kirkland, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Statistics, Mathematics, Data Science, Engineering, Physics, Economics, or a related quantitative field.
* 8 years of experienc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Internship AI Science Lab Research - Samsung Electronics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b3bbc009753ca7f2</link>
        <description>Samsung SDS is a global IT services and solutions leader that helps enterprises accelerate digital transformation. Combining deep industry expertise with advanced technologies — including cloud, AI, data analytics, and secure enterprise platforms — Samsung SDS America, the North America subsidiary, designs and delivers scalable, outcome\-driven solutions that improve operational efficiency, reduce risk, and unlock new business value across finance, manufacturing, retail, and public sectors.

**Why Join Samsung SDS America?**  

Becoming part of our team means being at the forefront of innovation. You’ll collaborate with talented individuals—thought leaders, visionaries, and problem solvers—who are passionate about shaping the future of technology.


Here, your ideas matter. Whether you’re just starting out or a seasoned professional, you’ll find endless opportunities to grow and make a lasting impact. We foster a culture of collaboration, learning, and creativity, offering you the tool</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Head of Applied AI, Google Public Sector - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c778b5693aa87b77</link>
        <description>**Must be a US Citizen to meet customer and compliance requirements, including potential access to classified information.**  

  

The application window will be open until at least March 02, 2026\. This opportunity will remain online based on business needs which may be before or after the specified date.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Reston, VA, USA; Austin, TX, USA; Boulder, CO, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Washington D.C., DC, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 10 years of experience in a technical role focused on artificial intelligence and machine learning.
* 5 years of experience in a leadership role managing customer\-facing technical teams.
* Experience in one or more of the following domains: Generative AI, Natural Language Processing (NLP), Computer Vision, or Machine Learning Operations (MLOps).
* Active or the abilit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Manager, Engineering - Enterprise AI and Automation - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=378494a85de1654f</link>
        <description>As a Senior Engineering Manager for Agentic Systems \&amp; Platform Architecture, you will lead the strategy and execution for NVIDIA’s agentic developer platform—deeply understanding how teams across the company build, evaluate, and improve autonomous agents, and turning those evolving patterns into scalable platform capabilities. You will identify gaps and friction, drive rapid proof\-of\-concepts on emerging agent constructs and ecosystem tools, and operationalize the best approaches into reusable building blocks, integrations, and governance mechanisms that accelerate developer productivity and agent quality. If you’re passionate about staying at the forefront of agent architectures and turning experimentation into real business impact, this role offers a chance to build a platform. This platform helps teams safely ship more autonomous systems at NVIDIA scale.
What you will be doing:* Track and deeply understand evolving agent development patterns across NVIDIA and the broader ecosyste</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, Perception Data - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=80f77d2e6b64e66a</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4325


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Perception Data team at Waymo is responsible for the overarching strategy and technical steering of all data used to train and evaluate the Waymo Driver’s perception </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-23</postDate>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
