<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>Indeed Python Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>Scraped Indeed jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Engineer, Global E-commerce - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d5da820e8618ee64</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Research Engineer, Global E\-commerce
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A177957
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

The e\-commerce industry has seen tremendous growth in recent years and has become a hotly contested space amongst leading internet companies. With millions of loyal users globally, we believe TikTok is an ideal platform to deliver a brand new and better e\-commerce experience to our users.
  
  

Our AI Innovation team is dedicated to building next\-generation e\-commerce experiences powered by AIGC and agentic shopping systems. We explore how AI\-generated content and intelligent agents can meaningfully enhance user experiences and reshape the way people discover, evaluate, and purchase products.
  
  

**Responsibilities:**  

* Develop and optimize AIGC video generation models, with a focus on multimodal post\-training for e\-commerce short\-video scenarios.
* Design and implement p</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Infrastructure Engineer – Distributed AI Systems - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1e7a1b91b42fe800</link>
        <description>Job Description

We are seeking a highly experienced infrastructure engineer (**phD Only**) to design and maintain large\-scale distributed systems that support machine learning workloads, high\-throughput data pipelines, and real\-time model serving.

This role involves building robust backend services, optimizing GPU resource orchestration, and implementing advanced system monitoring to ensure low\-latency and highly reliable AI infrastructure.

The ideal candidate is comfortable working at the intersection of **distributed systems, ML infrastructure, and performance engineering**, and has strong experience with large\-scale production environments.

Responsibilities

* Design and implement high\-performance backend services supporting AI model training and inference pipelines
* Develop distributed systems capable of handling multi\-petabyte datasets and high\-throughput data processing
* Optimize GPU cluster scheduling, memory utilization, and workload orchestration
* Build internal</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>SAP iXp Intern - AI Machine Learning - SAP</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=90785d4b0ecee872</link>
        <description>**We help the world run better**  

At SAP, we keep it simple: you bring your best to us, and we'll bring out the best in you. We're builders touching over 20 industries and 80% of global commerce, and we need your unique talents to help shape what's next. The work is challenging – but it matters. You'll find a place where you can be yourself, prioritize your wellbeing, and truly belong. What's in it for you? Constant learning, skill growth, great benefits, and a team that wants you to grow and succeed. **What you’ll build**


The SAP Internship Experience Program is SAP’s global, strategic, paid internship program that provides university students with opportunities to find purpose in their careers. This is more than an internship, it’s the foundation for a career built on connection, creativity, and impact.


Position title: SAP iXp Intern \- AI Machine Learning


Location: Palo Alto, CA (in\-person)


Expected start date: June 2026


Contract Duration: 6 months (extendable)


Workin</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer - LLM - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e88d7644687e863d</link>
        <description>Imagine what you could do here. At Apple, new ideas have a way of becoming extraordinary products, services, and customer experiences very quickly. Bring passion and dedication to your job and there's no telling what you could accomplish. The people here at Apple don’t just create products \- they create the kind of wonder that’s revolutionized entire industries. It’s the diversity of those people and their ideas that inspires the innovation that runs through everything we do, from amazing technology to industry\-leading environmental efforts.  

  

Join Apple, and help us leave the world better than we found it.  

  

**Description**  

  

We are seeking a highly capable and dynamic Machine Learning Engineer to work cross\-functional in building out a GenAI system in support of Beats and Apple Audio products. The ideal candidate thrives in ambiguity, is exceptionally organized, relentlessly detail\-oriented, and an exceptional communicator at all levels of the organization.  

  

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Staff ML Engineer, Apple Cloud AI Platform - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=95e091c5b2ce2077</link>
        <description>Apple Cloud AI Platform powers the machine learning, AI, and data systems that enable intelligent experiences across Apple consumer products. We are looking for a Software Engineer who is excited to work directly with Apple product teams and translate real\-world AI needs into production\-ready solutions. You will operate at the intersection of full\-stack engineering, data and ML platforms, backend systems and applied AI, using customer requirements to build end\-to\-end solutions and workflows as part of our platform offerings. This role is ideal for engineers who are highly collaborative, proactive, adaptable, and capable of turning ambiguous customer requests into working AI\-powered solutions at scale.  

  

**Description**  

  

In this role you will partner directly with internal customers to understand their use cases, evaluate technical requirements, and build AI\-driven systems and solutions that leverage Apple Cloud AI Platform capabilities. You will work across the stack,</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Applied Sensing &amp; Health - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2db726006e6e44d7</link>
        <description>Are you a seasoned engineer passionate about transforming cutting\-edge ML researchinto production systems that improve lives? The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team is revolutionizing health and fitness technology, empowering millions to live healthier, more active lives. We develop sophisticated machine learning algorithms and sensor fusion systems that track human motion, turning raw data into meaningful, actionable insights for Apple users worldwide.  

  

Join a team of world\-class experts dedicated to applied ML in human movement and health. Here, you'll bridge the gap between research and production\-translating novel ML approaches into robust, high\-performance systems that delight and inspire millions of Apple customers every day. This is a unique opportunity to blend ML expertise withsystems engineering in service of a mission that truly matters.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team delivers critical Health and Fitness features for Apple Watch, iPhon</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Battery - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=14fcb3a9e5027ef1</link>
        <description>Do you have a passion for invention and self\-challenge? Do you thrive on pushing the  

  

limits of what’s considered feasible? As part of our Battery Engineering group, you’ll  

  

help craft creative battery solutions that deliver more energy in smaller spaces than  

  

ever before! We work across subject areas to transform improved hardware elements  

  

into a single, integrated design. Join us, and you’ll help us innovate new battery  

  

technologies that continually outperform the previous iterations. By collaborating with  

  

other product development groups across Apple, we push the industry boundaries of  

  

what batteries can do and improve the product experience for our customers across the  

  

world! This position works within a multi\-functional team supporting the entire Battery  

  

Department to identify trends, mine data, and help the battery team improve  

  

performance.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Battery Analytics team transforms data</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Embedded Software Manager - CommScope</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a1fd18f839a38be</link>
        <description>In our ‘always on’ world, we believe it’s essential to have a genuine connection with the work you do.

  

RUCKUS Networks, a CommScope BU, specializes in delivering high\-performance networking solutions while focusing on creating purpose\-driven networks that perform exceptionally well in challenging environments. RUCKUS Networks leverages advanced technologies like Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) to enhance network performance and reduce total cost of ownership.

  

The Embedded Software Engineering Manager will lead and mentor a team of engineers in the development of next\-generation WiFi Access Point solutions. This position requires a strong background in embedded systems, wireless and wired networking, and a proven track record of managing and delivering complex software projects. An experienced leader with a strong technical background in embedded systems, 802\.11 wireless networking, and SoC platforms who thrives in a fast\-paced, collaborative enviro</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - AI/ML Platform - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8b919e29e9ec8294</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO AI platform and Infrastructure team is seeking an exceptional Senior ML Platform Engineer to build and scale our machine learning infrastructure with a focus on Large Language Models (LLMs) and AI applications. This role combines deep technical expertise in cloud platforms, container orchestration, and ML operations with strong leadership and mentoring capabilities. You will be responsible for designing, implem</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Researcher - kiddom</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6d7006cf9ed1f5c5</link>
        <description>**About Kiddom**  

Kiddom is a groundbreaking educational platform that promotes student equity and growth by uniting high\-quality instructional materials with dynamic digital learning. Through unparalleled curriculum management functionality, Kiddom empowers schools and districts to take ownership of their curriculum – resulting in learning experiences tailored to meet the unique needs and goals of local communities. Kiddom’s high\-quality curriculum is layered with robust teacher and leader data insights to drive the continuous improvement of instructional decisions, school/district programming, and professional learning.  

Join our mission to revolutionize K\-12 education at the intersection of cutting\-edge AI and impactful learning outcomes. As a **Machine Learning Researcher**, you will play a pivotal role in pushing the boundaries of what’s possible with AI in education. Your work will assist teachers by personalizing their teaching experience and improving student outcomes. </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=77beaf29cf135608</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Artificial Intelligence and Business Development Specialist Leader - SFL Scientific - Deloitte</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d58b4d5ca2a71718</link>
        <description>Our Deloitte Strategy \&amp; Transactions team helps guide clients through their most critical moments and transformational initiatives. From strategy to execution, this team delivers integrated, end\-to\-end support and advisory services covering valuation modeling, cost optimization, restructuring, business design and transformation, infrastructure and real estate, mergers and acquisitions (M\&amp;A), and sustainability. Work alongside clients every step of the way, helping them navigate new challenges, avoid financial pitfalls, and provide practical solutions at every stage of their journey\-before, during, and after any major transformational projects or transactions.  

  

SFL Scientific, a Deloitte Business, is a U.S. based, data science consulting firm specializing in building mission\-specific, artificial intelligence (AI) technologies to support and transform our partners and clients. Our scientists and engineers' partner with Deloitte to deliver custom AI capabilities.  

  

With o</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist , Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=064d50d435fa4e88</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist - Foundation Model, Industrial Robotics Group - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b967e0f5c1cf8a19</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Industrial Robotics Group is seeking exceptional talent to help develop the next generation of advanced robotics systems that will transform automation at Amazon's scale. We're building revolutionary robotic systems that combine innovative AI, sophisticated control systems, and advanced mechanical design to create adaptable automation solutions capable of working safely alongside humans in dynamic environments. This is a unique opportunity to shape the future of robotics and automation at unprecedented scale, working with world\-class teams pushing the boundaries of what's possible in robotic manipulation, locomotion, and human\-robot interaction. This role presents an opportunity to shape the future of robotics through innovative applications of deep learning and large language models.  

  

We leverage advanced robotics, machine learning, and artificial intelligence to solve complex operational challenges at unprecedented scale. Our fleet of robots </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>MLA IP Design Verification Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b4323bc9a66bd519</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low\-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world.  

  

We are seeking an experienced Design Verification Engineers to build the next generation of our cloud server platforms. Our success depends on our world\-class infrastructure; we’re handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies.  

  

As a member of the Cloud\-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team you’ll be responsible for the design and validation of machine learning hardware in our data centers.  

  

Some of your responsibilities will include verifying/validating that our hardware and software solutions achieve their desired functionality, developing and executing multi\-faceted verification/validation plans, and measuring the teams progress towards our ambitious customer metrics.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Some of your r</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal. Tech Product Manager - Neuron Runtime and Cloud ML Infrastructure, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=64d46b56c7148cc9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Trainium is deployed at scale, with millions of chips in production, and has been used for training and inference of frontier models. AWS Neuron is the software stack for Trainium, enabling customers to run deep learning and generative AI workloads with optimal performance and cost efficiency.  

  

AWS Neuron is hiring a Technical Product Manager to work backward from Trainium customers and drive the developer experience for running high\-performance ML workloads at scale on AWS Trainium, from getting started with Neuron Deep Learning Containers, AMIs, and AWS services to operating at scale through orchestration, resiliency, and observability.  

  

You will drive the product strategy for how developers interact with Trainium through container ecosystems, resource management platforms, and AWS services. This includes Neuron integration with orchestration tools (SLURM, Kubernetes), AWS services (EKS, SageMaker), Neuron Deep Learning Containers an</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer Internship - Military Veteran - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5913e2fccc44feae</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Applications will be accepted on an ongoing basis  

  

This opportunity is for U.S. citizens who have served in the U.S. Armed Forces including Reserves, National Guard, and service member spouses.
  

  

* Please list your service in your resume to be considered for this position.

  

Do you want to solve real customer problems through innovative technology? Do you enjoy working on scalable services in a collaborative team environment? Do you want to see your code directly impact millions of customers worldwide?  

  

At Amazon, we hire the best minds in technology to innovate and build on behalf of our customers. Customer obsession is part of our company DNA, which has made us one of the world's most beloved brands.  

  

Our SDE interns use modern technology to solve complex problems while seeing their work's impact first\-hand. The challenges SDE interns solve at Amazon are meaningful and influence millions of customers,</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer Internship - Military Veteran - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d97fe98915912a0b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Applications will be accepted on an ongoing basis  

  

This opportunity is for U.S. citizens who have served in the U.S. Armed Forces including Reserves, National Guard, and service member spouses.
  

  

* Please list your service in your resume to be considered for this position.

  

Do you want to solve real customer problems through innovative technology? Do you enjoy working on scalable services in a collaborative team environment? Do you want to see your code directly impact millions of customers worldwide?  

  

At Amazon, we hire the best minds in technology to innovate and build on behalf of our customers. Customer obsession is part of our company DNA, which has made us one of the world's most beloved brands.  

  

Our SDE interns use modern technology to solve complex problems while seeing their work's impact first\-hand. The challenges SDE interns solve at Amazon are meaningful and influence millions of customers,</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Science Manager, Agentic AI Ads, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6b552335d35c2243</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) is at the heart of Amazon Advertising, helping millions of advertisers—from small businesses to global brands—connect with customers at the moments that matter most. Our advertising solutions enable sellers, vendors, and brand owners to grow their businesses by reaching shoppers with relevant, engaging ads across Amazon's store and beyond. We're obsessed with delivering measurable results for advertisers while creating a delightful shopping experience for customers.  

  

Are you interested in defining the science behind the future of advertising? Sponsored Products and Brands science teams are pioneering breakthrough agentic AI systems—pushing the boundaries of large language models, autonomous reasoning, planning, and decision\-making to build intelligent agents that fundamentally transform how advertisers succeed on Amazon.  

  

As an SPB applied science leader, you'll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Economist, Stores Economics and Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=22b0e68d026c6435</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


This role will contribute to developing the Economics and Science products and services in the Fee domain, with specialization in supply chain systems and fees. Through the lens of economics, you will develop causal links for how Amazon, Sellers and Customers interact. You will be a key and senior scientist, advising Amazon leaders how to price our services. You will work on developing frameworks and scalable, repeatable models supporting optimal pricing and policy in the two\-sided marketplace that is central to Amazon's business. The pricing for Amazon services is complex. You will partner with science and technology teams across Amazon including Advertising, Supply Chain, Operations, Prime, Consumer Pricing, and Finance.  

  

We are looking for an experienced Economist to improve our understanding of seller Economics, enhance our ability to estimate the causal impact of fees, and work with partner teams to design pricing policy changes. In this ro</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Manager, Sponsored Products and Brands Off-Search - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b42c24580c8afcb3</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through innovative generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.
  

  

Key job responsibilities  

This Software Development Manager role will be c</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Amazon Transportation - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b50cf1145ff458d9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon’s Middle Mile Planning Research and Optimization Science group (mmPROS) is looking for a Senior Applied Scientist specializing in design and evaluation of algorithms for predictive modeling and optimization applied to large\-scale transportation planning systems. This includes the development of novel machine learning and artificial intelligence techniques to improve on marketplace optimization solutions.  

  

The Middle Mile Science group is charged with developing an evolving suite of optimization tools to facilitate the design of efficient air and ground transport networks, optimize the flow of packages within the network to efficiently align network capacity and shipment demand, set prices, and effectively utilize scarce resources, such as aircraft and trucks. The scale of Amazon’s fulfillment operations challenges us to design, build and operate robust transportation networks that minimize the overall operational cost while meeting all cu</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, WW Sustainability - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=31d953bdb7f8b788</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join us at the Amazon's sustainability initiatives to work on environmental and social advancements to support Amazon's long term worldwide sustainability strategy. At Amazon, we're working to be the most customer\-centric company on earth. To get there, we need exceptionally talented, bright, and driven people.  

  

The Worldwide Sustainability (WWS) organization capitalizes on Amazon’s scale and speed to build a more resilient and sustainable company. We manage our social and environmental impacts globally, and drive solutions that enable our customers, businesses, and the world to become more sustainable.  

  

Sustainability Science and Innovation (SSI) is a multi\-disciplinary team within WW Sustainability combining science, analytics, economics, statistics, machine learning, product development, and engineering expertise. We use data across the sustainability imperatives (carbon, water, waste, biodiversity, environmental risk and more) and the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Security Software Development Engineer , Abuse Prevention, Devices and Services Trust and Safety - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5f673d90518a3b6a</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


We are open to hiring candidates to work out of one of the following locations:  

  

Austin, TX, USA \| Sunnyvale, CA, USA  

  

Amazon Lab126 is an inventive research and development company that designs and engineers high\-profile consumer electronics. Lab126 began in 2004 as a subsidiary of Amazon.com, Inc., originally creating the best\-selling Kindle family of products. Since then, we have produced devices like Fire tablets, Fire TV, Dash Button, Amazon Echo and Alexa. What will you help us create?
  

  

Are you passionate about security and eager to make a real impact? Join us as a Software Development Engineer and play a critical role in safeguarding millions of Amazon customers and their favorite devices, including Echo, Fire TV, Tablets, and more.  

  

In this role, you will design and implement backend security features that protect our devices and stay ahead of emerging threats. You will also have the opportunity to harness the power </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Product Manager, Content Platform Operations &amp; Publishing - Netflix</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cc5140ab6da9c9d7</link>
        <description>At Netflix, our mission is to entertain the world. Together, we are writing the next episode \- pushing the boundaries of storytelling, global fandom and making the unimaginable a reality. We are a dream team obsessed with the uncomfortable excitement of discovering what happens when you merge creativity, intuition and cutting\-edge technology. Come be a part of what’s next.


**Location**

Los Gatos, CA, Los Angeles, CA, or Remote (within the US). Regular travel to Los Gatos and Los Angeles is required.


**The Team**

The Content Platform Operations \&amp; Publishing (CPOP) team sits at the intersection of AI and machine learning, the consumer experience and the Netflix Studio. We are an integral part of making the Netflix experience feel personal and relevant by developing innovative approaches to how we promote, localize, and distribute our content. Our products impact both our members and the content creators, linguists, editors and executives who make our shows and films possible.


</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Embedded Software Engineer, Annapurna ML Software - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2cdb87afda207259</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago\- even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challenges that have never been seen before, and deliver results that help our customers change the world.  

  

In Annapurna Labs we are at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design not just in Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the industry. Our Annapurna MLA Software team is looking for candidates interested in diving deep into the different hardware technologies that power our Machine Learning servers and develop the software and firmware to drive, support and sustain these technologies as they evolve though concept and manufacturing, and finally take their place in our rapidly expanding fleet of bleeding edge Machine Learning products our customers demand.  

  

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products Off-Search Sourcing - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e606d10c3f7ff2f9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

The Off\-Search team within Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) is f</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Economist, People Experience and Technology Central Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=539aec6d3023636a</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The People eXperience and Technology Central Science (PXTCS) team uses economics, behavioral science, statistics, and machine learning to proactively identify mechanisms and process improvements which simultaneously improve Amazon and the lives, wellbeing, and the value of work to Amazonians. PXTCS is an interdisciplinary team that combines the talents of science and engineering to develop and deliver solutions that measurably achieve this goal.  

  

PXTCS is looking for an economist who can apply economic methods to address business problems. The ideal candidate will work with engineers and computer scientists to estimate models and algorithms on large scale data, design pilots and measure impact, and transform successful prototypes into improved policies and programs at scale. PXTCS is looking for creative thinkers who can combine a strong technical economic toolbox with a desire to learn from other disciplines, and who know how to execute and deli</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=244111b21d6a8c8e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is responsible for developing diverse datasets to train and evaluate the Amazon AI models. We are looking for Language Engineers to join our science and engineering team to support the development of complex, multimodal datasets, using a range of approaches including synthetic data generation, model\-supported data generation, and human\-in\-the\-loop data collections.
  

  

You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in evaluating and training AI models. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are best in class.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design complex data collections with human participants in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coor</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e133c78752afc8b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is looking for a Language Engineer with experience in dataset construction, linguistic annotation, dialog/semantic schemas, and automatic processing of large datasets. You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in natural language processing and machine learning. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are aligned with human policies and preferences.
  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Specifically, the Language Engineer will:
  

* Design data collection/creation tasks in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coordination of data collection efforts (including planning, scheduling, and reporting), and be responsible for the final deliverables
* Analy</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>HSIO Validation Engineer, Annapurna Labs Machine Learning Acceleration - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5175558ce229097d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


As an HSIO Validation Engineer, you will be responsible for ensuring the correct operation, bring\-up, and scalability of high\-speed I/O including PCIe, HBM, UCIe, and other protocols used in our custom machine learning chips. You will work with architecture, IP owners, DV, software, and signal integrity teams to productize the latest high\-speed I/O technology in both pre\-silicon and post\-silicon.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Gain a deep understanding of SoC architecture.
* Work with architecture, IP owners, DV, software, and signal integrity teams to verify and integrate high\-speed I/O functionality and performance.
* Execute feature enablement and validation test cases for high\-speed interfaces.
* Develop and maintain software\-based validation tests and automation frameworks for both pre\-silicon and post\-silicon environments.
* Debug and drive root\-cause analysis for device\-related issues; document failure analysis and report test </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c6fbf562f453398c</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is responsible for developing diverse datasets to train and evaluate the Amazon AI models. We are looking for Language Engineers to join our science and engineering team to support the development of complex, multimodal datasets, using a range of approaches including synthetic data generation, model\-supported data generation, and human\-in\-the\-loop data collections.
  

  

You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in evaluating and training AI models. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are best in class.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design complex data collections with human participants in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coor</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a9cda19ec29e0bf2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and exclusive access to coverage of live sports. All customers regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can access programming from subscriptions such as Apple TV, Peacock Premium Plus, HBO Max, FOX One, Crunchyroll and MGM\+, as well as more than 900 free ad\-support (FAST) Channels, rent or buy titles, and enjoy even more content for free with ads.
  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end owner</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer, Amazon Demand Side Platform - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8ada698cf77372d8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Imagine having the opportunity to directly shape the experiences of millions of Amazon customers every day. As part of our Advertising team, you'll do just that \- designing, building, and maintaining the large\-scale systems that power Amazon's advertising offerings.  

  

This is no ordinary software engineering role. You'll be tackling complex, industry\-defining challenges, leveraging the right technologies to create reliable, high\-performance solutions from the ground up for the entire Ad industry. From decomposing ambiguous problems into clear, straight\-forward implementations to collaborating with product managers on new feature ideas, every day will bring novel obstacles to overcome.  

  

The ideal candidate has a proven track record of delivering new products and features, with a deep understanding of computer science fundamentals, experience building large\-scale distributed systems and machine learning infrastructure. You take initiativ</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bf80327d16050ee9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Safety ML - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b233672bacbbebf7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


If you are interested in this position, please apply on Twitch's Career site https://www.twitch.tv/jobs/en/  

  

About Us:  

  

Twitch is the world’s biggest live streaming service, with global communities built around gaming, entertainment, music, sports, cooking, and more. It is where thousands of communities come together for whatever, every day.  

  

We’re about community, inside and out. You’ll find coworkers who are eager to team up, collaborate, and smash (or elegantly solve) problems together. We’re on a quest to empower live communities, so if this sounds good to you, see what we’re up to on LinkedIn and X, and discover the projects we’re solving on our Blog. Be sure to explore our Interviewing Guide to learn how to ace our interview process.  

  

About the Role  

  

We are looking for applied scientists to solve challenging and open\-ended problems in the domain of user and content safety. As an applied scientist on Twitch's Communi</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Measurement, AdTech and Data Science , Performance Measurement - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d0ded3809e5d7523</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Ads Measurement Science team within Amazon Ads' Measurement, AdTech, and Data Science (MADS) organization
  

serves a centralized role developing solutions for a multitude of performance measurement products to measure the full impact of advertiser spend, including both online and offline sales impacts across all timeframes. It delivers actionable insights for advertisers to optimize media portfolios. We also build science solutions for AI and AI\-powered tools that unlock new insights and automate high\-effort customer workflows for ad measurement, such as custom query and report generation based on natural language user requests. We leverage new technologies including Generative AI, machine learning, causal inference, natural Language Processing (NLP), and Computer Vision (CV) to drive these innovations.  

  

A key focus of this role is Modeled Attribution, Amazon's privacy\-compliant measurement system serving millions of advertisers and proc</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Measurement, AdTech and Data Science (NYC/Seattle/Palo Alto), Performance Measurement - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0fef6b3169640097</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Ads Measurement Science team within Amazon Ads' Measurement, AdTech, and Data Science (MADS) organization
  

serves a centralized role developing solutions for a multitude of performance measurement products to measure the full impact of advertiser spend, including both online and offline sales impacts across all timeframes. It delivers actionable insights for advertisers to optimize media portfolios. We also build science solutions for AI and AI\-powered tools that unlock new insights and automate high\-effort customer workflows for ad measurement, such as custom query and report generation based on natural language user requests. We leverage new technologies including Generative AI, machine learning, causal inference, natural Language Processing (NLP), and Computer Vision (CV) to drive these innovations.  

  

A key focus of this role is Modeled Attribution, Amazon's privacy\-compliant measurement system serving millions of advertisers and proc</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal ProServe Cloud Architect - Connect and Conversational AI, Amazon Connect Center of Delivery Excellence - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9c84922d34b05bec</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Feb 26, 2026  

  

The Amazon Web Services Professional Services (ProServe) team is seeking an experienced ProServe Cloud Architect (PCA) to join our team at Amazon Web Services (AWS). In this role, you'll work closely with customers to understand their technical requirements and business objectives, designing and implementing tailored cloud solutions. You'll be a key player in the pre\-sales process, providing technical expertise and guidance throughout the customer's cloud journey.  

  

In this role, you'll be responsible for creating and leading the solution design to address customer business outcomes (CBO). Operating as the conduit between ProServe Account Executives and our Global Delivery Teams, you'll ensure proposed solutions are realistic, achievable, and optimize ProServe and/or our partners to maximize CBOs. As a PCA you are a trusted advisor to our customers, providing guidance on industry trends, emerging technolo</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal ProServe Cloud Architect - Connect and Conversational AI, Amazon Connect Center of Delivery Excellence - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2c26070ef2f84069</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Feb 26, 2026  

  

The Amazon Web Services Professional Services (ProServe) team is seeking an experienced ProServe Cloud Architect (PCA) to join our team at Amazon Web Services (AWS). In this role, you'll work closely with customers to understand their technical requirements and business objectives, designing and implementing tailored cloud solutions. You'll be a key player in the pre\-sales process, providing technical expertise and guidance throughout the customer's cloud journey.  

  

In this role, you'll be responsible for creating and leading the solution design to address customer business outcomes (CBO). Operating as the conduit between ProServe Account Executives and our Global Delivery Teams, you'll ensure proposed solutions are realistic, achievable, and optimize ProServe and/or our partners to maximize CBOs. As a PCA you are a trusted advisor to our customers, providing guidance on industry trends, emerging technolo</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, LLM Code Agents, Kiro Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e39fc9dbc84125f2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is assembling an elite team of world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next generation of AI\-driven development tools. Join the Amazon Kiro LLM\-Training team and help create groundbreaking generative AI technologies including Kiro IDE and Amazon Q Developer that are transforming the software development landscape.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As a key member of our team, you'll be at the forefront of innovation, where cutting\-edge research meets real\-world application:  

* Push the boundaries of reinforcement learning and post\-training methodologies for large language models specialized in code intelligence
* Invent and implement state\-of\-the\-art machine learning solutions that operate at unprecedented Amazon scale
* Deploy revolutionary products that directly impact the daily workflows of millions of developers worldwide
* Break new ground in AI and machine learning, challenging what's possible in </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2ed99a7566e06fc8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Alexa Smart Home - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=26f7d6f3b8b5b46e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Smart Home team is focused on making Alexa\+ the user interface for the future home. From the simplest voice commands (turn on the lights, turn down the heat) to use cases spanning home security, home entertainment, and the home environment, we are evolving Alexa\+ into intelligent, indispensable companion that automates daily routines, simplifies interaction with appliances and electronics, and alerts when something unusual is detected. You will be part of a team delivering features that are highly anticipated by media and well received by our customers.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an Applied Scientist, you will work with other scientists and software developers to design and build the next generation of Smart Home voice and ambient controls using the latest Large Language Models and ML methods. And, you will have the satisfaction of working on a product your friends and family can relate to, and want to use every day.  

  

About the t</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. SoC Virtual Platform Modeling Engineer, Annapurna Labs Machine Learning Accelerators, AWS - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ddd7bd31d1b8fd76</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Custom SoCs (System on Chips) are the brains behind AWS’s Machine Learning servers. Our team builds C\+\+ \&amp; SystemC functional models of these custom\-designed accelerator SoCs for use by AWS internal teams to significantly left\-shift development. We’re looking for a Senior SoC Virtual Platform Modeling Engineer to join the team and deliver new functional models, infrastructure, and tooling for our customers.  

  

As part of the ML accelerator modeling team, you will:  

  

* Develop and own SoC models end\-to\-end, including model architecture, integration with other model or infrastructure components, testing, and debug
* Work closely with architecture, RTL design, design verification, emulation, and software teams to build, debug, and deploy your models
* Innovate on the tooling you provide to customers, making it easier for them to use our SoC models
* Drive model and modeling infrastructure performance improvements to help our models scale
* </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Research Scientist Intern, Quantum Algorithms, Center for Quantum Computing - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e732a9566fce8918</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Do you enjoy solving challenging problems and driving innovations in research?
  

  

As a Research Science intern with the Quantum Algorithms Team at CQC, you will work alongside global experts to develop novel quantum algorithms, evaluate prospective applications of fault\-tolerant quantum computers, and strengthen the long\-term value proposition of quantum computing.  

  

A strong candidate will have experience applying methods of mathematical and numerical analysis to assess the performance of quantum algorithms and establish their advantage over classical algorithms.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

We are particularly interested in candidates with expertise in any of the following subareas related to quantum algorithms: quantum chemistry, many\-body physics, quantum machine learning, cryptography, optimization theory, quantum complexity theory, quantum error correction \&amp; fault tolerance, quantum sensing, and scientific computing, among oth</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Device Driver Engineering Manager, Annapurna Labs Machine Learning Acceleration, AWS - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c45fc2c2a328c86</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Custom silicon chips live at the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers, and this team builds the backend software that runs these servers. We’re looking for someone to lead our SoC (System on Chip) device\-driver / HAL (Hardware Abstraction Layer) software team. You'll help us deliver at scale as we build the next generation of SoC software. This is a hands\-on, in\-the\-trenches leadership position, where you’ll manage systems, debug issues, and write code alongside your team.  

  

As the Manager for SoC driver software, you will:
  

* Manage a team of 6 developers
* Work with hardware designers to write drivers for newly developed SoC IPs
* Work with system software teams to solve SoC and system\-level architectural issues, drive debug, and innovate on cross\-functional solutions
* Refactor and maintain existing codebases throughout the device lifecycle
* Continuously test and deploy your software stack to multiple internal customers
* Innovate on</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Manufacturing Engineer, Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=65a3030d5ae225f0</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Leading the manufacturing of AI Servers and Systems based on Trainium chips across cross\-geographical ODMs and CMs. As part of the Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability Team in Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider.  

  

Within Annapurna Labs team is building the next generation cloud server infrastructure. Our success depends on delivering world\-class server infrastructure; we're handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies. Our servers include accelerators such as Trainium and Inferentia which are machine learning products designed to deliver high performance at low cost.
  

  

The Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability Team is part of Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider. We are seeking a talented and motivated Manufact</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=029e08146a9b1ca0</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Systems Software Manager, Annapurna Labs Machine Learning Acceleration, AWS - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ce83a7a91531dc95</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Trainium servers are complex supercomputers, with both hardware and software built entirely in\-house from the ground\-up. We’re looking for someone to lead our SoC (System on a Chip) Hardware Abstraction Layer (HAL) team. You’ll be responsible for directing the team both technically and managerially, getting into the details of both. You’ll dig in to understand our custom SoCs and build effective software that abstracts out the details for higher layers of the software stack.  

  

You’ll work closely with chip architects, designers, verification engineers, and fellow software engineers to shape our next\-generation of Machine Learning acceleration. You’ll effectively manage, coach, and direct your team to execute on this vision alongside you. This is a hands\-on, in\-the\-trenches leadership position, where you’ll manage systems, debug issues, and write code alongside your team.  

  

As the SoC HAL Manager, you will:  

* Manage and develop a </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. ASIC Design Engineer, Cloud-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration - Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=aa31bd7f40729e37</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Utility Computing (UC)  

AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products and Brands, Off-Search - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1cdfb13a911d4872</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is transforming advertising through generative AI technologies. We help millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. Our team combines human creativity with artificial intelligence to reinvent the entire advertising lifecycle—from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights.  

  

We develop responsible AI technologies that balance advertiser needs, enhance shopping experiences, and strengthen the marketplace. Our team values innovation and tackles complex challenges that push the boundaries of what's possible with AI.  

  

Join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

This role will redesign how ads create personalized, relevant shopping experiences with customer value at the forefront. Key responsibilities include:  

  

* Design and develop solutions using GenAI, deep learnin</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Graviton Software, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=19ee08b20245c723</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the AWS Graviton Software team as a Software Engineer focused on system performance. You will enhance the performance of the Graviton processor and help decide the features of future Graviton generations. Your role involves developing software for performance analysis and building services and improving performance of open source software and helping customers with their Graviton migration. This position offers exposure to diverse technologies including hypervisor, firmware, operating systems, cloud services, machine learning, databases, and visualization tools. While expertise in all these areas isn't required at the start, you'll have the opportunity to learn from experts as you help build innovative cloud services that advance AWS Graviton's performance.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As a Graviton Software Developer, you will have the opportunity to learn and contribute on a variety of different projects:  

  

* Develop services to analy</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=74fe2d61d7fe8d87</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Distributed SQL - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=618f579aa0e8ee8b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Aurora DSQL is a serverless, distributed SQL database with virtually unlimited scale, highest availability, and zero infrastructure management. Aurora DSQL provides active\-active high availability, providing strong data consistency designed for 99\.99% single\-Region and 99\.999% multi\-Region availability. Aurora DSQL automatically manages and scales system resources, so you don't have to worry about maintenance downtime and provisioning, patching, or upgrading infrastructure.  

  

As a Senior Applied Scientist, you will be expected to lead research and development in advanced query optimization techniques for distributed sql services. You will innovate in the query planning and execution layer to help Aurora DSQL succeed at delivering high performance for complex OLTP workloads. You will develop novel approaches to stats collection, query planning, execution and optimization. You will drive industry leading research, publish your research a</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Power Engineer, Annapurna Labs, Machine Learning Hardware - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d3dbf4dea26f8596</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challen</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e243de15e611cb9d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is building a central pipeline of Software Development Engineer (SDE) talent for anticipated roles in 2026\. This requisition supports hiring across all AWS SDE positions, from fungible SDE roles to specialized engineering positions in areas including:  

  

* Embedded Systems
* Game Development
* Compiler Engineering
* Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning
* Healthcare AI
* Infrastructure Services
* Firmware Development
* Cloud Computing
* Distributed Systems
* Security Engineering
* Video Processing and Streaming
* Content Delivery Network (CDN)


When you apply to this position, your profile will be considered for current and future SDE openings across AWS, including teams such as Twitch, AWS Elemental, and AWS CloudFront.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an AWS Software Development Engineer, you will:  

* Design, develop, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable code
* Implement complex software solutions t</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=66ffadbf1957bf07</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is building a central pipeline of Software Development Engineer (SDE) talent for anticipated roles in 2026\. This requisition supports hiring across all AWS SDE positions, from fungible SDE roles to specialized engineering positions in areas including:  

  

* Embedded Systems
* Game Development
* Compiler Engineering
* Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning
* Healthcare AI
* Infrastructure Services
* Firmware Development
* Cloud Computing
* Distributed Systems
* Security Engineering
* Video Processing and Streaming
* Content Delivery Network (CDN)


When you apply to this position, your profile will be considered for current and future SDE openings across AWS, including teams such as Twitch, AWS Elemental, and AWS CloudFront.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an AWS Software Development Engineer, you will:  

* Design, develop, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable code
* Implement complex software solutions t</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=28d55d62b86f6ff0</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is building a central pipeline of Software Development Engineer (SDE) talent for anticipated roles in 2026\. This requisition supports hiring across all AWS SDE positions, from fungible SDE roles to specialized engineering positions in areas including:  

  

* Embedded Systems
* Game Development
* Compiler Engineering
* Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning
* Healthcare AI
* Infrastructure Services
* Firmware Development
* Cloud Computing
* Distributed Systems
* Security Engineering
* Video Processing and Streaming
* Content Delivery Network (CDN)


When you apply to this position, your profile will be considered for current and future SDE openings across AWS, including teams such as Twitch, AWS Elemental, and AWS CloudFront.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an AWS Software Development Engineer, you will:  

* Design, develop, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable code
* Implement complex software solutions t</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ca99b2fadcd0f078</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services (AWS) is building a central pipeline of Software Development Engineer (SDE) talent for anticipated roles in 2026\. This requisition supports hiring across all AWS SDE positions, from fungible SDE roles to specialized engineering positions in areas including:  

  

* Embedded Systems
* Game Development
* Compiler Engineering
* Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning
* Healthcare AI
* Infrastructure Services
* Firmware Development
* Cloud Computing
* Distributed Systems
* Security Engineering
* Video Processing and Streaming
* Content Delivery Network (CDN)


When you apply to this position, your profile will be considered for current and future SDE openings across AWS, including teams such as Twitch, AWS Elemental, and AWS CloudFront.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an AWS Software Development Engineer, you will:  

* Design, develop, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable code
* Implement complex software solutions t</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Delivery Foundation Model - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=afa9fd7f747b462e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next science and engineering revolution at Amazon's Delivery Foundation Model team, where you'll work alongside world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next frontier of logistics through advanced AI and foundation models.  

  

We are seeking an exceptional Applied Scientist to help develop innovative foundation models that enable delivery of billions of packages worldwide. In this role, you'll combine highly technical work with scientific leadership, ensuring the team delivers robust solutions for dynamic real\-world environments. Your team will leverage Amazon's vast data and computational resources to tackle ambitious problems across a diverse set of Amazon delivery use cases.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design and implement novel deep learning architectures combining a multitude of modalities, including image, video, and geospatial data.
* Solve computational problems to train foundation models on vast amounts of Ama</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Product Manager - Kernels, AI/ML, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b35f8eae52a67895</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Neuron is looking for an experienced Technical Product Manager to define and drive product strategy for the Neuron Kernel Interface (NKI), a compiler library enabling custom kernel development and optimization. You will be part of the AWS Neuron Product Management team, driving innovation in machine learning acceleration software. AWS Neuron is the software stack for Trainium and Inferentia, the AWS Machine Learning chips, delivering best\-in\-class ML performance in the cloud. You will lead NKI requirements working backward from customer needs, drive kernel library features definition, and drive developer experience for custom kernel development, enabling customers to successfully and independently develop and optimize ML workloads on AWS Neuron through deep understanding of compiler systems, kernel optimization, and hardware acceleration.  

  

The ideal candidate will have solid understanding of compiler technologies, computer architecture, and</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Tech Product Manager - Neuron Runtime and Cloud ML Infrastructure, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d30f58051849647c</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Trainium is deployed at scale, with millions of chips in production, and has been used for training and inference of frontier models. AWS Neuron is the software stack for Trainium, enabling customers to run deep learning and generative AI workloads with optimal performance and cost efficiency.  

  

AWS Neuron is hiring a Technical Product Manager to work backward from Trainium customers and drive the developer experience for running high\-performance ML workloads at scale on AWS Trainium, from getting started with Neuron Deep Learning Containers, AMIs, and AWS services to operating at scale through orchestration, resiliency, and observability.  

  

You will drive the product strategy for how developers interact with Trainium through container ecosystems, resource management platforms, and AWS services. This includes Neuron integration with orchestration tools (SLURM, Kubernetes), AWS services (EKS, SageMaker), Neuron Deep Learning Containers an</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=746409ad06eb8286</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is looking for a Language Engineer with experience in dataset construction, linguistic annotation, dialog/semantic schemas, and automatic processing of large datasets. You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in natural language processing and machine learning. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are aligned with human policies and preferences.
  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Specifically, the Language Engineer will:
  

* Design data collection/creation tasks in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coordination of data collection efforts (including planning, scheduling, and reporting), and be responsible for the final deliverables
* Analy</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bb3a43e7da23d32b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is responsible for developing diverse datasets to train and evaluate the Amazon AI models. We are looking for Language Engineers to join our science and engineering team to support the development of complex, multimodal datasets, using a range of approaches including synthetic data generation, model\-supported data generation, and human\-in\-the\-loop data collections.
  

  

You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in evaluating and training AI models. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are best in class.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design complex data collections with human participants in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coor</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Manager, Neuron Tools, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=05fc811c051a9142</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Neuron is the complete software stack for the AWS Inferentia and Trainium cloud\-scale machine learning accelerators and the Trn1 and Inf1 servers that use them.  

  

As the Software Development Manager for the Tools Team, you will be responsible for leading a talented team of engineers to develop and maintain high\-performance monitoring and profiling tools for machine learning applications and AI accelerators. You will oversee the design, development, and deployment of the Neuron Profiler and other Neuron Tools. The profiler plays a crucial role to internal and external customers in optimizing AI workloads across hardware platforms such as Trainium and Inferentia devices, by providing deep insights into performance bottlenecks and system behavior.  

  

In this role, you will manage the full development life cycle of the Neuron Profiler/Tools toolchain, ensuring scalability, reliability, and usability. You will collaborate with cross\-function</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Engineer - EC2 Windows OS Technologies team, EC2 Windows - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e948b9af2de16f1f</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Do you want to help shape the future of compute for the Amazon Web Services cloud?  

  

The EC2 Instance Platform organization is responsible for tackling challenging problems faced by enterprise customers via cloud\-based solutions. The team uses next\-gen technologies to develop large\-scale platforms to help customers optimally run their business.
  

  

We are hiring Senior Software Development Engineers to make Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\) the best place to run enterprise class workloads. As part of our team you will help build next generation services that simplifies how our customers and partners configure and manage high performance computing workloads on the cloud. You will closely work with various pre\-release Amazon technologies and build services that handle large scale, highly available distributed systems.
  

  

We are looking for Software Development Engineers who are passionate about working on next\-gen technologies, who b</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Applied Scientist, Kiro Science - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7383cf94c997f154</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Agentic AI is looking for a Principal Applied Scientist who will partner with world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next generation of AI\-driven development tools. Join the Amazon Kiro LLM\-Training team and help create groundbreaking generative AI technologies including Kiro IDE and Amazon Q Developer that are transforming the software development landscape.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As a key member of our team, you'll be at the forefront of innovation, where cutting\-edge research meets real\-world application:  

  

* Push the boundaries of reinforcement learning and post\-training methodologies for large language models specialized in code intelligence
* Invent and implement state\-of\-the\-art machine learning solutions that operate at unprecedented Amazon scale
* Deploy revolutionary products that directly impact the daily workflows of millions of developers worldwide
* Break new ground in AI and machine learning, ch</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Development Engineer - AI/ML, AWS Neuron - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b8c30db800f4af75</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Annapurna Labs team at Amazon Web Services (AWS) builds AWS Neuron, the software development kit used to accelerate deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon’s custom machine learning accelerators, Inferentia and Trainium.  

  

The AWS Neuron SDK, developed by the Annapurna Labs team at AWS, is the backbone for accelerating deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon's Inferentia and Trainium ML accelerators. This comprehensive toolkit includes an ML compiler, runtime, and application framework that seamlessly integrates with popular ML frameworks like PyTorch and JAX enabling unparalleled ML inference and training performance.  

  

The Inference Enablement and Acceleration team is at the forefront of running a wide range of models and supporting novel architecture alongside maximizing their performance for AWS's custom ML accelerators. Working across the stack from PyTorch till the hardware\-software boundary, our engineers build systematic </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer - AI/ML, AWS Neuron - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9927ba9b21fcde77</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Annapurna Labs team at Amazon Web Services (AWS) builds AWS Neuron, the software development kit used to accelerate deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon’s custom machine learning accelerators, Inferentia and Trainium.  

  

The AWS Neuron SDK, developed by the Annapurna Labs team at AWS, is the backbone for accelerating deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon's Inferentia and Trainium ML accelerators. This comprehensive toolkit includes an ML compiler, runtime, and application framework that seamlessly integrates with popular ML frameworks like PyTorch and JAX enabling unparalleled ML inference and training performance.  

  

The Inference Enablement and Acceleration team is at the forefront of running a wide range of models and supporting novel architecture alongside maximizing their performance for AWS's custom ML accelerators. Working across the stack from PyTorch till the hardware\-software boundary, our engineers build systematic </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Amazon Ads - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e45bc7a3e4ba1e31</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Applications will be accepted on an ongoing basis  

  

Amazon Ads is re\-imagining advertising through cutting\-edge generative artificial intelligence (AI) technologies. We combine human creativity with AI to transform every aspect of the advertising life cycle—from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. Our solutions help advertisers grow their brands while enabling millions of customers to discover and purchase products through delightful experiences. We deliver billions of ad impressions and millions of clicks daily, breaking fresh ground in product and technical innovations. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Why you’ll love this role:
  

This role offers unprecedented breadth in ML applications and access to extensive computational resources and rich datasets that </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Amazon Ads - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9fc03de1d187312e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Applications will be accepted on an ongoing basis  

  

Amazon Ads is re\-imagining advertising through cutting\-edge generative artificial intelligence (AI) technologies. We combine human creativity with AI to transform every aspect of the advertising life cycle—from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. Our solutions help advertisers grow their brands while enabling millions of customers to discover and purchase products through delightful experiences. We deliver billions of ad impressions and millions of clicks daily, breaking fresh ground in product and technical innovations. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Why you’ll love this role:
  

This role offers unprecedented breadth in ML applications and access to extensive computational resources and rich datasets that </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. SoC Power Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Cloud Scale Machine Learning - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d31e5fa5bfed957</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (IoT), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Our Machine Learning Acceleration (MLA) team develops the Inferentia and Trainium SoCs that are used to power today’s AI workloads in datacenters all around the world. As a Sr. SoC Power Engineer, you’ll contribute to the project at the ground level by modeling and estimating power at every stage of the design from early RTL to final netlist and by driving ways to reduce pow</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Annapurna Labs at AWS Internships (US) - Machine Learning Systems &amp; Silicon Innovation - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4e0408736c8a790b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


What if you could help build something that's never existed before? At Annapurna Labs, an Amazon company, we're not just participating in the AI revolution, we're accelerating it. We design custom silicon and revolutionary software systems that were considered impossible just yesterday, powering the world's most advanced AI infrastructure at AWS. From training the largest language models on Earth to developing breakthrough ML accelerator chips, we're inventing the future of cloud computing.  

  

We're seeking bold innovators and builders for our 2026 internship program. At Annapurna Labs, you'll work on projects that directly impact millions of AWS customers worldwide, tackling real technical challenges that push the boundaries of what's possible in AI acceleration. Our program offers multiple technical tracks, matching your skills and interests with projects across our organization.
  

  

Want to architect next\-generation AI chips that process bi</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c2cfd8976596a006</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is responsible for developing diverse datasets to train and evaluate the Amazon AI models. We are looking for Language Engineers to join our science and engineering team to support the development of complex, multimodal datasets, using a range of approaches including synthetic data generation, model\-supported data generation, and human\-in\-the\-loop data collections.
  

  

You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in evaluating and training AI models. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are best in class.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design complex data collections with human participants in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coor</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer, Nitro SSD - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=52dd3474cab128e8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The AWS Hardware Engineering team is driving rapid innovation in the server and storage infrastructure used by Amazon Web Services. Our designs are industry\-leading in frugality and operational excellence, and are critical to the success of the AWS business and the more than one million customers who use AWS today. Our Firmware Engineers solve challenging technology problems, and build architecturally sound, high\-quality components to enable AWS to realize critical business strategies.
  

  

The ideal candidate for this role will be an innovative self\-starter. You will be an SSD firmware expert with experience in making architectural tradeoffs to optimize SSD performance for a variety of use cases. You will work with engineers across the company as well as external companies and lead firmware development efforts on custom solid\-state devices. You will collaborate with internal and external development engineers (architecture, hardware, validation</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Robotics - Software Development Engineer Intern/Co-op - 2026 - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6db1bda0220f17e5</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Do you want to solve real customer problems through innovative technology? Do you enjoy working on scalable services in a collaborative team environment? Do you want to see your code directly impact millions of customers worldwide?  

  

At Amazon, we hire the best minds in technology to innovate and build on behalf of our customers. Customer obsession is part of our company DNA, which has made us one of the world's most beloved brands.  

  

Our Software Development Engineers (SDEs) use modern technology to solve complex problems while seeing their work's impact first\-hand. The challenges SDEs solve at Amazon are meaningful and influence millions of customers, sellers, and products globally. We seek individuals passionate about creating new products, features, and services while managing ambiguity in an environment where development cycles are measured in weeks, not years.
  

  

At Amazon, we believe in ownership at every level. As an SDE\-I, you</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Design Technologist, Prime Video - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9ad0db268f786d5d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Do you want to define the next generation of how and what Amazon customers are watching? Prime Video is changing the way people watch movies and TV. From one service, we’re delivering versatile ways to watch hundreds of thousands of movies, TV series, and live events on the web, mobile, and TV. Our service is available in more than 200 territories globally, and we’re just getting started.  

  

Working closely with business and technology partners, we use research, design, and prototyping to guide early product development, bring clarity to engineering goals, and develop a customer\-centric point of view. This is where you come in.  

  

As a Senior Design Technologist, you'll be a key part of our Experience Design organization. Your role will be all about proving, advancing, and evolving forward\-looking UX concepts through prototyping and hands\-on product work. You'll work alongside other </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, SPB Advertiser Guidance - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5bafd10884b9fb14</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


We are looking for a passionate Applied Scientist to help pioneer the next generation of agentic AI applications for Amazon advertisers. In this role, you will design agentic architectures, develop tools and datasets, and contribute to building systems that can reason, plan, and act autonomously across complex advertiser workflows.
  

  

You will work at the forefront of applied AI, developing methods for fine\-tuning, reinforcement learning, and preference optimization, while helping create evaluation frameworks that ensure safety, reliability, and trust at scale. You will work backwards from the needs of advertisers—delivering customer\-facing products that directly help them create, optimize, and grow their campaigns.
  

  

Beyond building models, you will advance the agent ecosystem by experimenting with and applying core primitives such as tool orchestration, multi\-step reasoning, and adaptive preference\-driven behavior. This role requires w</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=87f103af9e3d4e42</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is responsible for developing diverse datasets to train and evaluate the Amazon AI models. We are looking for Senior Language Engineers to join our science and engineering team to support the development of complex, multimodal datasets, using a range of approaches including synthetic data generation, model\-supported data generation, and human\-in\-the\-loop data collections.
  

  

You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in evaluating and training AI models. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are best in class.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Define and lead the organization's data creation strategies for our science partners
* Design and lead complex data collections with human participants in response to science nee</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>MLA IP Design Verification Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3f736b8f9eb45738</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low\-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world.  

We are seeking an experienced Design Verification Engineers to build the next generation of our cloud server platforms. Our success depends on our world\-class infrastructure; we’re handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies.  

  

As a member of the Cloud\-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team you’ll be responsible for the design and validation of machine learning hardware in our data centers.  

  

Some of your responsibilities will include verifying/validating that our hardware and software solutions achieve their desired functionality, developing and executing multi\-faceted verification/validation plans, and measuring the teams progress towards our ambitious customer metrics.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Some of your respo</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Design Verification Engineer, Annapurna ML - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9fe0f0c92f50b353</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------

  

Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low\-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world. We have data center locations in the U.S., Europe, Singapore, and Japan, and customers across all industries. We are seeking experienced Hardware Design Engineers to build the next generation of our cloud server infrastructure. Our success depends on our world\-class server infrastructure; we’re handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies.  

  

As a member of the Cloud\-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team you’ll be responsible for the design and optimization of hardware in our data centers .  

  

Some of your responsibilities will include verifying/validating that our hardware and software solutions achieve their desired functionality, developing and executing multi\-faceted verification/validation plans, and measuring the teams p</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a10d25d22a5489c7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Applied Science Internship - United States, PhD Student Science Recruiting, Frontier AI &amp; Robotics - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=eb153d2bfc298bdd</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you a brilliant mind seeking to push the boundaries of what's possible with intelligent robotics? Join our elite team of researchers and engineers \- led by Pieter Abeel, Rocky Duan, and Peter Chen \- at the forefront of applied science, where we're harnessing the latest advancements in large language models (LLMs) and generative AI to reshape the world of robotics and unlock new realms of innovation.  

As an Applied Science Intern, you'll have the unique opportunity to work alongside world\-renowned experts, gaining invaluable hands\-on experience with cutting\-edge robotics technologies. You'll dive deep into exciting research projects at the intersection of AI and robotics.  

This internship is not just about executing tasks – it's about being a driving force behind groundbreaking discoveries. You'll collaborate with cross\-functional teams, leveraging your expertise in areas such as deep learning, reinforcement learning, computer vision, and </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>C/C++ Hardware / Software Co-Design SDE, Machine Learning Acceleration Systems - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=99aaf6a9bc5c3290</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>MLA IP Design Verification Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e71927bc8c116a21</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low\-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world.  

We are seeking an experienced Design Verification Engineers to build the next generation of our cloud server platforms. Our success depends on our world\-class infrastructure; we’re handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies.  

  

As a member of the Cloud\-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team you’ll be responsible for the design and validation of machine learning hardware in our data centers.  

  

Some of your responsibilities will include verifying/validating that our hardware and software solutions achieve their desired functionality, developing and executing multi\-faceted verification/validation plans, and measuring the teams progress towards our ambitious customer metrics.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Some of your respo</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Recommendation/Search - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4a6dca1cddd2b14d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Science Manager, Amazon Sponsored Products &amp; Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=36c4c0d37b625aff</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sr. Manager Applied Science will lead a cross\-functional team of 30\+ builders in pioneering GenAI experiences for \+1\.3MM Amazon Sponsored Product and Brand (SPB) advertisers. The leader will invent and build the SPB\-Agent, a GenAI platform which will transform retail\-media advertising for SPB advertisers, from emerging brands to global brands selling on Amazon. SPB\-Agent will serve as an intelligent advisor integrated directly into Amazon Ad Console and Selling Partner portals (Seller Central and Vendor Central). Through conversational interfaces and deep reasoning, it will help advertisers discover growth opportunities, optimize campaign performance, and execute sophisticated strategies. The leader will drive this transformation from vision to reality, directly shaping the intersection of generative AI and advertising at unprecedented scale.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As a Sr. Applied Science Manager, you will:  

  

* Lead a cross</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer, Neuron Foundation Tools - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f810e7c6acd40e93</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Neuron is the complete software stack for the AWS Inferentia and Trainium cloud\-scale machine learning accelerators and the Trn1 and Inf1 servers that use them.  

  

As the Software Development Engineer for the Neuron Foundation Tools Team, you will be responsible for working alongside a team of engineers to develop and maintain high\-performance monitoring and profiling tools for machine learning applications and AI accelerators. You will work on design, development, and deployment of the Neuron Profiler and other Neuron Tools. The profiler plays a crucial role to internal and external customers in optimizing AI workloads across hardware platforms such as Trainium and Inferentia devices, by providing deep insights into performance bottlenecks and system behavior. Improving performance of ML Kernels and ML Frameworks.  

  

In this role, you will manage the full development life cycle of the Neuron Profiler/Tools toolchain, ensuring scalability</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Manager, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c8001b9220bf685d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


About Sponsored Products and Brands  

The Sponsored Products and Brands team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.
  

  

About our team  

  

The SPB Offsite team builds solu</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Software Dev Engineer, Machine Learning, Sponsored Products and Brands Ads Response Prediction - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0027eae5aa54e776</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


About Sponsored Products and Brands  

  

The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As a Software Dev</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Firmware Engineer, Annapurna Labs, Machine Learning Acceleration - Power and Performance - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0ce27a0669aac733</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challenges that have never been seen before, and deliver results that help our customers change the world.  

  

We are seeking a Senior Firmware Engineer to join our Power Architecture team, developing firmware algorithms for power and performance management on ML Acceleration Chips. In this role, you will design and implement intelligent control algorithms, optimization strategies, and real\-time decision\-making systems that maximize performance while managing power and thermal constraints.  

  

You will develop sophisticated firmware that monitors system state, makes dynamic trade\-offs between </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Firmware Engineer, Annapurna Labs, ML Acceleration - Performance Instrumentation &amp; Developer Tools - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c3dd6f7afac605a</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challenges that have never been seen before, and deliver results that help our customers change the world.  

  

We are seeking a Senior Firmware Engineer to join our Power Architecture team, developing firmware algorithms for power and performance management on ML Acceleration Chips. In this role, you will design and implement intelligent control algorithms, optimization strategies, and real\-time decision\-making systems that maximize performance while managing power and thermal constraints.  

  

You will develop sophisticated firmware that monitors system state, makes dynamic trade\-offs between </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Applied Scientist, AWS Agentic AI Science - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a59a909a6585eca2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Agentic AI is looking for a world\-class Applied Scientist with a strong deep learning background to help build industry\-leading Agentic AI (models, systems, and applications). Our mission is to provide a delightful experience to Amazon’s customers by pushing the envelope in Natural Language Understanding (NLU), AI assisted code development, reasoning and planning with LLMs, LLM training and fine\-tuning, and Applied Machine Learning (ML). As part of our AI team in Amazon AWS, you will work alongside internationally recognized experts to develop novel algorithms and modeling techniques to advance the state\-of\-the\-art in Agentic AI. Your work will directly impact millions of our customers in the form of products and services that make use AI technology. You will gain hands on experience with Amazon’s heterogeneous text, structured data sources, and large\-scale computing resources to accelerate advances in language understanding.  

  

We are l</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, AWS Agentic AI - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1317416b60d2f330</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Agentic AI is looking for motivated scientists to join its newly created org focusing on agentic AI. This group is entrusted with developing core natural language processing, agents, generative AI, AI reasoning and planning, and model training for AWS, with a focus on code development, broadly defined. You will invent, implement, and deploy state of the art deep learning algorithms and systems. You will build prototypes and explore conceptually new solutions. You will interact closely with our customers and with the academic community. You will be at the heart of a growing and exciting focus area for AWS Agentic AI, a generative AI–powered assistant for enterprise computing, and work with other acclaimed engineers and world famous scientists.  

  

As an Applied Scientist, you are recognized for your expertise, advise team members on a range of machine learning topics, and work closely with software engineers to drive the delivery of end\-to\-e</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Product Manager - Kernels, AI/ML, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=dcbbed001801353b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Neuron is looking for an experienced Technical Product Manager to define and drive product strategy for the Neuron Kernel Interface (NKI), a compiler library enabling custom kernel development and optimization. You will be part of the AWS Neuron Product Management team, driving innovation in machine learning acceleration software. AWS Neuron is the software stack for Trainium and Inferentia, the AWS Machine Learning chips, delivering best\-in\-class ML performance in the cloud. You will lead NKI requirements working backward from customer needs, drive kernel library features definition, and drive developer experience for custom kernel development, enabling customers to successfully and independently develop and optimize ML workloads on AWS Neuron through deep understanding of compiler systems, kernel optimization, and hardware acceleration.  

  

The ideal candidate will have solid understanding of compiler technologies, computer architecture, and</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c1238b5a99ac9768</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. ASIC Design Engineer, Cloud-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3576e20d04485b65</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Utility Computing (UC)  

AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Language Engineer, Artificial General Intelligence - Data Services - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d53d7b94365c2b1</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Amazon Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) Data Services organization is looking for a Language Engineer with experience in dataset construction, linguistic annotation, dialog/semantic schemas, and automatic processing of large datasets. You will play a critical role in driving innovation and advancing the state\-of\-the\-art in natural language processing and machine learning. You will work closely with cross\-functional teams, including product managers, engineers, and data scientists to ensure that our AI systems are aligned with human policies and preferences.
  

  

Key job responsibilities  

Specifically, the Language Engineer will:
  

* Design data collection/creation tasks in response to science needs: author instructions, define and implement quality targets and mechanisms, provide day\-to\-day coordination of data collection efforts (including planning, scheduling, and reporting), and be responsible for the final deliverables
* Analy</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Hardware Engineer - ML Acceleration, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ed4379e54ab7efb7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challen</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Post-Silicon Systems Software Validation Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a94d202b03a1420c</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs, an AWS organization with development centers in the U.S. and Israel, builds custom silicon and software for AWS customers. Our team combines cloud\-scale innovation with world\-class expertise across silicon engineering, hardware design, verification, software, and operations to tackle technical challenges that have never been seen before.  

  

Join our Silicon Validation team to validate next\-generation machine learning accelerators that power AWS's cloud computing infrastructure. You'll work in a fast\-paced, startup\-like environment alongside some of the brightest minds in the industry on cutting\-edge, internet\-scale technology that directly impacts how customers use Machine Learning acceleration. We are changing the landscape of cloud infrastructure by accelerating the development of custom silicon by moving beyond traditional partnerships to dominate in AI training and inference.  

  

Your work will span validation of the c</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Science Manager - Web Search/Retrieval/Ranking, AGI Info - Web Information Systems - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4f05c3544ab32762</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Help shape the future of artificial intelligence by leading breakthrough innovations in web search and Retrieval Augmented Generation at Amazon AGI. We're seeking an exceptional Applied Science Manager to drive the development of next\-generation search capabilities to improve agentic applications across Amazon. Your work will directly influence the next generation of Amazon's search and AI systems, improving how millions of users interact with our platforms through more intelligent and efficient information retrieval systems.  

  

What will you do?: You will lead a team of scientists to improve our web search capabilities and drive key improvements across multiple agentic systems across Amazon. You will be responsible for: (i) developing novel retrieval and ranking models to improve search, incorporating multiple objectives (e.g. relevance and trustworthiness), and partnering closely with engineering to improve model performance; (ii) improve conten</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Science Manager, Sponsored Products and Brands Ads Response Prediction - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f0f49e602f584719</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


About Sponsored Products and Brands  

  

The Sponsored Products and Brands team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.
  

  

Key job responsibilities  

As an Applied Science </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Development Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=64c76e2923b8f6d4</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


In this role you will be responsible for leading a technical team which is critical in providing profiling and optimization tools for the Neuron ML accelerators fleet. You will work closely with the hardware and software teams to ensure the right tools are available for performance profiling of large ML workloads, identifying bottlenecks and automatically providing improvement recommendations. Neuron Core Tools develops and maintains a family of profiling software and provides ability for performance engineers to develop and improve custom kernels that would impact efficiency of large workloads.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Provide technical leadership to the Neuron Core Tools team
* Work closely with the frameworks and compiler teams.
* Collect requirements from various other teams including training, inference and runtime.
* Collaborate with the compiler performance team to ensure timely release of the core performance tools.
* Anticipate fut</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science, Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3856ead68355b137</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Generative AI Innovation Center - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ff6d1517645013f9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Feb 24, 2026  

  

Are you looking to work at the forefront of Machine Learning and AI? Would you be excited to apply Generative AI to solve real world problems with significant impact? The Generative AI Innovation Center helps AWS customers implement Generative AI solutions and realize transformational business opportunities. This is a team of scientists, engineers, architects, and strategists working step\-by\-step with customers to build bespoke solutions that harness the power of generative AI.  

  

The GenAI Innovation Center helps AWS customers develop and scale generative AI solutions. The team helps customers imagine and scope bespoke use cases that will create the greatest value for their businesses, define paths to navigate technical or business challenges, develop models to power real world applications, and make plans for launching solutions at scale. The GenAI Innovation Center team provides guidance on best practi</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Hardware Engineer - ML Acceleration, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=94aeeb96a1c30c30</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challen</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Director, Applied Science, Stores Economics and Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=90b2c2fb61641290</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


We are looking for a science leader who is able to provide structure around complex business problems, work with machine learning scientists to estimate and validate their models on large scale data, and who can help business and tech partners turn the results of their analysis into policies, programs, and actions that have a major impact on Amazon’s business. We are looking for creative thinkers who can combine a strong economic toolbox with a desire to learn from others, and who know how to execute and deliver on big ideas.  

  

At the senior level, we expect you be able to own the development of scientific models and to manage, in close collaboration with scientists and engineers, the data analysis, modeling, and experimentation that is necessary for estimating and validating your model. You will need to work with our business partners to communicate the properties of your analysis/modeling and be able to work to incorporate their feedback and req</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Manager Research Science, WW Sustainability - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=901748963900b31e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Worldwide Sustainability (WWS) organization leverages Amazon's size, scale, and inventive culture to build a more resilient and sustainable company. WWS manages our social and environmental impacts globally, driving solutions that enable our customers, businesses, and the world to become more sustainable.  

  

We are seeking an experienced science leader to drive foundational innovations in sustainability measurement and planning across Amazon's global operations. This role will tackle complex sustainability challenges across all industrial sectors and geographic regions where Amazon operates, building science\-driven capabilities for confident decision\-making and investments in sustainability initiatives.  

  

You will lead a multidisciplinary team of scientists, economists, engineers, and scholars to deliver transformative solutions across multiple environmental impact areas, including carbon, water, waste, biodiversity, and circularity. You</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. MLE, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=508c604832f84232</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bf9e8846b8b3ff4f</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Recommendation/Search Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4c837388be17fe9f</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Substrate CAD Layout Eng, Annapurna Labs, Machine Learning Hardware - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=00c2fa6e80aac714</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challenges that have never been seen before, and deliver results that help our customers change the world.  

  

We are seeking an experienced Senior Substrate CAD layout Engineer for the next generation of our ML ASIC. This is a fast\-paced, intellectually challenging position, and you’ll work with thought\-leaders in multiple technology areas. You’ll have relentlessly high standards for yourself and everyone you work with, and you’ll be constantly looking for ways to improve your products performance, quality and cost.  

  

We’re changing an industry, and we want individuals who are ready for this challenge and want to reach beyond what is </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. ASIC Engineer III, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=df582aef1c07e48d</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Utility Computing (UC)  

AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video , Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=21bca39920e1e6b7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a2dcfde7553a0481</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc4ebc6e9e06055e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b05aa3118f67bb30</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Development Engineer, AI/ML, AWS Neuron, Model Inference - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bfed585bb267b955</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Annapurna Labs team at Amazon Web Services (AWS) builds AWS Neuron, the software development kit used to accelerate deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon’s custom machine learning accelerators, Inferentia and Trainium.  

  

The AWS Neuron SDK, developed by the Annapurna Labs team at AWS, is the backbone for accelerating deep learning and GenAI workloads on Amazon's Inferentia and Trainium ML accelerators. This comprehensive toolkit includes an ML compiler, runtime, and application framework that seamlessly integrates with popular ML frameworks like PyTorch and JAX enabling unparalleled ML inference and training performance.  

  

The Inference Enablement and Acceleration team is at the forefront of running a wide range of models and supporting novel architecture alongside maximizing their performance for AWS's custom ML accelerators. Working across the stack from PyTorch till the hardware\-software boundary, our engineers build systematic </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist III, StoreGen - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e0557b0f061d0a9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join our Generative AI focus team to innovate Software Development at Amazon  

  

Are you ready to be part of a team that's redefining the future of software engineering? Our team is Amazon's ambitious initiative to pioneer AI development practices that will fundamentally transform how we build software at scale.  

  

Our Mission  

  

We’re building the next generation of development tools — uncovering how LLMs can originate new ways of thinking, building, and collaborating.  

  

What Makes Us Different  

  

* Ground\-floor opportunity to shape the future of software development
* Direct impact on Amazon's global engineering practices
* Working with the latest technologies and large language models
* Culture of experimentation and innovative thinking

  

What We’re Looking For  

You’ll lead the research, design, and development of AI technologies that challenge conventional software practices and uncover new ways for engineers to build and </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. HSIO Validation Engineer, Annapurna Labs Machine Learning Acceleration - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9bc5b012827e3a0f</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


As an HSIO Validation Engineer, you will be responsible for ensuring the correct operation, bring\-up, and scalability of high\-speed I/O including PCIe, HBM, UCIe, and other protocols used in our custom machine learning chips. You will work with architecture, IP owners, DV, software, and signal integrity teams to productize the latest high\-speed I/O technology in both pre\-silicon and post\-silicon.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Gain a deep understanding of SoC architecture.
* Work with architecture, IP owners, DV, software, and signal integrity teams to verify and integrate high\-speed I/O functionality and performance.
* Execute feature enablement and validation test cases for high\-speed interfaces.
* Develop and maintain software\-based validation tests and automation frameworks for both pre\-silicon and post\-silicon environments.
* Debug and drive root\-cause analysis for device\-related issues; document failure analysis and report test </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist II, Prime Video Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9de973dfd9afebbc</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.
  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-th</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. SDE C/C++ Hardware/Software Co-Design, Machine Learning Acceleration Systems - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=48cf4eae3f12a7d2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Development Engineer, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=43ec88c67ef2fbee</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


In this role you will be responsible for leading a technical team which is critical in providing compute sanitization to the Neuron ML accelerators fleet. You will work closely with the hardware and software teams to ensure the right tools are available for identifying defects or faulty states of the hardware before the customer hits an issue. Neuron Compute Sanitizer Tools develops and maintains a pre\-check and functional correctness checking suite and provides visibility at the fleet level to understand the trends of hardware/software sanitization.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Provide technical leadership to the Compute Sanitization team
* Work closely with the hardware and firmware design teams.
* Collect requirements from various other teams including training, inference and runtime.
* Collaborate with the runtime team to ensure timely release of the pre\-check tools.
* Anticipate future needs based on the product roadmap and develop neces</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Science Manager, Prime Video Personalization &amp; Discovery - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ed1757eab425cb6e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Amazon Advertising - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fd7dfa1cf94e3cf0</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Advertising is one of Amazon's fastest growing and most profitable businesses. Amazon's advertising portfolio helps merchants, retail vendors, and brand owners succeed via native advertising, which grows incremental sales of their products sold through Amazon. The primary goals are to help shoppers discover new products they love, be the most efficient way for advertisers to meet their business objectives, and build a sustainable business that continuously innovates on behalf of customers. Our products and solutions are strategically important to enable our Retail and Marketplace businesses to drive long\-term growth. We deliver billions of ad impressions and millions of clicks and break fresh ground in product and technical innovations every day!  

  

As a Senior Applied Scientist on this team, you will:
  

* Be the technical leader in Machine Learning; lead efforts within this team and across other teams.
* Perform hands\-on analysis and mo</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Prime Video - Personalization and Discovery Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2b7b9c07b902db14</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Prime Video is a first\-stop entertainment destination offering customers a vast collection of premium programming in one app available across thousands of devices. Prime members can customize their viewing experience and find their favorite movies, series, documentaries, and live sports – including Amazon MGM Studios\-produced series and movies; licensed fan favorites; and programming from Prime Video add\-on subscriptions such as Apple TV\+, Max, Crunchyroll and MGM\+. All customers, regardless of whether they have a Prime membership or not, can rent or buy titles via the Prime Video Store, and can enjoy even more content for free with ads.  

  

Are you interested in shaping the future of entertainment? Prime Video's technology teams are creating best\-in\-class digital video experience.  

  

As a Prime Video technologist, you’ll have end\-to\-end ownership of the product, user experience, design, and technology required to deliver state\-of\-the</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Manager, Foundations Software - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ef7d80e05390a376</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


In this role you will be responsible for building and supporting a team which is critical in providing compute sanitization to the Neuron ML accelerators fleet. You will work closely with the hardware and software teams to ensure the right tools are available for identifying defects or faulty states of the hardware before the customer hits an issue. Neuron Compute Sanitizer Tools develops and maintains a pre\-check and functional correctness checking suite and provides visibility at the fleet level to understand the trends of hardware/software sanitization.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Build and develop a strong team of engineers that would deliver the pre\-check suite.
* Work closely with the hardware and firmware design teams.
* Collect requirements from various other teams including training, inference and runtime.
* Collaborate with the runtime team to ensure timely release of the pre\-check tools.
* Anticipate future needs based on the pro</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist, Sales AI - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8553d5e520bf7695</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Are you interested in shaping the future of Advertising and B2B Sales? We are a growing science and engineering team with an exciting charter and need your passion, innovative thinking, and creativity to help take our products to new heights.  

  

Amazon Advertising is one of Amazon's fastest growing and most profitable businesses, responsible for defining and delivering a collection of advertising products that drive discovery and sales. Our products are strategically important to our businesses driving long term growth. We deliver billions of ad impressions and millions of clicks and break fresh ground in product and technical innovations every day!  

  

Within the Advertising Sales organization, we are building a central AI/ML team and are seeking top science talent to build new, science\-backed services to drive success for our customers. Our goal is to transform the way account teams operate by creating actionable insights and recommendations </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. SDM, AI Inference Technology, Neuron SDK - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8a705fe4e03648b7</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry.
  

  

Come develop inference acceleration for AWS Neuron, the complete software stack for Trainium, Amazon's custom cloud\-scale machine learning accelerators that power the latest AI models  

  

As the Sr. SDM for the Inference Technology Team, you will lead a strong team of managers and engineers to build fundamental inference technology building blocks and libraries to enable AI developers to optimize model for inference on Trainium and Inferentia devices. You will be responsible for the full development life cycle of inference library and feature development, including reliability and scalability. You will develop the Neuronx\_Distributed Inference Libraries and contribute to other popular open source Inference Librarie</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Worldwide Specialist Solutions Architect - HPC/ML, Computer Aided Engineering (CAE), Weather &amp; GPU Computing - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1b7bcc6d251f521b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Application deadline: Feb 25, 2026  

  

AWS Specialist Solutions Architects (SSAs) are technologists with deep domain\-specific expertise, able to address advanced concepts and feature designs. As part of the AWS sales organization, SSAs work with customers who have complex challenges that require expert\-level knowledge to solve. SSAs craft scalable, flexible, and resilient technical architectures that address those challenges. This might involve guiding customers as they refactor an application or designing entirely new cloud\-based systems. Do you enjoy solving novel and unique technical challenges for customers? Become an AWS Specialist SA!  

  

The Worldwide Specialist Organization (WWSO) is part of AWS Sales, Marketing, and Global Services (SMGS), which is responsible for driving revenue, adoption, and growth from the largest and fastest growing small\- and mid\-market accounts to enterprise\-level customers including public sector. We work b</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Applied Scientist, Delivery Foundation Model - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c42827efb65e1c83</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next science and engineering revolution at Amazon's Delivery Foundation Model team, where you'll work alongside world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next frontier of logistics through advanced AI and foundation models.  

  

We are seeking an exceptional Principal Applied Scientist to help develop innovative foundation models that enable delivery of billions of packages worldwide. In this role, you'll combine highly technical work with scientific leadership, ensuring the team delivers robust solutions for dynamic real\-world environments. Your team will leverage Amazon's vast data and computational resources to tackle ambitious problems across a diverse set of Amazon delivery use cases.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design and implement novel deep learning architectures combining a multitude of modalities, including image, video, and geospatial data.
* Solve computational problems to train foundation models on vast amou</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Quality &amp; Reliability Engineer, Trainium Servers and Systems Manufacturing - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=992eed0a4ca4aea4</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Trainium Manufacturing, Quality and Reliability (MQR) Team is part of AWS Annapurna Labs focused on Machine Learning products that designs cutting AI platforms for the world’s largest Cloud Services provider. As a Senior Reliability Engineer you will engage with an experienced cross\-disciplinary staff to conceive and design infrastructure technologies. You will work closely with an internal inter\-disciplinary team, and outside partners to drive key aspects of product definition, execution and test in manufacturing. A successful candidate will be responsive, flexible and able to succeed within an open collaborative peer environment. You will:  

  

* Be responsible for the test validation of future technologies.
* Drive manufacturing process improvements to address reliability issues and concerns.
* Qualify manufacturing lines and mechanisms for mass production
* You will have a fundamental understanding of Reliability statistics/Reliability test</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Delivery Foundation Model - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8cbf5c1e43445fce</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next science and engineering revolution at Amazon's Delivery Foundation Model team, where you'll work alongside world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next frontier of logistics through advanced AI and foundation models.  

  

We are seeking an exceptional Senior Applied Scientist to help develop innovative foundation models that enable delivery of billions of packages worldwide. In this role, you'll combine highly technical work with scientific leadership, ensuring the team delivers robust solutions for dynamic real\-world environments. Your team will leverage Amazon's vast data and computational resources to tackle ambitious problems across a diverse set of Amazon delivery use cases.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design and implement novel deep learning architectures combining a multitude of modalities, including image, video, and geospatial data.
* Solve computational problems to train foundation models on vast amounts</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist - Privacy, Privacy Engineering - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c8cfe9993e91ce49</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon is seeking an innovative and high\-judgement Senior Applied Scientist to join the Privacy Engineering team in the Amazon Privacy Services org. We own products and programs that deliver technical innovation for ensuring compliance with high\-impact, urgent regulation across Amazon services worldwide.
  

  

The Senior Applied Scientist will contribute to the strategic direction for Amazon’s privacy practices while building/owning the compliance approach for individual regulations such as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), DMA, Quebec 25 etc. This will require helping to frame, and participating in, high judgment debates and decision making across senior business, technology, legal, and public policy leaders.
  

  

A great candidate will have a unique combination of experience with innovative data governance technology, high judgement in system architecture decisions and ability to set detailed technical design from ambiguous compliance</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist - Privacy, Privacy Engineering - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cb10a130741f7439</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon is seeking an innovative and high\-judgement Senior Applied Scientist to join the Privacy Engineering team in the Amazon Privacy Services org. We own products and programs that deliver technical innovation for ensuring compliance with high\-impact, urgent regulation across Amazon services worldwide.
  

  

The Senior Applied Scientist will contribute to the strategic direction for Amazon’s privacy practices while building/owning the compliance approach for individual regulations such as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), DMA, Quebec 25 etc. This will require helping to frame, and participating in, high judgment debates and decision making across senior business, technology, legal, and public policy leaders.
  

  

A great candidate will have a unique combination of experience with innovative data governance technology, high judgement in system architecture decisions and ability to set detailed technical design from ambiguous compliance</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Applied Scientist - Privacy, Privacy Engineering - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e557c882a6d55a44</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon is seeking an innovative and high\-judgement Senior Applied Scientist to join the Privacy Engineering team in the Amazon Privacy Services org. We own products and programs that deliver technical innovation for ensuring compliance with high\-impact, urgent regulation across Amazon services worldwide.
  

  

The Senior Applied Scientist will contribute to the strategic direction for Amazon’s privacy practices while building/owning the compliance approach for individual regulations such as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), DMA, Quebec 25 etc. This will require helping to frame, and participating in, high judgment debates and decision making across senior business, technology, legal, and public policy leaders.
  

  

A great candidate will have a unique combination of experience with innovative data governance technology, high judgement in system architecture decisions and ability to set detailed technical design from ambiguous compliance</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Applied Scientist, Delivery Foundation Model - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=43ba60ef63af296a</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next science and engineering revolution at Amazon's Delivery Foundation Model team, where you'll work alongside world\-class scientists and engineers to pioneer the next frontier of logistics through advanced AI and foundation models.  

  

We are seeking an exceptional Principal Applied Scientist to help develop innovative foundation models that enable delivery of billions of packages worldwide. In this role, you'll combine highly technical work with scientific leadership, ensuring the team delivers robust solutions for dynamic real\-world environments. Your team will leverage Amazon's vast data and computational resources to tackle ambitious problems across a diverse set of Amazon delivery use cases.  

  

Key job responsibilities  

* Design and implement novel deep learning architectures combining a multitude of modalities, including image, video, and geospatial data.
* Solve computational problems to train foundation models on vast amou</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Economist, Stores Economics and Science - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=242b28d0ee042e6e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


This role will contribute to developing the Economics and Science products and services in the Fee domain, with specialization in supply chain systems and fees. Through the lens of economics, you will develop causal links for how Amazon, Sellers and Customers interact. You will be a key and senior scientist, advising Amazon leaders how to price our services. You will work on developing frameworks and scaleable, repeatable models supporting optimal pricing and policy in the two\-sided marketplace that is central to Amazon's business. The pricing for Amazon services is complex. You will partner with science and technology teams across Amazon including Advertising, Supply Chain, Operations, Prime, Consumer Pricing, and Finance.  

  

We are looking for an experienced Principal Economist to improve our understanding of seller Economics, enhance our ability to estimate the causal impact of fees, and work with partner teams to design pricing policy changes.</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Applied Scientist, FAR (Frontier AI &amp; Robotics) - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=988b9143eeff99ac</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next revolution in robotics at Amazon's Frontier AI \&amp; Robotics team, where you'll work alongside world\-renowned AI pioneers to lead key initiatives in robotic intelligence. As a Principal Applied Scientist, you'll spearhead the development of breakthrough foundation models that enable robots to perceive, understand, and interact with the world in unprecedented ways. You'll drive technical excellence in areas such as perception, manipulation, science understanding, sim2real transfer, multi\-modal foundation models, and multi\-task learning, designing novel algorithms that bridge the gap between state\-of\-the\-art research and real\-world deployment at Amazon scale.  

  

In this role, you'll combine hands\-on technical work with scientific leadership, ensuring your team delivers robust solutions for dynamic real\-world environments. You'll leverage Amazon's vast computational resources to tackle ambitious problems in areas like very large m</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning - Compiler Engineer II, AWS Neuron, Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2aaf93a11fec877b</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Do you want to be part of AI revolution? At AWS our vision is to make deep learning pervasive for everyday developers and to democratize access to AI hardware and software infrastructure. In order to deliver on that vision, we’ve created innovative software and hardware solutions that make it possible. AWS Neuron is the SDK that optimizes the performance of complex ML models executed on AWS Inferentia and Trainium, our custom chips designed to accelerate deep\-learning workloads.  

  

This role is for a software engineer in the Compiler team for AWS Neuron. As part of this role, you will be responsible for building next generation Neuron compiler which transforms ML models written in ML frameworks (e.g, PyTorch, TensorFlow, and JAX) to be deployed AWS Inferentia and Trainium based servers in the Amazon cloud. You will be responsible for solving hard compiler optimization problems to achieve optimum performance for variety of ML model families includi</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. ASIC Design Engineer, Cloud-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=03e312d74f4a5220</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Amazon Web Services provides a highly reliable, scalable, low\-cost infrastructure platform in the cloud that powers hundreds of thousands of businesses in 190 countries around the world. We have data center locations in the U.S., Europe, Singapore, and Japan, and customers across all industries.  

  

Custom SoCs (System on Chip) live at the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers. As a member of the Cloud\-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team you’ll be responsible for the design and optimization of hardware in our data centers including AWS Inferentia, our custom designed machine learning inference datacenter server. Our success depends on our world\-class server infrastructure; we’re handling massive scale and rapid integration of emergent technologies. We’re looking for an ASIC Design Eengineer to help us trail\-blaze new technologies and architectures, while ensuring high design quality and making the right trade\-offs.  

  

Key job responsib</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>ASIC Design Engineer, Cloud-Scale Machine Learning Acceleration team - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=53f02640760f81a2</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Utility Computing (UC)  

AWS Utility Computing (UC) provides product innovations — from foundational services such as Amazon’s Simple Storage Service (S3\) and Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2\), to consistently released new product innovations that continue to set AWS’s services and features apart in the industry. As a member of the UC organization, you’ll support the development and management of Compute, Database, Storage, Internet of Things (Iot), Platform, and Productivity Apps services in AWS, including support for customers who require specialized security solutions for customers who require specialized security solutions for their cloud services.  

  

Annapurna Labs (our organization within AWS UC) designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Development Engineer, FAR (Frontier AI &amp; Robotics) - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5523a44cc2b3e76e</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Join the next revolution in robotics at Amazon's Frontier AI \&amp; Robotics team, where you'll work alongside world\-renowned AI pioneers like Pieter Abbeel, Rocky Duan, and Peter Chen to make breakthrough foundation models run at production scale. As a Senior Machine Learning Engineer embedded in our science team, you'll be instrumental in transforming cutting\-edge research into high\-performance production systems. You'll collaborate directly with scientists to optimize large\-scale transformer architectures for robotics applications, leveraging your expertise in CUDA and TensorRT to achieve unprecedented inference efficiency at Amazon scale.  

In this role, you'll balance deep technical optimization work with strategic input on model architecture decisions, ensuring our innovative robotics models are designed with performance in mind from the ground up. You'll leverage NVIDIA's acceleration stack and other compilation techniques to tackle ambitious p</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Engineer- AI/ML, AWS Neuron Distributed Training - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6fa924591387f0a1</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs designs silicon and software that accelerates innovation. Customers choose us to create cloud solutions that solve challenges that were unimaginable a short time ago—even yesterday. Our custom chips, accelerators, and software stacks enable us to take on technical challenges that have never been seen before, and deliver results that help our customers change the world.  

  

AWS Neuron is the complete software stack for the AWS Trainium (Trn1/Trn2\) and Inferentia (Inf1/Inf2\) our cloud\-scale Machine Learning accelerators. This role is for a Senior Machine Learning Engineer in the Distribute Training team for AWS Neuron, responsible for development, enablement and performance tuning of a wide variety of ML model families, including massive\-scale Large Language Models (LLM) such as GPT and Llama, as well as Stable Diffusion, Vision Transformers (ViT) and many more.  

  

The ML Distributed Training team works side by side with chip ar</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 05:09:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
