<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
    <title>DS&MLE Jobs</title>
    <link>https://indeed.com</link>
    <description>jobs</description>
    
    <item>
        <title>IC Wire Bond, Die Attach and Flip Chip Engineer - Silitronics Solutions, Inc</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ed1e43b68da97b94</link>
        <description>Silitronics takes pride in delivering Vertically Integrated Design and Assembly Services for next\-generation products in AI/ML, Silicon Photonics, High Performance Computing, IoT Sensors, Medical, Defense, LiDAR, RF, and Commercial Applications. Our team brings over 100 years of combined domain expertise in Complex Assembly, Substrate and Board Design, Silicon Assembly, and automated Photonics Active Alignment. Silitronics specializes in advanced Semiconductor IC and Photonics PIC assembly, complemented by value\-added design engineering services.

We are seeking a driven IC Assembly Engineer to support the development of fully automated die attach and flip chip assembly processes. This role involves contributing to complex tooling, precision fixtures, and advanced assembly solutions, including photonics applications. It is an excellent opportunity for an engineer passionate about hands\-on engineering, learning advanced photonics assembly techniques, and pioneering silicon photonics </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-28</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer, Data &amp; Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f5979d3730e144c9</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Waymo Mapping team's goal is to build a high resolution map of the world to support safe autonomous driving. We work on creating the map using a combination of automatic and manual techniques and build the infrastructure to store, process, and distribute the map. Our team collaborates wit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Vision Algorithm Engineer - PICO Lab (San Jose) - ByteDance</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6b0b100c46440674</link>
        <description>**Location:**  

San Jose
  
  

**Team:**  

Technology
  
  

**Employment Type:**  

Regular
  
  

**Job Code:**  

A174273
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About Team
  
PICO’s Imaging Systems \&amp; Human Engineering team is looking for passionate and versatile imaging experts to work on next\-generation imaging algorithms that deliver top\-tier visual experiences across PICO products, from camera capture to display rendering.
  
  

Our team focuses on the end\-to\-end imaging pipeline, bridging camera systems, display technologies, and human visual perception. We develop and evaluate imaging algorithms that span optical design, digital image processing, computer vision, and system\-level optimization, with a strong emphasis on image quality, efficiency, and real\-world user experience.
  
  

Team members play a key role in shaping both technology direction and productization roadmaps, contributing to the future of imaging technologies and their applications in VR/MR/AR devices
  
  </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer - Backend - Uber</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=371b123ed1445e56</link>
        <description>**About the Role**
  

  

You will be a Senior Software Engineer in the Machine Learning Platform team and involved in the development and implementation of the infrastructure layer for multi\-modal data processing and ML. The ideal candidate will be able to identify issues, provide solutions and implement the fixes as well as setting a high technical excellence bar in all things we do. You'll be able to collaborate across Platform Engineering teams which include areas such as networking, storage, compute, big data and cloud engineering.  

  

**What the Candidate Will Need / Bonus Points**
  

  

Design and deliver software and tools as part of our state\-of\-the\-art Machine Learning platform  

* Systems architecture design, including management of upstream and downstream dependencies
* Provide technical leadership, influence and partner with fellow engineers to architect, design and build scalable solutions for ML technology that can stand the test of scale and availability, whi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026) - Cadence Design Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=55f7883904d0c65e</link>
        <description>At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology.
AI \&amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026\)
As an intern, you will join a dynamic team of software developers and research‑minded engineers shaping the future of AI‑accelerated chip design and verification. You will be part of the SVG (System Verification Group), whose charter is to develop state‑of‑the‑art EDA software and hardware platforms used for high‑performance functional verification of advanced integrated circuits.
Our products include industry‑leading simulation (Xcelium), formal (Jasper), hardware acceleration (Palladium), FPGA prototyping (Protium), and embedded software bring‑up environments (Helium). Increasingly, these next‑generation verification systems incorporate AI, automation, and advanced data‑driven workflows \- and that’s where you come in!
What You’ll Work On
You will contribute to applied research and engineering projects that sit at the intersection of AI</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI &amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026) - Cadence Design Systems</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ca56a1a56a60215d</link>
        <description>At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology.
AI \&amp; Chip Design Intern (Summer 2026\)
As an intern, you will join a dynamic team of software developers and research‑minded engineers shaping the future of AI‑accelerated chip design and verification. You will be part of the SVG (System Verification Group), whose charter is to develop state‑of‑the‑art EDA software and hardware platforms used for high‑performance functional verification of advanced integrated circuits.
Our products include industry‑leading simulation (Xcelium), formal (Jasper), hardware acceleration (Palladium), FPGA prototyping (Protium), and embedded software bring‑up environments (Helium). Increasingly, these next‑generation verification systems incorporate AI, automation, and advanced data‑driven workflows \- and that’s where you come in!
What You’ll Work On
You will contribute to applied research and engineering projects that sit at the intersection of AI</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Anti-Cheat Engineer, ARM64 - Electronic Arts</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=168a826695554fb0</link>
        <description>### **General Information**

**Locations**: Redwood City, California, United States of America
* Location: Redwood City
* State: California
* Country: United States of America

  

Role ID
212781
Worker Type
Regular Employee
Studio/Department
CT \- Security
Work Model
Hybrid
### **Description \&amp; Requirements**

Electronic Arts creates next\-level entertainment experiences that inspire players and fans around the world. Here, everyone is part of the story. Part of a community that connects across the globe. A place where creativity thrives, new perspectives are invited, and ideas matter. A team where everyone makes play happen.
### **EA Security**

**Location:**Hybrid and Possibly Remote work options available across most North America locations


Join the SPEAR (Secure Product Engineering \&amp; Anti\-Cheat Response) Anti\-Cheat Engineering team, part of EA Security! Our mission is to ensure fair play across our many PC titles. We deliver EA Javelin Anticheat, a kernel anti\-cheat solution</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>CPU Architect - Samsung Electronics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1d42789699ec445e</link>
        <description>Position Summary
Samsung, a world leader in advanced semiconductor technology, is founded on a simple philosophy – the endless pursuit of excellence will create a better world for all. At Samsung Austin Research and Development Center (SARC) and Advanced Computing Lab (ACL), we are building a center of excellence for Intellectual Property (IP) that is applied to high\-performance computing devices (mobile, automotive, and other custom market segments) consumed by millions of people around the world. Come build with us!
Role and Responsibilities
We are seeking a highly experienced CPU Architect to join our team at Samsung SARC/ACL. As a CPU Architect, you will be responsible for designing and developing innovative CPU architectures that meet the demands of Samsung’s Exynos flagship SoCs, with a focus on delivering high\-performance, power\-efficient, and secure processors.* You design and develop CPU architectures that meet performance, power, and area requirements
* You perform quantit</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineer - Agent Automation - Zoom Communications</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f5af786d5985c54f</link>
        <description>What you can expect


We're seeking an experienced AI Engineer specialized in agent orchestrator design and implementation, agent workflow, and LLM evaluation metrics and pipeline design. You'll be instrumental in developing and deploying intelligent agent systems that can understand context, orchestrate multi\-step processes, automate complex workflows, and execute tasks autonomously across Zoom. Your expertise will help us create agents that streamline operations, reduce manual intervention, and optimize end\-to\-end business processes through intelligent automation.


About the Team


The Agentic Workflow Automation team is committed to revolutionizing productivity by streamlining complex workflows, automating routine tasks, and making decisions with great speed and clarity. We are passionate about leveraging cutting\-edge technology to drive significant advancements in how people communicate and collaborate.


Responsibilities


* Designing and implementing agent architectures that</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Bioinformatics Research Engineer II - Freenome</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81f00d48d521c4d0</link>
        <description>**About this opportunity:**

  


As a Senior Bioinformatics Research Engineer, you will work on Freenome's computational platform for R\&amp;D, developing and deploying bioinformatics research software and tooling. As part of an interdisciplinary R\&amp;D team, you will work in close collaboration with computational biologists, machine learning scientists and software engineers. You will develop cutting edge solutions at the intersection of machine learning, genetic sequencing technology, biological data, and distributed systems. These contributions will drive our mission to diagnose cancer at its most actionable and early stages.



The role reports to a Director of Bioinformatics Research Engineering. This role can be a Hybrid role based in our Brisbane, California headquarters (2\-3 days per week in office), or remote.


**What you'll do:**


* Work at the intersection of computational biology, machine learning research, software engineering and biological data.
* Lead the development of F</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Application Engineer, Foundry - Parallel Bio</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0a00640e862bca2d</link>
        <description>At Parallel Bio, we are leveraging the human immune system to unlock safer, more effective drugs. We believe immunotherapies are the future of medicine, but their discovery is hindered by outdated models that fail to capture the complexity of the human immune system.


Our platform overcomes these challenges by combining best\-in\-class human immune organoids with massive scale and advanced computational methods, including AI and machine learning. This allows us to generate unprecedented, population\-scale insights into human health and disease.


We can rapidly discover new drugs that we know will work in patients from the start and understand how they will perform across an entire population—something not possible with today's technology. This knowledge will allow us to engineer therapies that will work for as many people as possible, ensuring a safe and effective cure for everyone.


We are a fast\-paced, venture\-backed company at a pivotal moment of growth. Join us on our journey </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Software Engineer, GenAI Quality, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bbb72fcd176e000a</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Cambridge, MA, USA; New York, NY, USA; Mountain View, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Computer Science or related technical field, or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in software development.
* 7 years of experience leading technical project strategy, ML design, and working with industry\-scale ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
* 5 years of experience with design and architecture; and testing/launching software products.
* Experience with Generative AI technologies (e.g., LLM capabilities and applications).
* Experience working on search quality.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 8 years of experience with data structures/algorithms.
* 5 years of experience in a technical leadership role leading project teams and setting technic</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Product Manager, GenAI Workspace Safety and Security - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c4fac855740b6fce</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; New York, NY, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 8 years of experience in product management, or a related technical role.
* 3 years of experience developing or launching products or technologies within Artificial Intelligence/Machine Learning (AI/ML).
* Experience working with AI technologies and generative models.
* Experience taking products from conception to launch.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a technology or business related field.
* 5 years of experience in a business function or role (e.g., strategic marketing, business operations, consulting).
* 5 years of experience in product management, specifically bringing innovative software products to market.
* 4 years of experience in a role preparing and delivering technical presentations to exec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Engineer, AI Compute, Google Distributed Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ce936191f4ed0023</link>
        <description>In accordance with Washington state law, we are highlighting our comprehensive benefits package, which is available to all eligible US based employees. Benefits for this role include:  

* Health, dental, vision, life, disability insurance
* Retirement Benefits: 401(k) with company match
* Paid Time Off: 20 days of vacation per year, accruing at a rate of 6\.15 hours per pay period for the first five years of employment
* Sick Time: 40 hours/year (statutory, where applicable); 5 days/event (discretionary)
* Maternity Leave (Short\-Term Disability \+ Baby Bonding): 28\-30 weeks
* Baby Bonding Leave: 18 weeks
* Holidays: 13 paid days per year

  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; Cambridge, MA, USA; Raleigh, NC, USA; Durham, NC, USA; Seattle, WA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree in Engineering, Computer Science, or related technical field, or equival</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Search Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=24a214971b475f10</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Pittsburgh, PA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience with software development in C\+\+ and Python.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend well beyond web search. We're looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from all areas, including information </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Data Center Infrastructure Management Cooling - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=638776a688f698d1</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with coding in C\+\+ and Python, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with distributed computing.
* 1 year of experience with SQL.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science, or a related technical field.
* Experience working with two or more from the following: data analysis, data processing pipelines, distributed and parallel systems, machine learning, information retrieval, web application development, Unix/Linux environments, mobile application development, natural language processing, networking, developing large software systems, or security software development.
* Experience with monitoring systems and cooling systems.

**About the job**
-----------------


The DCIM (Data Center Infrastructure Management) Cooling team's mission is to deliver reliable, efficient, and intelligent cooling soluti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Engineer, YouTube ML Recommendations Systems - Youtube</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9eb19e998f2c09f2</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, similar technical field of study, or equivalent practical experience
* 15 years of software engineering experience, including technical leadership
* Engineering experience in machine learning with a focus in ML systems and recommendations, software development, and implementation

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master’s degree or PhD in Computer Science or related field
* 15 years of professional experience in engineering
* Experience with full\-stack backend software development and implementation of sustainable, well\-designed systems and data pipelines, with production launch/impact
* Deep technical expertise in building large\-scale machine learning systems, and knowledge of ML models/algorithm design/implementation, and their application to real\-world problems
* Ability to communicate and collaborate effectively to create a shared sense of vision or purpose
* Demonstrated track record of technical</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=462e153bfa108b02</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**About Team:**
**The Merchant Technology team builds best\-in\-class experiences to make the Merchant's life easier for millions of buying decisions. We are a group of software engineers, data scientists, and machine learning experts pushing the boundaries of GenAI technology in complex enterprise applications. The Merchant Technology team is part of the US Omni Tech organization in Walmart Global Tech. We partner with our product, business and UX teams to drive significant measurable business impact. Our mission is to help Merchants make the right decisions for buying the best assortment mix for our customers to save money and live better.**
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff, Software Engineer - Walmart</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bb26820e22eaf9c6</link>
        <description>**Position Summary...**
-----------------------

**What you'll do...**
---------------------

**The Merchant Technology team builds best\-in\-class experiences to make the Merchant's life easier for millions of buying decisions. We are a group of software engineers, data scientists, and machine learning experts pushing the boundaries of GenAI technology in complex enterprise applications. The Merchant Technology team is part of the US Omni Tech organization in Walmart Global Tech. We partner with our product, business and UX teams to drive significant measurable business impact. Our mission is to help Merchants make the right decisions for buying the best assortment mix for our customers to save money and live better.**
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Product Manager - AI Context - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92e658ee3102acc</link>
        <description>**Category** Product Management **Location** Mountain View, California **Job ID** 19995
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the AI Foundations Product Management Team at Intuit as a Senior Staff Product Manager for our AI Context Platform. Our AI Foundations team is part of the Product Development Acceleration (PDX) organization. We empower developers, including data scientists, ML engineers, and software engineers, across Intuit to build, train, deploy, and innovate with Machine Learning, Generative AI, and Agentic AI technologies. Our goal is to deliver </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist – EDA Datacenter Observability and Reliability - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bce841bced1704c0</link>
        <description>NVIDIA’s Hardware Infrastructure organization is seeking a Senior Data Scientist to support EDA datacenter observability, hardware reliability, and capacity forecasting. In this role, you will work closely with hardware, software, and infrastructure engineering teams to analyze large\-scale observability and telemetry data generated by EDA workloads running across global CPU and GPU compute clusters.
We work with observability and platform teams to turn raw infrastructure and workload data into meaningful conclusions. These conclusions will help improve reliability, availability, performance, and long\-term datacenter scaling. Our work will directly inform operational decisions and long\-term planning for NVIDIA’s rapidly growing EDA environment.
What You’ll Be Doing:* Collaborate with hardware, software, infrastructure, and observability teams to define analytical requirements for EDA datacenter monitoring and reliability
* Examine large\-scale observability data, hardware health sign</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Compiler Engineer - Backend GPU - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d49adbd656acb48d</link>
        <description>NVIDIA's invention of the GPU 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing — with the GPU acting as the brain of computers, robots, and self\-driving cars that can perceive and understand the world. Today, we are increasingly known as “the AI computing company”.
We are searching for a Senior Backend Compiler Engineer with experience in LLVM code generation for an exciting and fun role in our GPU Software organization. Our Compiler team is responsible for constructing and emitting the highest performance GPU machine instructions for Graphics (OpenGL, Vulkan, DX) and Compute (CUDA, PTX, OpenCL, Fortran, C\+\+). This team is comprised of worldwide leading compiler engineering experts who provide leading edge performance and capabilities for NVIDIA's current and future complex parallel SIMT architectures.
What you will be doing:* Guid</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Mask Design Engineer - Hardware - NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=cbe8136cd407fb52</link>
        <description>NVIDIA has continuously reinvented itself over two decades. Our invention of the GPU in 1999 sparked the growth of the PC gaming market, redefined modern computer graphics, and revolutionized parallel computing. More recently, GPU deep learning ignited modern AI — the next era of computing. NVIDIA is a “learning machine” that constantly evolves by adapting to new opportunities that are hard to take on, that only we can pursue, and that matter to the world. This is our life’s work, to amplify human creativity and intelligence. We would love to hear from you!
We are looking for a Senior Mask Layout Design Engineer, someone who is excited to join a growing and dynamic group of diverse individuals responsible for handling meaningful high\-speed mixed\-signal circuit designs.
What you'll be doing:* Performing physical layout for mixed\-signal functions like PLL's, high speed SerDes, Analog to Digital converters, ESD structures designs in state\-of\-the\-art sub\-micron CMOS technologies usi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Perception Evaluation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a2df945166e2d4bc</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


3582


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


The Perception Evaluation team at Waymo is at the forefront of autonomous driving, ensuring the safety and reliability of our self\-driving technology. We develop and uti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>EM SF - Hive</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=45685e14254f84c5</link>
        <description>**About Hive**

Hive is the leading provider of cloud\-based AI solutions to understand, search, and generate content, and is trusted by hundreds of the world's largest and most innovative organizations. The company empowers developers with a portfolio of best\-in\-class, pre\-trained AI models, serving billions of customer API requests every month. Hive also offers turnkey software applications powered by proprietary AI models and datasets, enabling breakthrough use cases across industries. Together, Hive’s solutions are transforming content moderation, brand protection, sponsorship measurement, context\-based ad targeting, and more.

Hive has raised over $120M in capital from leading investors, including General Catalyst, 8VC, Glynn Capital, Bain \&amp; Company, Visa Ventures, and others. We have over 250 employees globally in our San Francisco, Seattle, and Delhi offices. Please reach out if you are interested in joining the future of AI!

**Engineering Manager Role**

In order to execu</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Implementation Support Engineer - Taulia</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1a2e258c5eaaaef9</link>
        <description>### **Taulia's Commitment:**

**Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion**
------------------------------------


It is our duty to create and advance a diverse and inclusive company where all Taulians feel they are celebrated. All individuals are welcomed, free to express themselves and rewarded for showing up as authentically every day. By hiring women, people of color, individuals with disabilities, veterans, people of all sexual orientations and from underrepresented and marginalized communities, Taulia will revolutionize fintech.

**About the Job**
-----------------


We are seeking a highly capable AI Implementation Support Engineer to join our IT Department. This critical role will be instrumental in empowering our employees and teams to effectively integrate Artificial Intelligence into their daily work processes and workflows. The AI Implementation Support Engineer will serve as the primary AI technical implementation and support expert.

  

When not engaged in primary AI support dut</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineering Manager, Test Automation - Apple Maps - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=262793efcd643fa4</link>
        <description>At Apple Maps, we're not just building world\-class location experiences \- we're shaping the future of how people explore and navigate the world. As a Software Development Engineering Manager in Test Automation, you'll lead a high\-impact team that's passionate about quality, automation, and innovation. You'll drive the development and evolution of sophisticated test automation solutions that ensure the reliability and performance of Maps across all Apple platforms and devices.  

  

Our team culture is built on deep collaboration, shared ownership, and the principle that quality is everyone's responsibility. We support each other, challenge each other, and grow together\-all while solving some of the most complex test automation problems at Apple. If you're energized by mentoring talented engineers, pushing boundaries in automation and AI\-driven testing, and working with an exceptional group of collaborators, we'd love to have you join us.  

  

**Description**  

  

As the Softw</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Sensing &amp; Health Software Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9c2825b289b3a9d3</link>
        <description>Join the Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team and build the software systems that will enable the next generation of fitness, safety, health experiences. We are a highly multi\-disciplinary team and we tackle the most challenging problems in this space. As a member of our team, you will have the unique and rewarding opportunity to shape upcoming products that will motivate and inspire millions of Apple's customers every single day.  

  

**Description**  

  

The Applied Sensing \&amp; Health team delivers Health/Fitness/Safety features for Apple Watch, iPhones and other Apple products. We are looking for software engineers who care deeply about their craft to join our team.  

  

","responsibilities":"The roles and responsibilities include designing and implementing software for algorithms, optimizing implementations for power, memory and performance, and operating at the intersection of software and data engineering. You will work with scientists, engineers, QA, and project managers through</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Xcode Intelligence Foundation Engineer - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8b672bc6e5a8fd4a</link>
        <description>The Xcode Intelligence Foundations team develops tools and systems that empower developers worldwide to leverage the creative power of machine learning in software development. From developers taking their first steps to teams building large, complex apps, our work underpins intelligence features across Xcode. Our goal is to equip developers on Apple platforms with dependable, well\-crafted, and thoughtfully designed tools that reduce the time between idea and outcome, enhance software quality, and build remarkable experiences.  

  

**Description**  

  

This team is responsible for building and maintaining frameworks, systems, and approaches that integrate Xcode with a variety of intelligent tools for developers \- including third\-party coding agents and large language models.  

  

Day\-to\-day, engineers on the Xcode Intelligence Foundations team work cross\-functionally with peers at Apple and our industry partners to build features, troubleshoot issues, and help prototype and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AIML - Machine Learning Engineer, Technical Lead, Evaluation - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9f23b4d235cec13e</link>
        <description>Do you want to play a part in building a groundbreaking technology for large scale systems, generative AI experiences and shipping next generation of Apple products?  

  

You will improve and enrich lives of Apple users across the globe.  

  

Join the Evaluation team at Apple AIML.  

  

**Description**  

  

You will play a critical role in scaling up global evaluation of Apple AIML products, with the primary focus on next generation Siri and Apple Intelligence features.  

  

You will drive and scale our evaluation work to enable high\-velocity development and shipping of Generative AI features globally, in every country and language where Apple AIML features are available.  

  

You will drive LLM\-based evaluation as a product, delivering simulation\-based evaluation of personalized user experiences, reflective of cultural and language diversity of our customers.  

  

The focus of this technical lead role is strategy and execution of high quality evaluation datasets groun</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Engineer, Apple Intelligence Model Platform - Apple</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e402448eed057538</link>
        <description>The Proactive Intelligence Platform is at the heart of an intelligent system experience that understands you and anticipates your needs. We are building an on\-device personal and contextual intelligence platform that will benefit the millions of people who use Apple devices every day. Our team is comprised of Systems engineers and ML engineers focused on seamlessly integrating intelligence into all Apple products. Our team is responsible for developing exciting new features across all Apple platforms \- iOS, macOS, watchOS, tvOS, visionOS, and private cloud compute. You should have a strong understanding of operating system fundamentals and experience working throughout the stack. As a member of the team, you would participate in all stages of software development, from new feature design and implementation, to maintenance and bug fixing of released code. You will develop and improve unit tests and performance tests, and may also work on diagnosing and resolving customer reported issu</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Software Engineer - AI/ML Infra - GEICO</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=976e18ca019d1a9e</link>
        <description>**At GEICO, we offer a rewarding career where your ambitions are met with endless possibilities.**

**Every day we honor our iconic brand by offering quality coverage to millions of customers and being there when they need us most. We thrive through relentless innovation to exceed our customers’ expectations while making a real impact for our company through our shared purpose.**

**When you join our company, we want you to feel valued, supported and proud to work here. That’s why we offer The GEICO Pledge: Great Company, Great Culture, Great Rewards and Great Careers.**


GEICO AI platform and Infrastructure team is seeking an exceptional Senior ML Platform Engineer to build and scale our machine learning infrastructure with a focus on Large Language Models (LLMs) and AI applications. This role combines deep technical expertise in cloud platforms, container orchestration, and ML operations with strong leadership and mentoring capabilities. You will be responsible for designing, implem</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Engineer - Large Driving Model, Autonomy - Rivian</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=05b421d451b57eac</link>
        <description>About Us:

Rivian is on a mission to keep the world adventurous forever. This goes for the emissions\-free Electric Adventure Vehicles we build, and the curious, courageous souls we seek to attract.  

As a company, we constantly challenge what’s possible, never simply accepting what has always been done. We reframe old problems, seek new solutions and operate comfortably in areas that are unknown. Our backgrounds are diverse, but our team shares a love of the outdoors and a desire to protect it for future generations.
Role Summary:

We are seeking a Staff Data Engineer to drive the advancement of our Large Driving Model (LDM). The successful candidate will be responsible for the end\-to\-end data strategy that fuels our models, from mining and curation to experimental collaboration. You will build the pipelines that surface high\-value examples, refine evaluation benchmarks, and partner closely with modeling teams to accelerate model performance. Your work will directly influence the </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Manager, Site Reliability Engineering - tubi</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=07aa54a0f2204a4f</link>
        <description>**About the Role:**



Site Reliability Engineering (SRE) at Tubi is not a traditional operations team. We are a software engineering organization that applies a developer's mindset and toolkit to the challenges of building and running large\-scale, distributed systems. Our mission is to engineer resilience from the ground up, enabling our product teams to innovate rapidly while ensuring our users have a stellar experience. We own the availability, latency, performance, and capacity of our platform, and we achieve our goals through a culture of data\-driven decision\-making, blameless learning, and relentless automation.



We are seeking an experienced and visionary Senior SRE Manager to lead and grow our newly built Site Reliability Engineering team. You are more than a people manager or a tech lead; you are the strategic leader responsible for architecting our reliability roadmap. You will build and mentor a team of talented engineers, foster a culture of blameless learning and cont</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Safety Foundation - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7de9fc1c8239d0bc</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5747
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY SAFETY?**  

At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization's mission is to become the leader in civil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, Application Networking - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ed5ddfcbd6b526cc</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5599
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


Roblox is reimagining the way people come together to connect, create, and express themselves. To support our massive scale, we are powered by microservices. The App</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Home Modeling - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=81b718c5458f23d5</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5803
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning engineers who thrive on solving complex challenges and designi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytical Data Product - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5a687a75e4c295db</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5202
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer - Fullstack, Account Identity - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ebe51fb9fc608a07</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5848
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY SAFETY?**  

At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization's mission is to become the leader in civil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Platform Engineer, ML Platform - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=195e8264cf1c046f</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5304
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


ML Platform powers hundreds of use cases and billions of inferences per day across Discovery, Safety, Economy, and Creation. We build the primitives that let teams t</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior / Principal Inference Engineer - ML Platform - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e849e139e8be97e7</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 4797
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior / Principal Inference Engineer on ML Platform you will build the next generation of ML Ecosystem Tooling, specifically around model inference. ML Platfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal AI Platform Engineer, Agentic Systems - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bb2cdb306ac437ae</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5455
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


Join the **AI Platform** team at Roblox, where our mission is to create a cutting\-edge AI/ML platform that powers some of the most innovative and widely used produc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Content Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=279fa0acdf16465e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5885
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**Why Content Safety?**
-----------------------



As a **Principal Machine Learning Engineer** for Content Safety, you will define the future of proactive moderation</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Avatar - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3de71cfb924c3f12</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5891
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The **Avatar Team** is at the heart of the Roblox experience. The Roblox Avatar defines the identity of every player and is a core pillar of the metaverse. Our team </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Software Engineer, User Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=e7644a1e91455820</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5906
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY SAFETY?**



At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization's mission is to become the leader in civil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Embodied AI and Smart NPCs - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f99abbc2884b814c</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5898
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Principal Machine Learning Engineer within the Creator Services Machine Intelligence team, you will focus on the research and development of Embodied AI and Beh</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Safety Core Data - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4fa7369cec471d81</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5759
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

#### **Why Safety?**



At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization’s mission is to become the leader in </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Applied Scientist, Off-Search, Sponsored Products and Brands - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=1405904aa9eb7cc8</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights.
  

  

We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover mo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied Scientist, Sponsored Products Off-Search Sourcing - Amazon.com</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=3c23a5d869560c79</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


The Sponsored Products and Brands (SPB) team at Amazon Ads is re\-imagining the advertising landscape through state\-of\-the\-art generative AI technologies, revolutionizing how millions of customers discover products and engage with brands across Amazon.com and beyond. We are at the forefront of re\-inventing advertising experiences, bridging human creativity with artificial intelligence to transform every aspect of the advertising lifecycle from ad creation and optimization to performance analysis and customer insights. We are a passionate group of innovators dedicated to developing responsible and intelligent AI technologies that balance the needs of advertisers, enhance the shopping experience, and strengthen the marketplace. If you're energized by solving complex challenges and pushing the boundaries of what's possible with AI, join us in shaping the future of advertising.  

  

Curious about our advertising solutions? Discover more about Sponsor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Software Development Engineer II, C/C++ Hardware/Software Co-Design - MLA Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f1070d3a794f62e9</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Software Development Engineer, C/C++ Hardware/Software Co-Design - MLA Annapurna Labs - Amazon Web Services</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=5155c20d48c88537</link>
        <description>**DESCRIPTION**
---------------


Annapurna Labs stands at the forefront of hardware/software co\-design, leading innovation not just within Amazon Web Services (AWS) but across the entire industry. We design and build every component of our hardware and software to create best\-in\-class machine learning products that accelerate customer workloads through industry leading hardware using our custom silicon solutions. If you're passionate about building the highest\-performing, hardware\-accelerated Machine Learning systems and want to be part of the entire journey from pre\- through post\-silicon development, Annapurna Labs offers an exceptional career opportunity. Join us in shaping the future of AI acceleration  

  

At the heart of AWS Machine Learning servers reside our custom Amazon\-designed silicon that powers next\-generation machine learning capabilities for our customers. We're seeking an experienced C/C\+\+ engineer to join our embedded software team, where you'll develop b</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Intern - AI Software QA Engineer - Fremont Bank</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2e20f3e88254de62</link>
        <description>**Job Title: AI Software QA Engineer Intern**  

**Location: Livermore, CA**  

**Hiring Salary Range: $20\.00 per hour**  

  

**Position Summary**  

  

Fremont Bank — one of the Bay Area’s most respected and long\-standing financial institutions — is seeking a strategic, hands\-on intern to join and help advance our Information Technology team. This is a high\-impact opportunity to contribute to the success of a mission\-driven organization committed to excellence, community service, and strong client relationships.  

  

If you're energized by purpose\-driven work, collaboration, and delivering meaningful results, we’d love to connect.  

  

**Why Fremont Bank?**  

  

Founded in 1964, Fremont Bank is one of the oldest independently owned banks in the Bay Area and has been consistently recognized as a Top Workplace for the past 15 consecutive years. Our foundation is built on relationships — with our clients, our associates, and our communities.  

  

We offer:

* A people\-f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Model Design Staff - Language Engineer - Microsoft</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4d545902eea1b2ce</link>
        <description>**Overview**  


Microsoft AI is pushing the boundaries of technology. We are creating unique, beautiful and powerful products that will change lives. As a small, friendly, fast\-moving team, we support each other to do the best work of our lives, always looking to break new ground, fast. We are proud of what we build, how we build it and that our products will define the AI era. We run lean, obsess about users, and always make our decisions based on the evidence. We ship regularly, so your work will have real and immediate impact. It’s a time of huge change in the AI landscape, and this role will put you right in the heart of it.

We’re on the lookout for a detail\-oriented **Language Engineer** to help build the next wave of capabilities of our personal AI, Copilot. Language is an increasingly important modality for how we interact with computers. As a Language Engineer on the Copilot team, you will be responsible for how Copilot wields language. You will collaboratively work with da</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior GTM Data Scientist New - Intercom</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=321b9d7d7adb85f1</link>
        <description>Intercom is the AI Customer Service company on a mission to help businesses provide incredible customer experiences.



Our AI agent Fin, the most advanced customer service AI agent on the market, lets businesses deliver always\-on, impeccable customer service and ultimately transform their customer experiences for the better. Fin can also be combined with our Helpdesk to become a complete solution called the Intercom Customer Service Suite, which provides AI enhanced support for the more complex or high touch queries that require a human agent.



Founded in 2011 and trusted by nearly 30,000 global businesses, Intercom is setting the new standard for customer service. Driven by our core values, we push boundaries, build with speed and intensity, and consistently deliver incredible value to our customers.

**What's the opportunity?**
---------------------------



Intercom is building a **GTM Data Products** team to embed machine learning and AI directly into our Sales and Marketing wo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Intern, Bixby Edge AI, Language (Summer) - Samsung Research America</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=8e77ec814edded0d</link>
        <description>**Lab Summary:**



Advanced Intelligence Lab at Samsung Research America is working towards a vision of a world\-class voice assistant that provides a unified AI experience across multiple devices (Galaxy Smartphones, Galaxy Watch \&amp; Smart home appliances like TVs, Family Hub, IoT devices etc.) with deep integration and building AI assisted services intelligent solutions.



We work on applied research, innovative products, services, and experiences to delight our users by promoting new technologies to make best user experience with Bixby on devices to be intuitive, faster, seamless, more powerful, and multi\-dimensional across different product domains/categories. Our goal is to improve user's lifestyles through technology advancement and experience enrichment.


**Position Summary:**



Bixby is an intelligent personal assistant which is only available as a built\-in application on Samsung flagship devices and wearables. This application uses Natural Language Understanding to perfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>2026 Intern, Memory and Personalization (Summer) - Samsung Research America</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=038e06c5fa27ee8e</link>
        <description>**Lab Summary:**



Advanced Intelligence Lab at Samsung Research America is working towards a vision of a world\-class voice assistant that provides a unified AI experience across multiple devices (Galaxy Smartphones, Galaxy Watch \&amp; Smart home appliances like TVs, Family Hub, IoT devices etc.) with deep integration and building AI assisted services intelligent solutions.



We work on applied research, innovative products, services, and experiences to delight our users by promoting new technologies to make best user experience with Bixby on devices to be intuitive, faster, seamless, more powerful, and multi\-dimensional across different product domains/categories. Our goal is to improve user's lifestyles through technology advancement and experience enrichment.


**Position Summary:**



Bixby is an intelligent personal assistant which is only available as a built\-in application on Samsung flagship devices and wearables. This application uses Natural Language Understanding to perfor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Applied AI Engineer - WorkOS</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b1b1d0796510f0e4</link>
        <description>**About WorkOS**


WorkOS builds tools and services for developers to help them implement authentication, identity, authorization, and overall enterprise readiness. We’re a fully distributed team with employees across North American time zones. We’re well\-funded, having raised $100m in funding from top investors including Greenoaks Capital, Lachy Groom, and Lightspeed Ventures. Our fast\-growing customer base includes rapidly growing SaaS companies like OpenAI, Cursor, Perplexity, Vercel, Plaid, and hundreds of others.

**About the Role**
------------------


We’re building an Applied AI function to dramatically increase productivity across Engineering, Sales, Support, and Operations.


As an Applied AI Engineer, you’ll design and ship production AI systems that change how WorkOS builds, sells, and supports software. Your focus is internal: building durable tools and workflows that teammates rely on every day.


You’ll work on a small, high‑ownership team that:

* Chooses problems bas</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Ads - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b6a46f94f385e069</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5477
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning engineers who thrive on solving complex challenges and designi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Machine Learning Infrastructure Engineer, Content Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6e78cd0c47e72b17</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5749
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**Why Content Safety?**



Safety and civility are Roblox’s top priorities. Our mission is to protect our community by ensuring that all user\-generated content on th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Dynamic Economics - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9812bc1ecb5f1b0d</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5819
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a **Senior Machine Learning Engineer** on the **Economy ML** team, you will build models that power ranking, personalization, pricing, and optimization across Rob</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior/Principal Data Scientist, Creator Ecosystem - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=86126cb9407992f9</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5915
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior/Principal Data Scientist, you will be a strategic thought partner to our product and engineering leadership, specifically aligning with th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Distinguished Machine Learning Engineer - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=30c093a2b8a15716</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 4733
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Distinguished Machine Learning Engineer/Technical Director in the Safety organization at Roblox, you will drive the overall technical vision and execution for a</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist - Analytical Data Product (Temporary) - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7551d101967e86c9</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5392
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS (DSA)?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization’s mission is to increase the speed, frequency, and acumen of dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Analytical Data Product - Engine - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=baa3bcaf9d537827</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5748
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Generative AI - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c7741e88c36a750e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5610
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency, and acumen in making de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Risk Data Analyst - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=6fddc9936f689654</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5720
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


As a Senior Risk Data Analyst in our Payments organization, you will play a critical role in defending Roblox from various types of payment fraud across the platform</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - App Performance - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=49eee3b459fce011</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5887
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making decisions at scale by instilling a data\</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal/Senior Machine Learning Scientist - Search and Discovery - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=f9c0a5d5df1e3455</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5927
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


With Roblox’s daily active users growing at a record pace, we are seeking experienced machine learning researchers who thrive on solving complex challenges and desig</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Technical Director - Data Science (Discovery) - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=559bb4df8e70354b</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5526
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, People Science - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=2bc01ba9eb5d6b8b</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5460
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The People Science team at Roblox supports our Talent Acquisition organization and broader People, Places, \&amp; Systems group with applied statistics an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Ecosystem and Learning Platform - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fe68bb659770aec8</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5633
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency, and acumen in making de</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist - Growth Measurement - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b59b60244b1feafd</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5694
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of making dec</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr Machine Learning Engineer - Safety Experience - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7d89b400e85c1207</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5408
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The **Rights Manager** team and the **Content Suitability** team that are part of our **Safety Experience** are looking to hire a Sr Machine Learning Engineer for th</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Safety Experience - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d0097f0dd9bd5aef</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5384
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The Safety Experience organization builds the tools and systems that give Roblox Users and Creators control over their experience and empower moderators to enforce o</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Data Scientist, People Analytics - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=d50df090864d3144</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5245
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.


The People Science \&amp; Analytics team at Roblox partners with our People, Places, \&amp; Systems organization to apply data science, applied statistics, an</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Data Scientist - Safety - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=179e018a3941598e</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesData Science \&amp; Analytics ID: 5600
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

#### **WHY DATA SCIENCE \&amp; ANALYTICS?**



The Data Science \&amp; Analytics organization's mission is to increase our speed, frequency and acumen of makin</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Principal Machine Learning Engineer, Alt Defense - Roblox</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0fe68b9e9cda8e1c</link>
        <description>San Mateo, CA, United StatesEngineeringID: 5804
  
Every day, tens of millions of people come to Roblox to explore, create, play, learn, and connect with friends in 3D immersive digital experiences– all created by our global community of developers and creators.


At Roblox, we’re building the tools and platform that empower our community to bring any experience that they can imagine to life. Our vision is to reimagine the way people come together, from anywhere in the world, and on any device.We’re on a mission to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and looking for amazing talent to help us get there.


A career at Roblox means you’ll be working to shape the future of human interaction, solving unique technical challenges at scale, and helping to create safer, more civil shared experiences for everyone.

**WHY SAFETY?**



At Roblox, we strive to connect a billion people with optimism and civility, and the Safety organization’s mission is to become the leader in civil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Tooling &amp; Analytics Intern New - Nimble Robotics</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=b7937e2716900392</link>
        <description>**About Nimble**

Nimble is an AI robotics company building the autonomous supply chain to enable fast, efficient, and sustainable commerce. We’re developing a general\-purpose robot AI and a warehouse generalist superhumanoid robot, the first robot in the world capable of performing all core warehouse functions. We recently closed a $106M Series C at a $1B valuation,and we are continuing to grow our world\-class team.

Mission: to empower and inspire mankind to accomplish legendary feats by inventing robots that liberate us from the menial.

Vision: invent the Autonomous Supply Chain – everything from the inside of factories and warehouses to your front door – powered by industry\-generalist superhumanoids to deliver faster, more efficient, and more sustainable commerce.

Our founding team comes from the AI labs at Stanford and Carnegie Mellon and our board of directors include famed robotics and AI legends including Marc Raibert (founder of Boston Dynamics), Sebastian Thrun (founder </description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Software Engineer, AI/ML, Keywordless Search Ads - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=ac5224630ed4fa22</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience programming in Python or C\+\+.
* 3 years of experience testing, maintaining, or launching software products, and 1 year of experience with software design and architecture.
* 3 years of experience with one or more of the following: reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), multimodal Machine Learning, ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging), or specialization in another ML field.
* Experience with experiment analysis.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical field.
* 5 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* 1 year of experience in a technical leadership role.
* Experience leading and optimizing industry\-scale machine learning infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, data processing, debugging, fine tuning).
</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Staff Research Data Scientist, AI Data Intelligence - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=24b2d7dbd3bf3db6</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in Statistics, Data Science, Mathematics, Physics, Economics, Operations Research, Engineering, or a related quantitative field.
* 10 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 8 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* 12 years of work experience using analytics to solve product or business problems, coding (e.g., Python, R, SQL), querying databases or statistical analysis, or 10 years of work experience with a PhD degree.

**About the job**
-----------------


As a Senior Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a key innovation driver within our AI data organization. You will leverage your expertise in the full life\-cycle of data for large\-scale AI models (specifically Large Language Models (LLMs) from collection and distillation to precision curation and refinement.
In this</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Data Scientist, Statistics, Platform Analytics, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=9255bcdd267e436b</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience in a data science role using data for business or product decisions.
* Experience analyzing data from various sources such as product instrumentation, customer support systems, and internal operational tools.
* Experience with SQL, Python or R programming including advanced data analysis, statistical modeling, and data visualization.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in a relevant quantitati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Business Data Scientist, Statistics, Platform Analytics, Cloud - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0b1e6679a2ebae48</link>
        <description>Applicants in San Francisco: Qualified applications with arrest or conviction records will be considered for employment in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance for Employers and the California Fair Chance Act.  

Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Sunnyvale, CA, USA; San Francisco, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Master's degree in a quantitative discipline such as Statistics, Engineering, Sciences, or equivalent practical experience.
* 4 years of experience in a data science role using data for business or product decisions.
* Experience analyzing data from various sources such as product instrumentation, customer support systems, and internal operational tools.
* Experience with SQL, Python or R programming including advanced data analysis, statistical modeling, and data visualization.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* PhD degree in a relevant quantitati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Intuit Customer Success - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=0f6148143645cc2a</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


Come join the Intuit Customer Success data science team as a Staff Data Scientist to shape the strategy to enable best\-in\-class customer experiences for QuickBook customers.The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most important customer and business challenges.

 **Responsibilities**


We are seeking a Staff Data Scientist to deliver impactful insights into business performance and growth opportunities, build predictive models and insights, and drive measurable outcomes. This role requires a strong background in quantitative analysis, data\-driven decision\-making, and expertise in working with large data sets.
* Conceptualize business problems or opportunities, formulate hypotheses and goals, define key metrics, and make actionable recommendati</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Machine Learning Engineer, App SW - Wayve</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=bc190c129d35caea</link>
        <description>At Wayve we're committed to creating a diverse, fair and respectful culture that is inclusive of everyone based on their unique skills and perspectives, and regardless of sex, race, religion or belief, ethnic or national origin, disability, age, citizenship, marital, domestic or civil partnership status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, pregnancy or related condition (including breastfeeding) or any other basis as protected by applicable law.


**About us**
------------

Founded in 2017, Wayve is the leading developer of Embodied AI technology. Our advanced AI software and foundation models enable vehicles to perceive, understand, and navigate any complex environment, enhancing the usability and safety of automated driving systems.



Our vision is to create autonomy that propels the world forward. Our intelligent, mapless, and hardware\-agnostic AI products are designed for automakers, accelerating the transition from assisted to automated driving.
  

  

In our f</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Quality Engineer, Agent LLM - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=270605f9b0d70944</link>
        <description>### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree.
* 1 year of experience with one or more of the following: Speech/audio (e.g., technology duplicating and responding to the human voice), reinforcement learning (e.g., sequential decision making), ML infrastructure, or specialization in another ML field.
* 1 year of experience with ML infrastructure (e.g., model deployment, model evaluation, optimization, data processing, debugging).

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
* 2 years of experience with data structures and algorithms.
* Experience developing accessible technologies.

**About the job**
-----------------


Google's software engineers develop the next\-generation technologies that change how billions of users connect, explore, and</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-27</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Agentic Platform - Micron Technology</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=fb60204ae54a34bf</link>
        <description>**Our vision is to transform how the world uses information to enrich life for** ***all*** **.**

Micron Technology is a world leader in innovating memory and storage solutions that accelerate the transformation of information into intelligence, inspiring the world to learn, communicate and advance faster than ever.


Micron’s Data Science team builds AI and data‑driven capabilities that power breakthroughs in semiconductor process technology, product engineering, and manufacturing. We work hands\-on with massive datasets, advanced modeling tools, and cross\-disciplinary engineering teams to push the boundaries of intelligent automation and decision\-making.
In this role, you’ll design and deploy AI systems that directly accelerate semiconductor design, verification, validation, and manufacturing. You’ll shape how agentic AI, LLMs, and automated decision systems integrate into Micron’s workflows, improving speed, accuracy, and scalability across the company.
**Responsibilities:*** Buil</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. AI Machine Learning Engineer - A10 Networks</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=459c8aa3afb1e7dd</link>
        <description>Sr. AI Machine Learning Engineer
**Position Overview**
---------------------

We are looking for a talented and experienced Deep Learning Engineer specializing in Large Language Models (LLMs) to join our dynamic team. In this role, you will play a pivotal part in enhancing the reliability, safety, and performance of AI models and systems. You will work closely with AI researchers and product teams to drive cutting\-edge advancements in AI safety and responsible AI solutions.


**Responsibilities**

* Assist in designing and implementing end\-to\-end safety\-focused frameworks for LLMs
* Develop and apply risk mitigation techniques, including safe inference strategies to ensure reliable AI behavior
* Identify vulnerabilities in AI systems and contribute to adversarial testing, bias detection, and mitigation strategies
* Collaborate with cross\-functional teams to integrate safety mechanisms into AI workflows and pipelines
* Design and optimize LLM architectures to improve performance, s</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Sensor Validation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=573132bc8b2144e0</link>
        <description>Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Software Engineering builds the brains of Waymo's fully autonomous driving technology. Our software allows the Waymo Driver to perceive the world around it, make the right decision for every situation, and deliver people safely to their destinations. We think deeply and solve complex technica</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>AI Engineering Tech Lead / Architect - nan</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=a92f4c535a1af9c1</link>
        <description>**Mission**
-----------

At Faros AI, we are reshaping the way engineering organizations operate, with an engineering intelligence platform that provides visibility and context across the organization's software delivery systems. This deep operational context supports engineering leaders today, and is increasingly essential as AI agents begin to operate within real software delivery environments. Faros AI is laying the foundation for how humans and AI will build software together in the years ahead.

**About the Role**
------------------


Join our AI team to build Lighthouse AI \- the intelligence engine that helps engineering leaders understand organizational bottlenecks and improve performance in an age where AI is redefining the engineering craft. You'll work on natural language interfaces, causal analysis models, and ML\-driven insights that impact how thousands of engineers work at companies like Autodesk, Discord, and Vimeo.

**Responsibilities**
--------------------

* Collabor</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Model Risk &amp; Data Analytics, Internal Audit - AMS - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=974f4a3a534da030</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Senior Data Scientist, Model Risk \&amp; Data Analytics, Internal Audit \- AMS
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A174184
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About The Team
  
Internal Audit is a global function responsible for providing independent assurance and evaluating the company's risk management, governance and internal control processes to determine if they are designed and operating effectively. The Internal Audit team plans and executes audit projects according to our risk\-based audit plan by evaluating financial, compliance, operational, and IT processes and controls. We work with business functions in addressing risks and improving the control environment through timely and comprehensive audit work and tracking of remediation actions until completion.
  
  

We are looking for data scientists and AI developers who will power our mission by building data products that enable and empower conti</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Data Scientist, Global Data Analytics for Internal Audit Function - AMS - TikTok</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c276ceaec78f13bf</link>
        <description>Technology
  
  

Senior Data Scientist, Global Data Analytics for Internal Audit Function \- AMS
  
  

Location
  
:
  
  

San Jose
  
  

Employment Type
  
:
  
  

Regular
  
  

Job Code
  
:
  
  

A245992
  
  

Responsibilities
  
  

About The Team
  
Internal Audit is a global function responsible for providing independent assurance and evaluating the company's risk management, governance and internal control processes to determine if they are designed and operating effectively. The Internal Audit team plans and executes audit projects according to our risk\-based audit plan by evaluating financial, compliance, operational, and IT processes and controls. We work with business functions in addressing risks and improving the control environment through timely and comprehensive audit work and tracking of remediation actions until completion.
  
  

We are looking for a data scientist who will power our mission by building data products that enable and empower continuous auditi</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Analyst, Trust and Safety, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=4e9bc141554057be</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in data analysis, including identifying trends, generating summary statistics, and drawing insights from quantitative and qualitative data.
* 5 years of experience managing projects and defining project scope, goals, and deliverables.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with one or more of the following languages: SQL, R, Python, or C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with machine learning systems.
* Experience in prompt engineering and applying large language models for data labeling.
* Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
* Excellent problem\-solving and critical thinking skills with attention to detail in an ever\-chan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Engineering Analyst, Trust and Safety, Search - Google</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=c96b1184d842fbe8</link>
        <description>Note: By applying to this position you will have an opportunity to share your preferred working location from the following: **Mountain View, CA, USA; Sunnyvale, CA, USA**.### **Minimum qualifications:**

* Bachelor's degree or equivalent practical experience.
* 5 years of experience in data analysis, including identifying trends, generating summary statistics, and drawing insights from quantitative and qualitative data.
* 5 years of experience managing projects and defining project scope, goals, and deliverables.

  

### **Preferred qualifications:**

* Master's degree.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with one or more of the following languages: SQL, R, Python, or C\+\+.
* 5 years of experience or familiarity with machine learning systems.
* Experience in prompt engineering and applying large language models for data labeling.
* Excellent written and verbal communication skills.
* Excellent problem\-solving and critical thinking skills with attention to detail in an ever\-chan</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Staff Data Scientist, Intuit Customer Success - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=54469ad0fe08d617</link>
        <description>**Category** Data **Location** Mountain View, California; San Diego, California **Job ID** 19870
  
**Company Overview**
--------------------


Intuit is the global financial technology platform that powers prosperity for the people and communities we serve. With approximately 100 million customers worldwide using products such as TurboTax, Credit Karma, QuickBooks, and Mailchimp, we believe that everyone should have the opportunity to prosper. We never stop working to find new, innovative ways to make that possible.


**Job Overview**
----------------


Come join the Intuit Customer Success data science team as a Staff Data Scientist to shape the strategy to enable best\-in\-class customer experiences for QuickBook customers.The Data Science team plays a critical role in shaping strategy, scaling new businesses, and delivering delightful customer experiences. Our mission is to accelerate decision\-making through advanced models, insights, and experimentation that address our most impo</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer, Sensor Validation - Waymo</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=12e5fb1de98c135b</link>
        <description>MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA, UNITED STATES \| KIRKLAND, WASHINGTON, UNITED STATES


FULL\-TIME


SOFTWARE ENGINEERING


4316


  
Add to favorites
 View favorites

Waymo is an autonomous driving technology company with the mission to be the world's most trusted driver. Since its start as the Google Self\-Driving Car Project in 2009, Waymo has focused on building the Waymo Driver—The World's Most Experienced Driver™—to improve access to mobility while saving thousands of lives now lost to traffic crashes. The Waymo Driver powers Waymo’s fully autonomous ride\-hail service and can also be applied to a range of vehicle platforms and product use cases. The Waymo Driver has provided over ten million rider\-only trips, enabled by its experience autonomously driving over 100 million miles on public roads and tens of billions in simulation across 15\+ U.S. states.


Software Engineering builds the brains of Waymo's fully autonomous driving technology. Our software allows the Waymo Driver to perc</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=7769c33c8462acdc</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across disciplines to run rapid experiments, conduct deep analytical investigations, and drive cross\-functional alignment that unlocks durable customer and revenue growth.



As a Sr. Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a senior technical leader and strategic thought partner to product and business executives. You will shape the growth roadmap by framing ambiguous opportunities, defining measurable hypotheses, and leading the design and interpretation of complex experiments. You will elevate the analytical bar across the organization, applying advanced causal infere</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title>Sr. Staff Data Scientist - Intuit</title>
        <link>https://www.indeed.com/viewjob?jk=18a97eec706734ad</link>
        <description>**Overview**
------------


The Global Business Solutions Group (GBSG) Product Growth team is dedicated to accelerating business outcomes through a data\-driven, product\-led approach to growth. We leverage Product\-Led Growth strategies, scalable growth loops, and rigorous experimentation to identify and amplify the highest\-impact opportunities across the product ecosystem. Our team brings together exceptional talent across disciplines to run rapid experiments, conduct deep analytical investigations, and drive cross\-functional alignment that unlocks durable customer and revenue growth.



As a Sr. Staff Data Scientist, you will serve as a senior technical leader and strategic thought partner to product and business executives. You will shape the growth roadmap by framing ambiguous opportunities, defining measurable hypotheses, and leading the design and interpretation of complex experiments. You will elevate the analytical bar across the organization, applying advanced causal infere</description>
        <postDate>2026-02-26</postDate>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 00:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel>
</rss>
